[dramatic music]...
...   [engine revving]...
...   [music continues]...
...    [dog barking]...
...   [knock on door]...
...     - Yeah?
- I'm looking for Ana Paole.
- No, she doesn't live here anymore.
- Do you know where I can find her?
- Yeah.
[dramatic music]...
...   [music continues]...
...     [rattling]...
...  [instrumental music]...
...    [dog barking]...
...     [sighs]...
...    - Ana? I'm home.
Jesus, what's this mess?
[fly buzzing]...
...Ana, why didn't you clean up?
Ana?
Did you hear me?
Jesus.
I can't believe you're still
mad, this is stupid.
[dramatic music]...
...      Ana?
Are you okay?
Ana?
- I'm here,
just leave me alone.
- Open the door.
[sobbing]...
...  Ana, open the door.
- Leave me alone, please.
- Ana, open the fucking door.
Ana.
What...what did you do?
- I'm sorry.
I had to.
- Who is she?
[sobbing]...
...     [sniffles]...
...   [bones cracking]...
...     [sobbing]...
...  [indistinct chatter]...
... - What do we have here?
Hey, that's my spot.
Move your ass.
What's your problem?
You don't wanna make new friends?
- He's higher than you.
- Pussy.
I told you to move,
motherfucker.
- Bro, I think he's deaf.
- Move.
Or I'm taking your eye.
- What's stopping you?
[Martin grunting]...
...     [grunting]...
...   [glass shattering]...
...  - Did you like that,
motherfucker?
- Stop.
- Who the fuck are you?
- You're gonna kill him.
- Just keep moving.
[groans]...
...     - Wait.
Officer.
Officer. Stop. Here.
- What's the matter, kid?
Everything alright?
[laughing]...
...   [siren wailing]
- Oh, fuck. I'm outta here.
You handle this.
- Stop. Nobody move.
What the fuck is going on here?
- He attacked me.
It was self-defense.
- He attacked you?
- I'm telling the truth.
- You goddamn liar.
Who is he?
- I don't know, some drifter.
- Jesus, he's not breathing.
- Fuck him.
- What the hell
are you waiting for, dumbass?
Grab him before somebody sees us.
Move.
[engine revving]...
...   Get the shovel.
- Lieutenant, we got a 16-14...
...     on progress on Taylor and Seasons.
We need your assistance.
- Send Robinson.
He should be in that area.
- Negative, lieutenant.
Robinson is off duty, sir.
- Okay, I'm on my way.
Shit.
Cover him up.
I'll finish it later.
- I can take care of it.
- You can't even wipe your own ass.
Go home, now.
- Copy that.
[dramatic music]...
...  [instrumental music]...
...    [dog barking]...
... - Here, take my jacket.
Ma. Wake up, ma.
- Shh.
- Ma.
- Leave me alone,
I just got home.
- I need you to come.
- Later.
- Mom, it's an emergency.
- Who is this man?
- I don't know.
He came to the house
asking about Ana.
- Ana?
- Yeah, then he was stabbed at the park.
- And you brought him here?
You have to take him to the hospital.
I can't treat him here.
- I can't.
There was a cop there.
And he was the one
trying to hide his body.
If I take him to the hospital,
he's gonna find him.
- I don't wanna have
anything to do with the police.
- Please, mom,
just do what you can...
...   and I'll get him out of here soon.
I promise.
- Oh, God.
Okay, just get me the first-aid kit.
- Alright.
- No, don't -- don't touch me.
I'm sick.
Don't touch my blood.
- Here, mom.
[Martin grunts]...
...    - Let me die.
Or I'll kill you both.
- Mom.
- Why the hell
would you bring him here?
- I'm sorry.
- You should have left him
where you found him.
What where you thinking?
You idiot.
[sighs]...
...   - You're right.
I'll take him to the hospital.
- Don't. Not yet.
Wait until it's dark.
Otherwise,
someone's gonna see you.
[indistinct radio chatter]...
...   [intense music]...
...   - Son of a bitch.
[groaning]...
...  - Where the fuck am I?
- It's okay, you're safe.
- I don't need your fucking help.
- I...brought you something.
- Here. Drink.
Come on. Drink.
- No.
Leave me alone..
...you deaf motherfucker.
[cat meowing]...
...     - Caleb.
That tagger who saw you last night,
do you know him?
- Why?
- Do you know him or not?
- Fuck.
- What did he do?
- He followed us,
and he took your friend.
- Motherfucker. I'm gonna --
- You're not doing shit.
You'll only fuck it up worst.
Do you hear me?
What's this?
- Breakfast.
- You keep this shit out of my house.
- What's the big deal?
It's not like mom can say
anything anymore.
- Wait here until I come back.
Goddamn idiot.
[indistinct chatter on TV]...
...    [door opens]...
...     - Hi, Peter.
- Hi, mom.
- You're very lucky.
Nobody heard anything at the hospital.
I think we're okay.
Eva?
Where are you?
[sighs]...
...     - What?
[sniffles]...
...- What am I gonna do with you?
Next time you're out.
I won't allow you to fuck it all up again.
I just can't.
I thought you were done with this shit.
- It was just this once --
- Save it.
You heard me.
Next time you're out.
[telephone ringing]...
...   - Morning, Harris.
- Uh, hey, lieutenant.
- How's everything
in our humble little town?
- Peaceful.
Ran a little fender bender
over on Fourth and Burwash...
...  but nobody got hurt,
thank God.
- Nothin' else?
- No.
- Nothing last night?
At least not according to Russell's report.
Why, did you heard something?
- No, just checkin'.
Thank you.
- Oh, the chief called from Black River.
He said he's gonna stay out
there a couple more days.
Thank God his wife's surgery
went so well, huh?
- Oh, good, excellent.
Give him my best if he calls again.
- Yeah.
[dog barking]...
...     - Peter.
It's dark, take him out now.
Make sure nobody sees you.
- Okay.
Hmm, hello?
Sir?
[dog barking]...
...      Eva.
[glass shattering]
- Peter.
- What happened?
- There's someone outside.
- Come on out,
you little faggot.
- What do you want?
- We want you.
Fucking rat.
Get your ass out here, or else
we're comin' in for you.
- I'm calling the police.
Go away.
- Go ahead, bitch, do it.
And I'll burn your house down.
- No, no, no, no, no.
You'll only make it worse.
I'll take care of it.
- If you're not out here in 10..
...I'm smoking you out.
10..
...9, 8..
- I can't let them burn it all down.
- ...7..
- No, Peter.
- ...6..
- 6..
- Peter, they're gonna kill you. Don't go.
- ...5..
- I'm coming out. Stop.
- Don't, Peter.
- ...4..
- Don't go out there, please.
- Mom.
- Please trust me.
- ...3..
- I can take care of it.
- ...2..
[door opens]...
...  - What do you want?
- Come here.
- Oh. Oh, no.
- I swear,
I'm not gonna tell anyone.
- I said get over here.
- Oh, no.
Oh, no. Peter.
No.
- Fucking rat.
- No. Stop it.
Stop it.
- Like to talk, huh?
- Asshole.
- Stop it. Stop, please.
Stop it.
- Stay inside.
I'm not saying it again.
Come on, get up,
you piece of shit.
- Come on over here,
you little fucking..
[grunts]...
...    - Where is he?
- I don't know.
- Where is he, bitch?
- Where did you take him?
- I don't know. I swear.
- He's lying, Caleb.
- Fucking liar.
[beeping]...
...     Where is he?
Fuck him up, man.
[indistinct screaming]...
...    Motherfucker.
[screaming]...
...   [intense music]...
...   [siren wailing]...
...   - They found us.
- No.
Please.
No, don't.
No.
Stop. Don't.
Please. I'm pregnant.
- What?
No, no.
It's - - it's impossible. No.
- I'm sorry,
animals aren't enough.
- But we're sick.
- Maybe he isn't.
- I'm sorry.
It's too dangerous.
- It's too dangerous.
- No.
Please, stop it. No.
Martin, stop.
No. Stop.
No.
- Open the fucking door,
you sick fuck.
Open the door,
you motherfucker.
You fucking animals,
you killed my sister.
Open the fucking door,
you assholes.
Goddamn door.
Goddamn fucking assholes.
Open the fucking door.
- Ana. Ana, Stop.
Please.
Ana, stop. Ana.
- There he is.
Get him, Billy.
[monitor beeping]...
...     [sighs]...
...   - Is this yours?
What did you do with the body?
Where did you hide him?
- He wasn't dead.
- Bullshit.
- I swear I'm telling the truth, sir.
That's why I helped him out.
- So where is he now?
- I don't know, sir.
I swear.
He left last night.
- By himself?
- Lieutenant.
- I'm busy here.
- I know. I'm sorry, sir.
We found your son's friend.
- Okay.
- He was still alive
when they brought him here.
And they severed his jugular
and he bled out.
Connor put his time of death
about 8 to 10 hours ago.
- Did you close route 15?
- Yeah.
The team says they're getting upset.
They wanna talk to the chief.
- The chief is in Black River,
I'm in charge now.
- But, lieutenant,
even if we set up road blocks...
...  we still have no idea
who we're looking for.
- Yeah, we do.
Caucasian male, 6 feet tall...
...30-35, brown hair with a beard.
Start looking for him.
- Yes, sir.
I need your assistance.
[cell phone vibrating]...
...     - De Luca.
Okay. Yeah, okay, I'm on my way.
- He had a heart attack.
Probably caused by thrombosis
due to the burns.
He's stable for now but, uh..
...his blood levels
dropped dangerously low.
He could have another thrombosis..
...or an embolism.
And this time,
it could be fatal.
- My son is gonna live
longer than you and me.
Understood?
- Yeah.
[instrumental music]...
...     [sobbing]...
...   [music continues]...
...     [honking]...
... - We have a conversation
to finish. Get in.
- I can't.
What about my bike and my things?
- Nobody's gonna steal your shit.
Get in the car.
Come on.
[door creaking]...
... - I swear I've told you everything I know.
I'm not protecting him.
Please, sir.
What do you want?
- I wanna talk.
- Here?
- Get out of the car.
[rattling]...
...  [instrumental music]...
...Okay, cuff yourself to that.
- What for?
- Do it.
- I swear I won't run away, sir.
I'll tell you whatever you want.
- Come on.
I told you not to lie to me.
- I didn't lie. I swear
I was telling the truth.
- You told me
you didn't know who he was.
I don't. He came by my house.
But I've never seen him before.
- Okay.
I'll give you one more shot.
Do you wanna know
how my son feels?
- Please, sir.
- Where is he?
- I don't know.
I swear.
- You motherfucker.
- No. No. No.
[Peter screaming]...
...   [intense music]...
...     [groans]...
...     [gunshots]...
...- You thought you were gonna
get away, motherfucker?
[grunts]...
...     [groans]...
...    [door opens]...
...- What happened? Oh, my God.
What are you doing? I have
to take him to the hospital.
And look at him.
Let me go..
In 5 minutes he will be dead,
and I won't be able to help him.
So keep quiet and don't move.
[indistinct]...
...  - What are you doing?
You..
Oh, my God.
I need an ambulance.
My son has been in an accident.
209, 05 Anderson Drive.
He's dying, please send
someone right away.
What are you doing?
Are you insane?
Leave my son alone.
I'm begging you.
Please, hurry up. Please.
Please, please.
Sweetie, hold on.
The ambulance is on it's --...
...The ambulance is on it's way.
My love, sweetie, please.
- What happened to Ana?
Is he your son?
- Get out of my house.
Get out.
Hold on.
- I'm really sorry, Monica.
But I still don't understand.
How could this happen to him?
- He probably wasn't looking.
And when he lit the match,
the can exploded.
- Monica, Peter has burns
of different degrees...
...on different parts of his body.
Are you absolutely certain
this was an accident?
He's always been so reckless.
Alright. I'll come back later
to see how he's doing.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
[sobbing]...
...  - Is Peter Ana's son?
- What are you doing here again?
- She was my wife.
I need to know what happened.
If she was your wife,
then you should know..
...she was running away from you.
- What happened?
[instrumental music]...
...   - Good morning, Ana.
Would you like me to take him?
- Yes, please.
Goodbye, my love. Don't worry,
she'll take care of you.
- Should I close the curtains?
- No, I'd like to watch the sunrise.
- Okay.
[music continues]...
...    - Nobody knew
what happened to her.
- Ana wasn't normal,
she -- she was sick.
- I know, but Peter..
...was born healthy.
He's not a danger to anyone.
- How do you know that?
- Because he's my son.
The only danger here, is you.
[breathing heavily]...
...    - Goddamn kid.
[monitor beeping]...
...  [instrumental music]...
...     [honking]...
...   [tires screeching]...
...   [siren wailing]...
...     [sighs]...
...   - I don't know how
you made it out alive...
...   or where the fuck you came from.
But your life is gonna end
in this fucking cell.
What you did to Caleb
is nothing compared...
...   to what I'm gonna do to your sorry ass.
You hear me,
you piece of shit?
- Send my regards to your son.
- Motherfucker.
I'll kill you right now.
[instrumental music]...
...  - Then what are you waiting for?
- Everything okay?
- Yeah.
Everything's fine.
Friendly little chat,
that's all.
Quit breathing down my neck, Harris.
[birds chirping]...
...      - Mom.
Mom. Mom?
[monitor beeping]...
Sweetie, how are you feeling?
- Better.
- Morning, Monica.
- Hi, Sonia.
- Hi.
Looks like we're feeling
better today, Peter.
We're gonna change the bandages...
...on your arms, okay?
Can you lift your arm up a little for me?
That's good.
[instrumental music]...
...Something's not right here.
It's been less than 12 hours.
- No. No. Don't touch it,
it can get infected.
- It's okay, ma.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
Doesn't hurt at all.
- Wait, let me help you.
[instrumental music]...
...   [music continues]...
...    - Oh, my God.
[instrumental music]...
...    Are you ready?
- No, not really.
- Just bring
whatever you need right now...
...we can pick up the rest later.
- We can't come back, ma.
We'll have to see about that.
Hurry up, we can still make
the 11 o'clock bus, okay?
- Okay.
[monitor beeping]...
...   [dramatic music]...
...  - May I help you, sir?
Yes, what happened to the boy
who was in this bed?
Did he die?
- No, he was discharged.
- You, sure?
- Yes.
He left this morning.
It was a miracle.
[dramatic music]...
...     - Come on.
What's happening?
[knocking]...
...  - Sorry. Thank you.
[siren wailing]...
...     - Fuck.
- Fuck.
Don't stop. Please.
He's trying to kill us.
Please don't stop the bus.
No.
[dramatic music]...
...   - Hey. I'm looking for two passengers.
... How did you heal so fast?
What did they do to you?
I just wanna help my son.
Please. Just tell me.
Please, or he's going to die.
Please tell me.
What the fuck did you do?
[engine revving]...
...  - No. Leave him alone.
- You stay here.
[thud]...
...      - No.
Stop.
- Tell me.
- Stop.
- Tell me what you did?
Or I'll kill him right here.
- No. Don't tell him anything.
- You, shut the fuck up.
- You'll kill us anyway.
- If you talk..
...I'll let you go.
- No, ma. No.
- Swear you'll let us go.
- You have my word.
- We should take
the sample at the hospital.
- No, we can't let him out,
we gotta do it here.
- Lieutenant,
you can't take a blood sample...
...  without a court order.
You know that.
- I told you to get off my back, Harris.
I'm sorry sir,
but I'm may have to call...
...the chief on this one.
- You go over my head on this
and you have no idea...
...what's in the store for you.
Understood?
Alright, boys, go ahead.
I got this.
Come on.
[thud]...
...     - Ah. No.
No. No. Ow.
- Go ahead.
[groaning]...
...  - Please, don't do.
Please, don't do this.
Please, don't -- Please, don't.
You have no idea of what you're doing.
This is extremely contagious.
Please, don't do this.
[instrumental music]...
...     - Go on.
- No. No.
No, don't touch my blood.
[grunting]...
...      No.
[dramatic music]...
...The blood needs to be blessed.
No. No.
[groaning]...
...      No.
[speaking in foreign language]...
...[Speaking in foreign language]...
...  - Shut him the hell up.
[instrumental music]...
...   [gasps heavily]...
...  - Hang in there, Caleb.
Hold on,
everything's gonna be alright.
[groans]...
...    Keep going.
[monitor beeping]...
... - I don't know, man,
he's been acting...
...really weird lately.
I understand his kid's hurt and all...
... but he doesn't have to be
a jerk to everyone.
[instrumental music]...
...   [metal clanking]...
...   [monitor beeping]...
...     [coughs]...
...      - No.
Wait.
Easy.
Take it easy.
[coughing continues]...
...  Take a deep breath.
And lie down.
[gasping]...
... I'm calling your father.
He should be here.
[thud]...
...   [dramatic music]...
...   [cell phone rings]...
...  - What's happening?
[cell phone rings]...
...  [instrumental music]...
...   - What the fuck.
- I feel better.
[instrumental music]...
...    [phone rings]...
...   - Grey mountain,
second precinct.
Calm -- calm down, sir.
Where are you?
118..
Okay, we'll send somebody
down there right..
Are you sure it was him?
Ben, get the chief
down here immediately.
Tell him it's urgent.
- Okay. Come with me.
- Okay.
- Can you describe him for me?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh my God. Okay.
[siren wailing]...
...  - Wash up, and get rid of those clothes.
- What happened?
Where is she?
Let me go.
Mom.
[intense music]...
... - Whoa, whoa, whoa. Caleb?
Where you think you're going?
- To find the motherfucker
that did this to me.
- Okay.
Calm down.
We have to go before anyone
comes looking for you.
- I don't care.
- Listen, Caleb..
[siren wailing]...
...   [dramatic music]...
...- Close all the access roads too, okay?
Nobody can get through.
Yeah, I -- I just talked to Black River.
They said they're gonna --
- Where's the stranger?
- Uh, let me call you right back.
Um, he can't have
any visitors right now.
Listen, I understand
what you're going through..
...but it's probably best
if you just go home, okay?
- You have to let him go,
please.
- Sorry, I can't do that.
- Please. He's the only one
who can help my mom.
You have to let him go. Now.
- Sorry about your mom, kid.
There's nothing you can do
to help her now.
- He can. Let him go please.
- Hey. Get back here.
Take it easy, man.
Calm down.
I promise you we're doing everything..
Alright, man. Come on,
come on, come on --.
Let him go. Right now.
- Calm down, please.
Calm down, calm down.
Think about what you're doing,
this is stupid.
- Let him go.
- Come on, man.
- Go.
[dramatic music]...
...     Open it.
- Dumb move, kid.
You just got yourself into
a whole lot of trouble..
[grunting]...
...     [gunshot]...
...     - Open up.
- You have to save my mother.
Please, you have to save her.
- Is she still alive?
Sorry kid,
I can't heal the..
Where is the infected one?
I need to find him.
Where is he?
- De Luca, open the door right now.
That's an order.
- Just a minute, sir.
I'll be right out.
Go around back.
I'll distract them out front.
- Okay, De Luca,
you stop playing around...
...  and open this damn door right now.
- Get out of here.
Go out the back.
- Lieutenant, this is your final warning.
- Please, go, now.
Get the fuck out of here.
What the fuck are you doing?
You're crazy?
They're coming in.
[knocking]...
...      - Yes?
- Get out.
- Okay. Okay.
[instrumental music]...
...   [engine revving]...
...   - Stay in the car.
[dramatic music]...
...   [music continues]...
... - There's a cruiser
approaching at high speed...
...on Baywood.
I can't see the plates, but I
think they're the suspects.
- Copy that.
Just make them stop.
Black River's sending backup.
They should be there any minute.
- Copy.
Get out of the vehicle, please.
[dramatic music]...
...Get out of the vehicle, now.
[music continues]...
...    Please, sir.
Get out of the vehicle.
[music continues]...
...     [gunshots]...
...     [gagging]...
...  - We gotta gotta to.
They're trying to leave..
I'll call an ambulance.
[bones cracking]...
...  Why didn't you save him?
- He was infected.
[instrumental music]...
...    - Head south.
I'll buy you some time.
- I'm not going anywhere.
- Please.
Do it for me.
If not me, then for your mother.
I know, all this has been my fault..
...but, please, try not to hurt anyone else.
Can you promise me that?
[engine revving]...
...      - Ana..
...she was like you.
- Yeah.
But she was stronger.
She gave her life for her son.
[dramatic music]...
...- How many more are out there?
- I was the last one..
...until yesterday.
Why did you want to find her?
Would you have killed your son too?
[dramatic music]...
... Why did you have that --...
...   [glass shattering]...
...     [groans]...
...    [gun cocks]...
...     [gunfire]...
...      - Die.
[screaming]...
...     [groaning]...
...  - Look me in the eye.
[gun cocks]...
...     [gunfire]...
...   [heavy breathing]...
... - No. No, don't touch me.
Your hand are cut,
you'll get infected.
Get out of here.
- It doesn't matter.
I'm not leaving you here.
[sighs]...
...   - If you touch me,
I'll have to kill you.
Get away from me.
- What?
You're gonna let Caleb get away?
Just like that?
- Go.
- No.
I told you to leave me alone,
you deaf peace of shit.
Get the hell away from me.
[instrumental music].
I swear, I'll rip your throat..
...just like your fucking mother.
Go.
[music continues]...
...     [groaning]...
...   [music continues]...
...  What are you doing?
What are you doing?
- Covering my wounds.
- I told you to get the fuck out of here.
- Shut up.
We need to stop Caleb.
- Go away.
Get out.
- Shut up and push.
[groaning]...
...     [groaning]...
...     [panting]...
...  [instrumental music]...
...     [grunts]
- Come on.
[grunts]...
...   - I'm sorry, kid.
[instrumental music]...
...      - Fuck.
[grunting]...
...   [music continues]...
...   - We're expanding our search radius,
we're waiting for backup
from the surrounding areas.
[indistinct radio chatter]...
...   [music continues]...
...     [grunting]...
...     [groaning]...
...  [instrumental music]...
...   [music continues]...
...  - Suspect's patrol car spotted..
- 7 officers are down.
We're authorized to shoot to kill.
[groaning]...
...     [grunting]...
...   - Are you alone?
Don't worry.
I -- I just want to rest.
[panting]...
...   - Hey. Stop. Stop.
- Are you okay?
Who did this to you?
- Untie me.
Untie me, please.
Please.
- Jesus.
[barking]...
...   Okay, wait here.
I -- I'm gonna call an ambulance.
Oh, my God.
Come with me.
I'll take you to a doctor.
[heavy breathing]...
...   - Please don't.
- Are you okay?
[barking]...
... [indistinct radio chatter]...
...   [dramatic music]...
...   [music continues]...
...   [Martin panting]...
...     - Fuck.
[groaning]...
...   [dramatic music]...
...     [grunts]...
...     [panting]...
...   [music continues]...
...      No.
No.
[groans]...
...    [screaming]...
...     [groaning]...
...  - You piece of shit.
[groaning]...
...  Now you're gonna burn.
[dramatic music]...
...      No.
[screaming]...
...   [music continues]...
...    [screaming]...
...   [birds chirping]...
...    [wind howling]...
...   [metal clanking]...
...   [Martin groans]...
...    - Thank you.
[coughing]...
...     [panting]...
...   - What the fuck?
What are you doing?
[dramatic music]...
...- So now you know what we are.
We're humanity's death sentence.
- There has to be a cure.
- Yeah.
There you have it.
[dramatic music]...
...     [sighs]...
... I hope you've inherited
your mother's strength.
Otherwise hell will be waiting
for you out there.
[music continues]...
...    - Thank you.
[grunts]...
...   [music continues]...
Please leave the curtain open
before you leave.
[music continues]...
...     [groans]...
...   [music continues]...
...  [instrumental music]...
...   [engine revving]...
...   [music continues]...
...  [instrumental music]
[music continues].