We are standing in front of this building
awaiting talks between a Westerner
with capital from abroad
coming to do business with the Thai investor,
Chot Petchpantakarn.
There's nothing much going on at the moment.
- We are still waiting for him to arrive.
- This way, please.
Well, this is typical of a wealthy man like this.
He likes to come late.
Likes to se people wait. Those who can,
will wait for him, those who can't, will go home.
Copy that.
Now, we are in the grand ballroom
of a high-class hotel in the heart of the city.
It's the place where a contract will be signed
between the two powerful men,
completing a business deal between Mr Chot
Petchpantakarn and David's Group Public.
All done.
Get down!
For God's sake, get down!
Go!
Sir, get down!
Yes, we have an unknown number
of armed assailants.
The situation is getting worse.
Now, there's bloodshed,
but it's not known whose blood it is.
This blood doesn't belong to anybody.
It's mine.
That must mean I was shot.
- Hey, take Mr Chot away first. Now!
- Please come, sir.
Come on.
Sir, I'll count to three,
then you've got to run. OK?
One... two... three!
Sir!
The gun!
It's here!
- I know. Can you please pass it to me?
- Why didn't you tell me before?
Get up!
Get down!
- Sir, get up.
- If I die, it'll be because of you, not them.
Hey! Now they are outside.
Run!
- Quick!
- They are here now!
- Gentle, please.
Gentle... gentle.
It's going to be OK, sir.
Go. Now!
My goodness.
He must be going to die, definitely!
He has no choice.
I don't think he'll survive.
I think he will.
I can't see how he'll survive.
I think he will, definitely.
But I don't think so.
Yes, I don't think he will now.
He'll probably survive.
So what exactly is your opinion? OK. It's
up to you now to say whether he dies or not.
Right now I'm outside the hospital...
Chot Petchpantakarn is being treated,
following an assassination attempt
in the middle of signing a contract
with an important American businessman.
At the moment a team of doctors
is trying very hard to save his life.
Since this is a live report, we'll be keeping
you up to date with developments.
- Wongkom, where's my husband?
- In ICU.
- How is he?
- Book the temple for the funeral.
Chot!
Chai!
You have departed
From the family
Tony.
Tell him it's my father who died, not his.
Yes, boss.
Hello. Testing: one, two.
We would like to thank relatives and honourable
guests who have come to this funeral.
It was unexpected that Chot Petchpantakarn
should die so suddenly.
We would like to express our condolences.
He entered the business world
when he was 20 years old.
He worked extremely hard to become the best
in the business for four consecutive years.
He was the leader in the two industries:
two years in manufacturing
and another two in the software business.
To this day, no one has surpassed him.
His weight before he died
was 145 pounds.
He was 58 years old. He is survived by
Madam Chamchoi Petchpantakarn and his son,
whose name is Chaichol.
one house, 5,000 cows
and 100,000 chickens and ducks.
That was how he created
Petchpantakarn's Farm.
He has boosted Thailand's economy
and brought prosperity.
Round one!
May I ask the abbot
to preside over the funeral?
And may I ask the honourable guest Somchai
Khemtit to hold the funeral sacred cloth?
And may I call upon the vice president
of the Petchpantakarn Chemical Company?
Has it shattered? For that
you have to pay 500 baht for one injection.
CHANNEL 7 NEWS
Madam.
I'm so sorry that I couldn't help him.
I believe that you did the best.
Don't blame yourself, please.
It wasn't your fault.
Right. It was my father
who couldn't escape the bullets!
Chaichol, if he could have died for your father,
he would have done that.
Stop talking nonsense.
Hey! You turn up like an ugly ghost.
What's up?
Phakphoom, the lawyer,
would like to talk to you.
Thanks.
Hello, Khun Phakphoom.
Right, yes. Yes. I can do it.
I'll bring him along.
Bye.
Uncle, what seems to be the problem?
Your father's will says that after the funeral
it should be read before the committee,
and we must make sure everyone is present.
We have to go now.
Please excuse me, my sister.
Where are you going?
You'd better stay put.
I don't want to die like my father.
- Tony, arrange for the team to protect me.
- Yes, sir.
Back off! Back off!
I'd like to know who will control
the empire after him.
Kham-Sai reporting, Kham-Wieng
on camera from Wieng Thai, Sa-bai dii.
"I, Chot Petchpantakarn,
declare in this, my last will and testament,
that all my assets and
companies will belong to
Chaichol Petchpantakarn, my son,
who will run all of them
with sole authority."
"Signed: Chot Petchpantakarn."
That'll mean Mr Chaichol
will run all the companies. Is that right?
Yes, legally and practically.
Oh, dear! With all due respect,
my dear committee members,
I think he is not yet mature
and experienced enough.
to run such large-scale companies.
- He should have someone as a buddy...
- Songpol.
- Yes?
- You may sell your share. I'll buy it.
Yes, I think Mr Chot wrote the will very well
and with great foresight. Very... very good.
If it's OK, I would like to leave now.
Is there anybody who isn't happy with the will?
And how about you?
- No, it's fine.
- And why are you still here?
- Yes... I am about to leave.
- Right. Thank you.
Chaichol, you have to go home now. I'll see you
at home. I have to have a discussion with them.
Shit! Even if you died,
you could create a problem.
- It's me.
- Yes, sir.
Chaichol is leaving the building.
Tell Artit to capture him alive.
Yes, sir.
- You, go get the car.
- Yes, sir.
What the hell is this?
Unbelievable!
Boss, we were told to get Chaichol alive,
but kill the rest.
Honestly, aren't you embarrassed?
I am embarrassed for you.
Everyone in the company is staring at you!
Can't you dress like others?
Can't you wear a suit
and a wig on your fucking head?
- Do you understand?
- You're mad, aren't you?
Yes.
Hey, why isn't the lift going down?
You...!
I didn't press the button, sir.
Fucking idiot! Press it! Press it!
Press it!
What an idiot!
- Why did you press " up"? I'm going down.
- Down!
- For fuck's sake!
- Stupid!
Are you frustrated?
- Am I frustrated?!
- Yes!
Reverse!
Please get down, sir!
Help me, please!
- Help me!
- How did he turn up?
Don't shoot! Get him alive!
Where the hell is he?
- Hello, my sugar daddy.
- Ah... Hello
- Are you OK?
- I'm OK.
- Are you sure? You seem drunk.
- A little bit.
- Are you going home?
- Yes.
I'll take care of the bill, OK?
Waitress.
One spice sour snapper soup,
fish cakes,
and stir-fried crabs with cumin, to take away.
And put on an extra 500 baht for me.
- Sweetheart....
- Yes, dear? You ordered more, right?
What a mess! What are you doing,
sleeping all over the room, like stray dogs?
Lilly, you sleep like a transvestite being raped.
Pok! Pok! You sleep like a corpse.
Pok! Pok! Why are your heads in that position?
You're sleeping like a 69.
Put your head on the other side. Now!
Oh, dear! How am I going to fit in?
I can see a wristwatch on a human wrist.
No excuses. You've got to tell your men
to follow the rubbish lorry wherever it goes.
Get him.
You don't need a plan.
Do it right now.
Tell Artit to go to Wongkom's home,
just in case the son is hiding there.
But if he isn't there...
kill Wongkom.
Boss.
Sorry. It was my fault.
What a fucking suit!
Can't you see? Can't you dress like us?
What's this fucking wig? What is it?
Next time you think of dressing like that,
don't bother!
You again!
- Little Chick?
- Yes, Dad?
- Do you love me?
- Of course.
Go inside.
Bye.
Little Chick. Little Chick?
He is dead.
Dome.
My son's dead.
Dad?
What, Pokey?
Do you love me?
Yes. But you gotta go first.
Pokey... Pokey?
Youngie.
My son's also dead.
- Youngie.
- No need.
We'll go in together,
on the count of three.
One... two... three. Go!
Shithead? Why didn't you come in with me?
- One...
- We go in together.
One... two... three...
Fucking shit.
No. Youngie! Youngie!
He's in the swimming pool.
Check!
Get down! Get down! Get...
Go!
Oh, dear!
Get out of the way, please.
Out of the way!
Get him!
There's a mad naked man
running with a pistol.
- Look at him.
- Follow him.
Get away! Go!
Bangrajan will fall soon
Why has no one gone to get the Royal Army?
Bangrajan will fall soon for good.
Why didn't you go get the Royal Army form me?
Bangrajan will fall soon.
Listen! Why didn't you answer me?
Anyone there?
OK. If you are not going to say anything,
I'll make sure you talk.
Coming next is "Popular Country Songs".
Let's listen to the first song.
Shit!
I'll call someone to help you!
Knob!
Put the gun down.
Put it down slowly.
Good. Fantastic!
Really fantastic.
Put your hands up.
Slowly, both hands.
I think one is enough, sir
OK. Let's search him.
With him in that state? There's no need.
Well, he might have a weapon
hidden in the bowl.
MENTAL HEALTH HOSPITAL
- Tie him up.
- I'm not crazy.
Get in.
I told you to get the Royal Army!
Why are you wasting time?
What? He managed to escape?
Why don't you track him down and kill him?
- Fucking idiot!
- Yes!
What  the hell is this?
Are you taking the mickey?
I am going to hit you.
Hit you? Kill you!
Nutter, you shouldn't have brought me
your problems.
To hell with my luck.
What a mess.
What are we going to do with him?
Well, let's wait till he recovers.
We can discuss what are we going to do.
Goodness me.
He's got a high temperature again.
Stop it you horny transvestite.
You get horny whenever you see a man.
I think we should pawn his wristwatch.
Then we'll have money
for his treatment and medicine.
Mother, I know what you are thinking.
Stop thinking now.
You stop! I'm your mother,
not the other way round.
If I knew you'd like this, I'd have stuffed
your mouth with ash when you were born.
- Auntie, is there ash in the hospital?
- Damn! I'll kick you. No manners at all.
Auntie, we should go to the police.
- Please don't.
- Hey, you've come around.
Oh, dear! Slowly, slowly.
Be gentle with him.
Why? Why don't you want us
to tell the police?
Why?
What have you done? What crime?
- Well... I stole something.
- I thought so.
- Thought-so is the name of a northern province.
- Shithead! Eat my foot!
You'll listen to me when you turn to ash.
No manners at all.
And what did you steal?
- This wristwatch.
- My goodness.
My mother lives in the country
and she is not well.
I had to do it.
Well, even if you didn't do the right thing,
you are a good son.
You show gratitude to your parents.
OK. You may stay here overnight.
Cool! Let him sleep here.
Poor thing. I will look after you.
Auntie, you don't have to worry about him.
You'll sleep here tonight,
and tomorrow morning you will go with me. OK?
Mother!
Quiet! Why are you so ungrateful?
Catch a lot of fish?
Couldn't you see I was fishing in the can?
No fish at all.
Are you crazy?
You must be seriously crazy.
Fucking crazy.
I feel so sorry for you.
Dear, oh, dear!
And where are you off to?
Well, going home, of course.
Shithead!
Why do you stop so often?
When are you going to get home?
Can't you see? It's a red light?
Are you fucking blind? It's red.
You are totally nuts. Your brain's gone.
Do you understand? You are fucking nuts.
Getting zapped will make you normal.
- You are nuts.
- It's green now.
Red.
Green.
Fucking shit.
You want the police to arrest me?
You want to taste of my fist. Wanker!
Wongkom.
Yes, Madam?
Wow, dickhead.
Your wife came to pick you up.
Fucking gorgeous!
Can I fuck her tonight?
So beautiful. Your wife, right?
- Everyone from Tony's team is dead?
- Yes.
And Chaichol has disappeared.
I think he was kidnapped.
Is that right? Let me deal with it.
- Sis, are you OK?
- What happened?
Why did you stop so suddenly?
I will give you one last chance!
Go and get the Royal Army!
Bangrajan has nearly fallen now!
You, Melon!
And you, Shitty Gold!
Look after him. Go!
Yes, yes. Go now.
The Burmese will come if we don't go.
How come you gave him 800 baht?
It's too expensive!
300 baht should have been enough.
My business will collapse.
You don't work at all. I can't give you 800 baht.
What do you want?
A watch? Again?
I'll give you 300,000 baht.
Take it or leave it.
Um... Can I have 30,000 baht?
Yes.
PAWN SHOP
WE ACCEPT GOLD FOR 6,200 BAHT
Hey! How did it go?
How much did you get?
- I got 30,000 baht.
- Excellent! I never expected that much.
You see, I never take advantage.
As the watch is yours, you give me half, OK?
Where have you been so early this morning?
Wow, who's your date?
Your new hubby, right?
You fucking cunt!
Keep that mouth for eating with.
He's a relative from my hometown.
- Get out, cunt!
- I ain't staying with you, you prick.
You beat up women, my fucking husband!
I don't want to stay with you anymore!
You want to fight with me? Get lost!
I'm not staying any longer, you prick!
You wife-beater, you fucking loser!
Cunt! No one's gonna put up with you!
I'm away just for three days and
you're unfaithful! Everyone here knows it!
As handsome as I am
I can get anybody I want. Go. Bitch!
What are you looking at?
You want to get hurt? Go!
Have you never seen people arguing?
Fuck off!
Do you want a fight?
Ten years far away from you,
I can still remember,
Coming back, a dog still remembers its owner.
Three days after leaving your wife,
she doesn't care.
Oh, dear, my wife is worse than a dog -
she's a whore.
- Shithead. You want a fight?
- Heartless.
- Get the fuck out of my sight.
- Yes, dear.
I'm so happy today.
Hey, can I have
one prawn tom-yam to take away,
one beans stir-fried with sweet basil,
one pork fried with garlic and black pepper,
one soup with rare meat,
and no bean sprouts.
I changed my mind. No soup.
Just the three dishes.
Gong and Chai, can you take all these
back home? I gotta go now. OK?
And where are you off to?
It's none of your fucking business!
I'm playing cards. Leave me alone!
Dad! Dad!
Hey! It's nearly ten o'clock.
Go to school now.
You're all late every day.
And when are you going to finish school?
Here's the money. Now go. Quick!
Don't get into a fight, OK?
I don't want to have to deal with it.
You like fucking,
but why doesn't your husband stay with you?
Shit your gob, bitch!
What about you? You like to suck dick?
Suck and no one criticises you.
No wonder your hubby comes home on time.
Because you like to suck.
Do you want to play cards?
Do you? Wanna play?
Bitch. You suck and you fuck.
You're so horny.
Put one card down, Waew.
- Why are you sitting still?
- I forgot.
You're so damn slow.
I've got you,
hook, line and sinker!
Bitch! I've got no money left.
No money left. You deal with it, OK?
You've sucked me dry.
- How will we divide the money?
- She's moody.
- I've told you, don't let her play.
- I'm fed up with her.
Get out of my way.
Go sit somewhere else.
No, not here. Down there on the floor.
I'm knackered. Quick!
Oh, dear.
- I'm hungry. So fucking hungry.
- Me too.
So hungry, my tummy is rumbling.
Why? Is no food provided
where you do your charity?
- There was, but I didn't eat,
- Auntie, Pok pretended to be an angel.
She gave all the food to the children.
Only three boxes, and there was my name on it.
You're so generous, regardless of status. Bitch!
Lee, why the hell are you complaining?
Don't you feel sorry for the poor children?
There was no food, let alone shelter.
When all of you come home, there is food.
That's right. Eat at my house.
Are you thinking of settling down here?
Don't you have any desire to move out?
I let him stay.
Do you have any problem with that?
Who would dare to challenge Mummy!
Good! I'd better go to work.
So annoying. Look after the house.
Be careful! When you run out of omen,
my mother will get you out of the house.
- Thank you.
- Goodness!
We have the land,
we have the labour, the tools.
What we lack is the capital to build.
That's precisely the problem.
Teacher, what would you like us to do?
To make ends meet is so damned hard,
Teacher.
Teacher! Do you want to
suck the blood out of us builders?
When we're sick,
we barely have enough money to buy a medicine.
How are we going to scrape any up for you?
You should apply for a 30-baht card
for all treatments
and donate the money you save on medicine
to the teacher. That's sorted.
Nit, are you crazy? And where are we going
to get money to pay for childcare
when we earn so little already?
Suthin, calm down. Don't worry about that.
We will have volunteers from the charity.
They will take it in turns to teach.
We don't have to pay them anything at all.
Ah, Thaksa.
Don't you want to express your opinion?
Normally, you are so chatty.
It's a good idea.
OK. If you think it's a good idea, if you want
to make a donation, feel free to do so.
It's not compulsory.
I know you don't have a lot of money to spare.
I'll try to get some funding
from the charity.
But, for the time being,
you all have to get the land sorted.
Whoever's free, come and help.
OK, all sorted. Let's agree on this.
Thank you all for coming to the meeting.
I would like to draw the meeting to a close.
Thank you. Thanks, everybody.
Teacher, how much do you need
in order to look after the children?
To make it work,
we need to have bathrooms, bedrooms,
and teaching equipment and materials.
I think we need at least 100,000 baht.
Talking about this worries me a great deal.
I think I'll only manage to build the roof.
Don't give up.
I could talk to my old boss.
He's very kind and likes helping people.
I'll call him to see how he can help
with this project.
If we can get his help,
the children will be grateful.
Chai.  Are you all right, son?
I'm OK, Mum. I'm fine.
Don't worry, please.
And... where are you?
Can you tell me?
I'll ask Wongkom to pick you up.
Absolutely not, Mum.
And when are you coming back home?
- I love you, Mum.
- I know.
- Chai?
- Madam, it's me. Wongkom.
You see, Wongkom...
Chaichol has just called. He...
Madam, listen to me carefully.
Your phone is being tapped.
You mustn't answer the phone.
I'll take care of Chaichol. I've got to go.
Chaichol used the 142 phone booth,
zone three.
- That's in the slum area.
- That's right.
But as for Wongkom,
we haven't tracked his signal yet.
He uses some kind of interference.
The electric box
gives you loads of money!
Don't tell anybody, OK?
I'll buy you some sweets.
- Can I have ice cream as well?
- Sure. I'll get you three pots.
- Let's go.
- Yes.
Today, Chaichol went to get 100,000 baht
from Pop's department store cash machine.
Get your men to wait for him there,
just in case he turns up again.
And double your team.
Make sure the area is searched thoroughly.
Understood?
Perfect!
- Hey. Why don't you start the car?
- I can't drive.
You can't drive?
Then why the fuck are you sitting there?
- And you can drive. Go and drive now!
- Yes, sir.
For fuck's sake.
Neat.
Let me help you.
You know how to use a computer, don't you?
Well... my old boss taught me a little.
That's why I can use it a bit.
I saw you talking to two Westerners.
You can chat in English as well, I suppose.
Well... my old boss is a Westerner.
That's why I can speak it a bit.
Now you're better, why don't you leave?
Well, where do you want me to go?
It's up to you.
Wherever you fancy. Just go.
- If it's up to me, I'll stay put.
- What?
Pok! Lilly!
There was a road accident. Quick!
Quick! Come and help me!
Here! Here! Here!
Press the wound on the leg!
Do you hear me?
Over here! He is conscious now!
On my first day at work,
I was like you.
Here's some water. Rinse it.
Pok! Pok! Someone is very critical here.
Come here, quick. He just feels sick,
but he's not going to die.
Come on!
Bitch!
I wasn't swearing at you.
I was calling to my friend.
- He's come round.
- Yes.
- Lilly! Come here on this side.
- Me again?
Did a dung truck drive past here?
Boss? Boss?
Hello. Yes... yes...
Wow! 100,000 baht!
This guy helped us get as much as
100,000 baht for our project.
Let's give him round of applause
for his work.
Hey, you!
I know where you got the money from.
What money?
- Don't play the innocent.
- Really?
Nutter told me you got the money
out of the cash machine.
Don't listen to him.
You can't believe anything what he says.
- You two go and get the stuff on this first.
- OK.
- Get back here as soon as you can. Quick! Go!
- Yes, sir.
Chai? Pok! You're the she-devil
of the community.
When jobs and fortunes are gone,
one is left with only goodness,
leaving treasures for the people.
Even your body will be burned on the pyre.
Please forgive everybody.
I'm not dead yet. I was just napping.
Shithead!
Is that so?
- Give me my money back.
- I know, I know.
Fuck off. Fucking annoying, you are.
You don't look like a thief at all.
I believe what Nutter said.
And how did you find 100,000 baht
to help the teacher that quickly?
- Pok, have you got a boyfriend yet?
- Hey, weren't you listening?
- What do you want to talk about, exactly?
- Well... let's talk about me first.
- Have you got a boyfriend?
- OK. Not yet.
What about you?
Got a girlfriend?
I'm about to get one.
She's from around here.
370 baht in total, please.
Thank you. Please come again.
Pok?
I'm really scared. Don't hurt me.
Please take whatever you want.
It's not mine. Take it all.
You! We're not here to rob you.
Open the door. Turn the signal off. Quick!
I've got two children.
My wife doesn't work. She just lives off me.
- Don't hurt me.
- Open the fucking door!
Yes, yes. And my mother's at the hospital.
My father has a kidney failure.
And my older brother is a soldier,
and he's tough.
If he finds out I'm in trouble,
he and his mates will come as a battalion.
It's my brother calling.
You... don't have to come now. It's too late.
You talk too much, shithead.
Hey, you! Open the door.
Turn the signal off! Now!
Go! Go wherever.
Go. Don't wriggle.
Police!
Don't wriggle!
- How many of them are there?
- I don't know. I came with you, sir.
Pass me the loudspeaker.
To the people who are inside, please...
- Is it on?
- You didn't order it, sir.
Do I have to order you around?
To the people who are inside, please
put your guns down and release the hostages.
You are surrounded by police.
Did they hear us?
- I don't know, sir.
- You don't know anything.
Go and get the NP.
Excuse me, sir. What does NP mean?
Negotiating policeman, you idiot!
- Go.
- You! Go get the negotiating policeman.
What?
- Sir, he took his family for a holiday in Phuket.
- Great, isn't it?
You take the phone to them.
We are now sending our man
to give you a phone.
Let's talk. Our man is unarmed.
OK?
- Can I speak to your leader?
- Are you sure you want?
I'm sure.
OK.
Boss.
Hey. Am I talking to an alien?
The voice is unintelligible.
Boss...
Boss, let me talk to him.
Let me.
Yes.
Hey!
I need a car.
What model?
Any fucking model, as long as
it can fit in seven or eight people.
I'll give you 30 minutes.
Wait, wait, wait. Is 40 minutes OK?
35 minutes. OK?
Let's meet halfway.
38 minutes. OK?
Given that it's a charity.
36 minutes. That's the best I can do.
I'm not benefiting from it.
I'm not asking for too much. OK?
That's it. Bye.
Go and get the MS.
- That means "Miss", right, sir?
- Come to see your fucking dad?
- It's the SWAT unit! Have you never heard of it?
- Yes, sir.
Quick, quick, quick, quick!
Dickhead.
You're running like you're shitting yourself.
Quick! Get in! Let me in!
This is not a training exercise, that is real.
Do your best and keep up to the plan. Understood?
Yes, sir.
Unknown men have robbed a department store
and are holding some staff hostage.
- Follow the procedure. Understood?
- Yes, sir!
Use your intelligence,
be cool and be patient,
and when we finish this task,
we can go back to our families safely.
- Understood?
- Yes, sir!
- Can't you say something else?
Excellent! Weapons at the ready.
Camouflage.
We are under attack.
Get out!
Quick! Quick!
The SWAT unit, where are they?
Where? Come out! Come out!
- Come out!
- Commander. Commander.
- Why are calling me?
- A tyre's blown, sir.
Don't wriggle.
Yes, boss.
It's been ten minutes.
- Dickhead. What the fuck are they doing?
- My boss flares up easily.
Hey. Are you sucking the blood from him?
Sir, it's the SWAT unit's vehicle.
A tyre's blown.
Why does the SWAT unit
have this problem now?
They're so fucking slow.
Shit! Dickhead!
- Whose dick do you mean?
- My dick.
Boss, 11 minutes now.
He loves talking.
- Dickhead.
- Stay still, will you?
Go get the TA.
- What is...?
- Twin assassins!
Twin assassins! You hear me?
You're such an idiot!
We don't want anybody to get killed,
so stop sending your men.
Hey. What unit is coming?
DK, sir.
DK? DK? What is DK?
- Don't know, sir.
- Don't know... What?
Don't think you can get away with that.
- Hey!
- What's going on?
Find a place to hide, country bumpkin.
You're gonna die!
- Thanks, buddy.
- No big deal, Humlae.
That's another film, dickhead.
Chai.
Pok!
Let go! Let go!
- Leave Pok alone!
- Go! Go! Go!
Quick, quick!
Pok! Pok!
- Get in the car. Now!
- Let go. Pok! Pok!
Wanker!
Do you know what have you just done?
What is it?
Why are you so nasty to him?
He has just saved your life.
- I'm going to help her.
- Boss, don't go anywhere right now.
It's dangerous.
I'm close to tracking down
who's behind it.
- Please stay put here, for your own safety.
- I agree with him.
Yes, I agree with him.
As for that young girl, I'll take care of her.
If she's alive, I'll bring her back.
I promise.
TRANSFER OF OWNERSHIP
Sign it.
Then we can end it quickly.
You won't get even a penny.
Is that so? Well, shall we see?
Let's see what I will get from you.
You.
Go and get them!
You! Go and get them!
Go!
Wait and see.
You idiot! Why did you fucking bring him?
He's one of us.
- That's right!
- Get another one. Another one.
Are you mad or drunk? Go!
Sign!
That's right.
Uncle!
Don't sign.
Whether you sign or not, we're gonna die.
Sign now!
Shall we see some blood first?
Sign! Now!
You. Deal with him.
Don't sign.
Uncle! Uncle!
Uncle!
Are you going to sign now?
No? Let's have another demonstration.
Go and get that person.
You love to see blood gushing out
before you sign, right?
Be gentle with me.
Mother!
- Son!
- Mother!
Don't you dare wriggle.
Do you want her to die like your father did?
Sign!
Sign. Sign.
Here.
Sign!
- Yes.
- Excellent.
This is it.
All done, boss.
We got the signature.
Easy, wasn't it?
- Choung!
- Shut up!
This... are you behind this?
Shut your gob!
It's OK. This document hasn't got a seal.
It's not valid.
What fucking seal
are you talking about, lawyer?
And where is it?
She hasn't got it. What the seal is, you have to
get Wongkom's thumb stamped on it.
You fucking shit!
Even though you're dead, you still make trouble.
Call him, now!
- Wongkom.
- Release her and her son. Now.
And the lawyer as well.
You can't use guns here.
Then what shall we do?
You stamp your thumbprint here.
Quickly! Don't make a big fuss,
- so we can finish this business.
- Sure.
But you'll have to break my arm first.
You want to be crippled? Sure.
Baldie, go!
- You fucking shit! Get out of my fucking sight!
- You go!
Go!
- Sunny.
- Yes, sir?
Cool. I'm going now.
Go!
Is it too painful?
Wake up!
Now you know who's the boss.
Mummy! Goodbye, Mum.
What's he playing at?
Oh... I'm fractured.
- Come on. What's the matter? Try this.
- No.
No? No? I'm kicking you. How about that?
You're a champion, right?
Fuck your Thai boxing.
How about a kick in the groin?
You said we couldn't use guns.
The sign's gone now.
Hey, go the other way, You're shooting
near my ear, for fuck's sake! Go!
- What?
- Don't you fucking "what" me! Go!
Dickhead! He's there!
Don't! Wongkom!
Sister-in-law, I'm so sorry. It was my fault.
Please forgive me.
You feel guilty now, do you?
How about this?
You...
You are shit-faced.
You are two-faced.
- Fuck-faced, madam!
- What?
- Fu...
- Enough, Mum. Let the police deal with him.
Let's go.
Wongkom, I have to apologise
for the way I've treated you.
That's OK. It's my duty anyway.
Why are you arresting me?
What have I done wrong?
We're near the end of the film
and I still haven't had a big part.
Only one scene where I say three words!
Where's the director?
- At the police station.
- You poking fun at me?
That's the fucking director, standing there!
You trapped me into this. You shit! Wanker!
You talk in the film and no one understands you.
I talk coherently, but I'm not allowed to.
You shit! Don't let me see you again!
Boss, that girl you wanted to save
is still alive.
Really?
Mum, I'd like to get married.
- You want to get married?
- Yes.
Wait till I have a chance to make a film!
I'll have you naked for the whole film. Shit!
How can you treat me like this?
Me, a comedy superstar!
In the whole film I said only three words!
When you're no longer popular,
don't come to me!
Now we know who was behind Chot's murder.
It was his younger brother.
At the moment, we are about to see the unexpected
wedding procession of his only son.
We will keep you updated as to
when and where it will end and who the bride is.
CHANNEL 5 NEWS
Nutty, eat.
Eat? Don't worry about me.
I ate earlier.
Pok, eat.
Don't call her.
With her symptoms, she won't eat.
When I was 17 or 18, I was like her.
She's fallen in love.
Looks like there's the problem.
When you have a problem, go to the loo.
What kind of fish is in the water?
My own fucking foot.
It can be either on land or under water.
Or even on your face.
Play at the wrong place, at the wrong time,
I'll stitch up your gob!
I'm in a bad mood now. Again.
Hey, that's Jam's house.
That's him at your house.
On channel 7.
On TV, Auntie.
He's outside our house.
He's in front of our house.
Pok, he's outside. That's him.
- Pok?
- What?
Will you marry me?
Put it on. Yes.
I've always had an eye
for the real thing.
What are you fucking staring at?
Good, good!
Pok! Bitch! You're fucking spoiling everything.
Is this how you betray your best mate?
You've got to kill me now.
Why did you poo on my heart?
I really want to die!
When love is new,
even spinach soup is sweet.
Excellent, excellent.
Hug each other. Hug now. You both look good.
Why don't you go to the bedroom?
It's empty.
This is great. I love it.
I'm so happy. It's empty. Go inside.
Now everything is back to normal.
Some people still wonder
who was behind the crime.
It was quite straightforward.
It was just a hitman who had a contract to kill.
The person who wanted him dead
was his younger brother.
It had been Mr Choung,
who was the younger brother of Mr Chot.
Mr Chot was the father of Chaichol.
Mr Chaichol is the nephew of Mr Choung.
You're starting to get confused now, right?
But I'm not confused at all,
because I'm reporting this news.
Now, Mr Chaichol has a passionate herb -
no, I mean surprising.
Lemongrass -  we use it for cooking.
That's right, isn't it?
We were surprised
because he unexpectedly got married.
It was a lightning ceremony -
done in a flash.
It's going to rain. Rain and then lightning.
It was almost impossible to report.
I am reporting on the wedding procession.
I will keep you updated
as to where and how.
We'll do focus news. We'll go to his house.
But we can't go inside the bedroom.
If I go in there,
I might see something obscene,
and we really can't broadcast it.
But we will follow them.
Is that enough?
- Enough, now?
- A little bit more.
I will keep reporting
because the director has told me to do so.
About the wedding,
I think it'll be probably enough.
- A little.
- A little?
He forced me to do it.
I've been waiting since this morning.
Enough?
He said it was up to me.
Kham-Sai reporting from Wieng Thai,
Sa-bai dii.
I might not be able to get down.
Shoot. Shoot now.
Get me down.
Let go of the rope.
When I count to three, run. OK?
One... Wait.
Lovely dance.
Great. Very good.
Good, good, good.
- Start!
- I'm afraid of heights.
- Find out who I am. Find out.
- Find out who I am.
Is that right, Little Chick?
Go! I'm away for a few days and you...
Go! You think I...
You've been unfaithful! How dare you?
You think I don't have...