Previously on Power...
- [Door opens]
- Ghost! We need to talk.
This club is the dream.
I don't know any old,
wrinkled drug dealers.
They're either dead or inside.
They're not as good as you.
Retail side's been locked up tight
since we sent those body parts around town.
You hire this motherfucker
to boost my product?
Fuck, no, I've never seen him before.
Anibal Santalises.
_
You want a ride home?
When was the last time you
asked a girl out on a real date?
Do you even know how?
My boss told me not to get distracted.
But somehow when it comes to you...
I got you.
♪ They say this is a big, rich town ♪
♪ I just come from the poorest part ♪
♪ Bright lights, city life ♪
♪ I gotta make it, this
is where it goes down ♪
♪ I just happen to come up hard ♪
♪ Legal or illegal,
baby, I gotta make it ♪
♪ I never took a
straight path nowhere ♪
♪ Life's full of twists and
turns, bumps and bruises ♪
♪ I live, I learn ♪
♪ I'm from that city full of
yellow cabs and skyscrapers ♪
♪ It's hard to get a start
in these parts without paper ♪
♪ Homey, I grew up in hell,
a block away from heaven ♪
♪ That corner every 15
minutes, they moving seven ♪
♪ Pure snow, bag it, then watch it go ♪
♪ Occupational options,
get some blow or some hoes ♪
♪ Shoot the ball or the strap,
learn to rap or to jack ♪
♪ Fuck it, man, in the meantime,
go head and pump a pack ♪
♪ This my regal, royal
flow, my James Bond bounce ♪
♪ That 007, that's 62 on my count ♪
♪ I'm an undercover liar,
I lie under the covers ♪
♪ Look a bitch in the eyes
and tell her, baby, I love ya ♪
♪ You're my inspiration,
you're my motivation ♪
♪ You're the reason that I'm
moving with no hesitation ♪
♪ They say this is a big, rich town ♪
♪ Yeah, I just come
from the poorest part ♪
♪ Bright lights, city life ♪
♪ I gotta make it, this
is where it goes down ♪
- ♪ Oh, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I just happen to come up hard ♪
♪ Legal or illegal,
baby, I gotta make it ♪
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com
[Goapele's Play]
♪
♪ Uh, uh ♪
♪ I wanna know ♪
♪ What you wanna do ♪
♪ What if I could say
there wasn't any rules ♪
♪ I wanna play ♪
♪ Play around ♪
♪ Tell me if you think
that you can get down ♪
[Laughs]
♪ 'Cause this is what I'm dying for ♪
[Phone vibrating]
♪ I mean, this is
what I'm dying to do ♪
_
[Sighs]
I don't give a fuck what Anibal said.
He's behind these hits.
Right now the retail business
is all we got running.
We both know that shit alone
is not paying the bills.
We need to light Anibal's ass up
and turn this fucking tap back on.
Anibal has always been a person
who likes the status quo.
I don't see him making a move like that.
He's too fucking lazy.
It's just as possible
somebody's setting him up.
You over-think everything, man.
We burnt the shit out of that kid,
and he told us that
fatboy gave him the job.
Case closed for me.
Kanan would've had this
motherfucker toe up already.
Yeah, and I ain't fucking Kanan.
We're having this sit-down
in a couple of days.
We kept 'em all dry for a minute now.
The motherfucker who ain't thirsty
is the one hitting us.
We'll know for sure who's behind this shit
when we're across a table
staring them all in the eye.
What if it ain't one of them?
I mean...
you ever think Lobos might be
the one behind all this shit?
Every damn day.
But I can't figure out why he'd do it,
why he wouldn't have had us capped already.
So until I got good answers
to those fucking questions,
I gotta assume Lobos ain't involved.
We'll compare notes after this meeting
- and see where we end up.
- All right.
We're gonna find out who's fucking with us.
And then we're gonna kill 'em.
Hmm.
[Door opens]
There's my baby girl! Hey, come here!
- Aww.
- [Laughs]
Yo, what's up, "T"?
- Go say hey to Uncle Tommy.
- Come here.
Where you been?
Out... with 'Keisha.
- 'Keisha.
- What?
Mm.
Leave her alone. You know that's my friend.
Mm-hmm, your friend that has everything
to say about everything.
Yas doing all right after
that thing the other night?
Yas has forgotten about it, of course.
I can't get it out of my head.
She was just fine, and then, boom. Yeah?
That's how things happen.
Your whole life can change in one breath.
I'm still trying to figure out
where she got the keychain
from in the first place.
You know, I'm gonna talk
to the housekeeper about it.
- It don't matter now, right?
- Right.
Count our blessings while we have 'em.
Hey! Cynthia's here to talk
about the Sutton Place Party.
- Cool, where is she?
- She's in your office.
Now don't give away the store
to get this party, all right?
Offer her a good deal, not a great one.
- Mm.
- Should I come with?
I got this.
I got us 8:00 reservations
at that Italian spot
- at 7th and the Park.
- [Laughs]
You haven't heard the word
"No" very often in your life,
have you?
I hear it all the time, I just ignore it.
You have to find another date.
Maybe there's some girls getting
off their shift at Cheetah's.
Hey, tell Kantos you feel
sick so we can break out.
I'm working.
And Thursday's one of our busiest nights.
So I don't care if you're Derek Jeter,
I'm not losing out on $1,000
worth of tips for anyone.
Here.
Here's 2,000.
Let's bounce.
I'm not gonna fuck you.
Good to know. Can we go now?
[Coughs]
I think I'm coming down with the flu.
That drug overdose the other night
is not the kind of
publicity you want, James.
It wasn't an overdose.
A girl got some bad coke.
- Could happen anywhere.
- But it happened here.
And it's unseemly of us
to partner with a venue
that has a reputation for drug use.
Now one incident's an anomaly,
another one, well...
You should know that my budget
for the Sutton Place Party
has been dramatically trimmed.
But you shouldn't focus on money.
If I have the event here...
Truth will be in every major publication
from the New York Times to China Daily.
That's game-changing publicity
for a new club like yours.
You need this party, trust me.
One party.
It's an anomaly.
Okay, you can have the venue.
All you have to cover is bar and staff.
But I want the rest of
your parties this year...
Tribeca Film, Fashion Week, Hot List.
I want them all.
Okay, unfortunately
those parties are already spoken for.
Fashion Week is at Parley.
Tribeca Film Festival is at Verbatim.
Simon Stern's clubs.
I'm offering you a
better deal than he will.
As you said, your budget's
been "Dramatically Trimmed."
_
Why don't you go talk to your employers
and get back to me?
That's the kind of person I am.
I don't think first, I just do what I want.
What about you? What
kind of person are you?
- What kind of person am I?
- Yeah.
I don't know, a regular person?
[Laughs] Do you have any hobbies?
I mean, like, what do you for fun?
I don't know. Video games?
[Laughs] What are you, 13?
- Hey, let's grab a drink.
- What about dinner?
Drink now, eat later.
[Opens door]
Remember, no one dances on the banquettes.
That blonde bitch last week
cost us 800 bucks in refinishing
because of her fucking Louboutins.
- Headed uptown.
- How'd it go with Cynthia?
Well, I told her all she'd have to do
is cover bar and staff if she'd give us
the rest of her parties this year.
- Boss.
- No, look.
I know we'll lose money.
But hey, if we get those
events, fools will be
cutting blank checks to get up in here.
Look, I get that you're
building for tomorrow,
but we gotta keep the lights on today.
See, short-term thinking
creates short-term results.
Come on.
My first day of sixth grade,
I find the biggest kid in P.S. 142
and bam!
I put him on his ass. Lights out.
Right hand to the motherfucking jaw.
So no one ever messed with you after that?
Are you kidding me?
I was the only white kid for 20 blocks.
I got my ass kicked every day.
But I never gave up.
I never stopped fighting.
Some people are asking for it.
[Laughs]
Wow, it looks... looks good on you.
It would look good on anyone.
Not like this.
We went 18 years,
now I feel like I can't
even make it two days.
Yeah, I know.
I needed to see you too.
This... why did you...
I just wanted, you know,
to give you something nice.
Make you feel special.
I feel special when you look at me.
You don't need to buy me anything.
[Laughs]
So...
what now?
Are we "Going out"? Is
that what we called it?
[Laughter]
My baby daughter almost
died two days ago, Angie.
You... you have a daughter?
I have three kids.
And I have a wife.
I almost lost my baby girl Yasmine.
Yasmine.
And it made me think about you...
and us.
I got no excuse. I should've told you.
I never stopped thinking about you...
all these years.
I can't just ask you...
I have a boyfriend.
Greg.
I guess we were just fooling ourselves.
I didn't tell you about Greg
for the same reason you didn't tell me.
I just thought that...
Yeah, me too.
- You should take this.
- No.
You can't give it back.
That's a gift.
When you walked out of my life,
you left ten days before your birthday.
Consider it a belated birthday present.
I should go home.
You should get back to your family.
Good night, Jamie.
Good night... Angie.
[Overlapping chatter]
My body is my business.
Well... business is dope.
[Clears throat]
[Rock music]
- [Grunts]
- [Gasps]
- [Glass clattering]
- Motherfucker!
- Yeah! Beat his ass!
- [Laughs]
You wanna fucking touch her?
Yeah, yeah, fucker!
Punk!
[Grunts]
- Don't come back!
- Jesus.
- Yeah, come on!
- Fucking get out of here!
Yo! He touched her ass, yo!
He got what he deserved.
Get back in your fucking bar.
I'll beat down every motherfucker in there!
[Door slams]
[Gasps] That was awesome.
What the fuck you talking about?
I snatched it from his neck.
This is where you live?
I don't actually spend a whole
lot of time here, I guess.
I kinda hang out all over.
- With other girls?
- Naw! It's not like that.
- I just...
- Shh.
I don't care.
I lied to you before.
Turns out I am gonna fuck you tonight.
I forgive you for lying.
If you lie to me, I
won't forgive you, okay?
So don't do it.
- Ah.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
- Promise?
Yeah.
[Chuckles]
Got any blow?
It's always better with.
Yeah. I got some.
[Snorts]
[Jamie N Commons' Worth Your While]
♪ Picked a fine old time
to think about leaving ♪
♪ When I'm down on my knees
and my heart keeps bleeding ♪
[Laughter]
♪ I'll make it worth your while ♪
[Both panting]
♪ Just bring it back to me, yeah ♪
- ♪ Just bring it on home ♪
- Oh, yeah!
♪ And turn your light on, baby ♪
[Snorts]
[Moans]
♪ Yeah, yeah yeah, yeah ♪
[Both grunting, panting]
[Groans, grunts]
[Sighs]
[Both breathing heavily]
[Groans]
[Sighs]
[Snorts]
How long until you can go again?
Girl, I don't know.
Things got better between us for a minute
- after the thing with the baby...
- Right.
but he's still keeping shit from me.
He's never done that before.
Well, if he didn't act the
fool every now and then,
then he wouldn't be a man.
Ooh, girl, look at these.
These are fly.
I bought them in black last week.
Of course you did.
Is there a reason why
you pressing up on me?
Well, it's my job to protect you.
Who told you I need protection? Ghost?
- No, I-I was just...
- You need to back up, Shawn.
Oh, well, you can protect me anytime, baby.
- [Laughs]
- Come along, 'Keisha.
Relax, girl.
Everybody know that boy
only got eyes for you,
jump in front of the
damn two train for you.
[Laughs]
You go out earlier this morning?
I missed you.
It's nice to be missed.
I was out shopping with 'Keisha,
Shawn was breathing down my neck.
I checked him, and he said
he was there to protect me.
Something I need to know about, Ghost?
Me and the kids need to
get out of town for a while?
Nah, nothing like that.
Kid is just being over-protective,
taking his job too seriously.
I'll tell him to ease up.
I'll talk to you after work.
You meeting up with Tommy?
Headed to the club.
I don't recall you getting
up at the crack of dawn
to head out to the Wash N' Folds,
emptying quarters out the dryer.
This is different.
Yeah, looks that way.
Steady trying to figure out why.
I told you why.
Seems like you could spend the
day at home with me and Yas.
You know, like you used to.
Everything I'm doing,
I'm doing for you, Tasha!
What the fuck is that supposed to mean?
Everything.
[Door opens, closes]
[Sighs]
So Lobos' New York distributor
is meeting with his network.
We just don't know where
or when it's happening.
My C.I. is trying to get me specifics,
but as of right now I don't have anything
beyond what I told you already.
Your C.I.'s info is bogus.
For the record, we haven't heard shit
about a big meeting with
Lobos' New York distributor,
and we've been shaking trees all over town.
Maybe you're shaking around trees.
Or maybe this lead is just bullshit.
It's not bullshit.
It's legit intel that's been cultivated
from a confidential informant.
It's how a real investigation is conducted.
Mm!
I don't need you to tell me
how an investigation is conducted.
I been on Lobos since you were sucking
- on your mommy's titty, Knox.
- [Laughs]
I was on your mama's titty last night.
Where are we on fatman?
Our opinion hasn't changed.
If in fact Lobos is looking to
switch up his current connect,
Anibal Santalises would be
the most likely candidate.
He's got the infrastructure,
the relationships,
and the disposition.
We've got guys on him 24/7.
I want you two on him.
If he's the player you say he is,
I want Agent Medina to handle
surveillance personally.
- Saxe, you work up the warrant.
- Understood.
You stay on this distributor meeting.
If it's happening, we need to be there.
Ruiz won't go near Harlem.
Rolla won't fuck with the Bronx,
Anibal ain't feeling either of them.
We need to find some neutral ground
for this sit-down.
Ghost! This shit's tomorrow!
We need to get everything in place.
Yeah, we'll do it at the
Chinese spot downtown.
Lok Sing? What about food?
Rolla's on some vegan shit now.
This ain't no goddamn catered affair!
I put fucking food on their
table every fucking day, Tommy.
Motherfuckers gotta eat.
If one of these guys is behind these hits,
we need to make sure they
don't have the drop on us.
I don't want anybody stashing fucking gats
before we all get there, all right?
We do it okeydoke 20
minutes before game time.
And get the room swept.
I don't want anybody
listening in on our shit.
We need to get to the bottom of this
so things will go back to normal.
We need our shit to work smoothly
so we can think about other things.
What other things?
Not this.
[Kids playing in distance]
_
[Door opens]
- What do you got?
- [Door closes]
I got what you want.
But it's gonna cost you. [Sniffs]
I was watching the FBI files...
and they said... [Sniffs]
informants get paid.
So... you want information
about this meeting...
[Scoffs] you pay.
Something tells me...
you're not hurting for cash.
Hmm.
You got me there, mami.
You ever think, if we'd
met a different way...
[Laughs] Nope.
Just tell me what I need to know.
Lok Sing Restaurant,
downtown, 2:00 tomorrow.
And the New York connect's gonna be there?
Mm-hmm.
We need you to wear a wire.
I told you I'm not invited.
I'm on the outside.
Then how'd you find out?
Little birdie told me.
Leave Isabel alone, Nomar.
Even if that's how you get
your precious information?
Be careful no one makes
you coming out of here.
Mm-hmm.
Pastrami, pickles, and Swiss. Hot.
Mm!
Thanks for picking up Tariq from practice.
I would've asked Shawn, but...
- he's with Ghost.
- Mm.
Speaking of Shawn,
he was hanging real close this morning.
Told me it was for my protection.
What's going on, Tommy?
You know, I got kids to think about.
[Chuckles]
We got it under control. Don't worry.
Ghost ain't telling me shit.
It's all, "The club this, the club that."
[Scoffs]
So sick and tired of
hearing about fucking Truth.
Me too!
Did Ghost tell you he took a grip of money
out of our personal account
and used it to open Truth?
That's none of my business.
He didn't even tell me about it.
I had to find out myself.
Look where you live,
Tasha. Look at your life.
From where I'm sitting,
it looks like things are
playing out pretty good for you.
So he dug in a little
deep on this club bullshit.
So what? Doesn't change
shit about your life.
He's changing, Tommy. Ghost is changing.
And that's not good for either of us.
You got any more pastrami up in here?
[Door closes]
[Door opens]
You should really take the
"B" to the "N" or the "R"
from the safe house.
You tailed me?
If you insist on seeing
that piece of shit alone,
I'm gonna watch your back.
You can't fucking spy on me, Greg.
You're right.
Instead I should tell Frankie
that you're subverting protocol
to play footsie with that dick.
Did he even give you anything?
[Chuckles]
I got the address.
You're good.
You're fucking stalking me.
Ah.
[Giggles]
I'm only stalking you...
because I like you so much.
[Both laugh]
You're a dumbass.
You're a pain in my dumb ass.
Mm.
Did you tell Frankie about what Nomar said?
- She's gonna call in the cavalry.
- I know.
- Better go right.
- I know that.
[Sighs]
What do you think about me
leaving some clothes over here?
At this point, I'm staying
over here a few nights a week.
It'll be easier for me to
just leave some shit here.
- You got any room in this drawer?
- [Gasps]
[Slams drawer]
What the hell was that?
Um...
Angela, what the hell was that?
Are you hiding something in that drawer?
- Of course not.
- Then what's the problem?
What's going on here?
You haven't wanted to hang out,
you've been distracted
when we have hung out,
and now you practically take my hand off
when I mentioned leaving
some clothes over here.
So what's up?
I mean, what are we doing here?
Is there someone else?
No.
There's no one else.
Then what is it?
I'm going home.
- [Sighs]
- Greg!
[Door opens, slams]
We have directional cameras
set up on the street,
but we couldn't get inside.
There's just too many people
going in and out of there
over the past 24 hours.
Did you guys hear that?
We couldn't get inside.
Mm-hmm.
Control, dispatch, for a 730 switching,
secondary transmission. Stand by.
According to Valdes,
this meeting's supposed
to start in an hour.
Yeah, and Anibal's still up in his house
eating pints of Cherry fucking Garcia.
How the hell are they gonna
have a meeting without him?
That's because there is no meeting.
Valdes is full of shit. [Laughs]
[Sighs]
Who'd you rather bang, Valdes or Frankie?
- Frankie don't take dick.
- I know!
But let's just say she does.
Or she would.
I'd go with Frankie.
I like a broad with balls. [Laughter]
Ah, I think I'd smash Valdes.
She's always got that
expression on her face
like she's so fucking full of herself.
I wanna see what her face looks like
when she's full of me.
You mean half full.
Fuck you.
They're all on their way.
Time for the okeydoke.
Do it now.
[Laughs]
You always land on your
feet, don't you, Kantos?
Who's the man in charge?
You're looking at him.
Nobody is stupid enough to
bankroll a spot for you, Kantos.
Come on. Where's the boss?
He's not here.
- What can I help you with?
- Jack shit.
You can help us with exactly jack shit.
We need to be laying eyes
on your boss right now,
or you're not gonna be
opening up your doors tonight
or any other night.
I got Victor, Darien, Queso, and Jayski
patting motherfuckers
down for steel at the door.
Now as far as food goes,
I'm just having them bring
those fucking Pu Pu
platter joints with a little
something-something for everybody.
I figure Anibal's gonna be
hungry as a motherfucker.
[Phone vibrating]
You remember when he ate 25 donuts?
Yeah?
Shutting us down? Tonight?
I'm on my way, Kantos.
Drop me off at the club.
Where the fuck you going?
Cops saying they're gonna shut down Truth
unless they speak to me face to face.
You're gonna have to run
this meeting solo, Bro.
Are you fucking with me?
We're getting hit, you shut shit down.
Now we got an entire network meeting
and you're gonna go deal with
some bullshit at the club?
They're shutting the club down, Tommy!
We wash more money up in there than we do
at every other front we got combined.
You want me to just fuck this off?
- Hell, yeah, I do.
- They want the fucking owner.
That's me. I gotta deal with it.
You can handle this on your own, Tommy.
I don't even believe this shit.
You got this.
Just don't tell them
you're turning shit back on.
Until we know who's hitting
us, we're not moving any weight.
- Go get Julio.
- No time.
I'll take the kid with me.
Hit me when you're done.
[Door closes]
You ready for your
balls to drop today, kid?
I want photos of anybody
and everybody on that block.
I don't give a shit if
it's little Sally Kimball
walking her cockapoo,
I want her photographed and I.D.'d,
and I want the dog's license number.
- Are all our cameras up?
- They're up.
6987, now confirmed to copy.
Out.
[Speaking Spanish]
_
[Gasps]
[Gags]
Everything's been permitted,
the place is up to
code, all our licenses...
business, beverage, noise... are current.
Yeah, you see, the problem is, Jimmy...
you don't mind if I
call you "Jimmy," do you?
See, the problem is we
know illegal narcotics
have been sold inside this establishment.
As you can imagine that's
a big problem for us.
Yeah, well, we're in the process
of tracking down the dealer right now.
And I'm gonna make sure
I turn him over to you
as soon as I find him,
okay? You have my word.
And that's great, Jimmy.
I mean, that's all a man really has, right?
His word.
But in this instance, I
don't think your word's
really gonna do the trick.
So what are you thinking,
Ed, two weeks or so?
I'm not following. What
do you mean by "Two Weeks"?
Jimmy, we gotta shut you down
for at least 14 business days.
This is totally unreasonable.
We have a business to run.
We gotta go through all your paperwork,
we gotta get health in here,
we gotta get fire in here.
We gotta make sure
everything's on the up and up.
Officer, I just told you.
Everything's up to code.
Well, sometimes it seems that way
when it really isn't that way.
This is bullshit!
Enough. Look.
What do you say you give my
partner and I some time, huh,
to work out the kinks?
- Pleasure.
- The pleasure's mine.
Oh, and hey...
keep us posted on that drug sting of yours.
- They're gonna be back.
- No shit.
- This is a restaurant?
- Yeah.
In our business, you try
not to use the front door.
Oh, hey, hey, hey. Sorry.
Here's how it's gonna play. I
sit down, you stand behind me.
Look straight ahead.
You don't look anyone in the eye.
And no matter what, you
don't say a fucking word.
Ever.
And by the way, while I'm thinking of it,
lay off Tasha, man.
You don't spook her
under any circumstances.
Get it? Let Ghost handle his wife.
All right, time to focus on this sit-down.
Stop distracting me, man.
What the fuck?
What is it?
It ain't anything good.
[Camera shutters clicking]
What about the entrance on
Elizabeth Street, anything?
Nothing.
Is there another way in?
Wait.
Isn't there an old tunnel system
underneath all these buildings
that the Tongs used back in the day?
Yeah.
But the entrance to the
only remaining tunnel
is on Doyers Street.
That's out on Chatham Square.
They wouldn't use that to come here.
I'm just thinking about what's
underneath this neighborhood.
Get me a blueprint for the restaurant.
Angela, the agents already
canvassed the building.
The entrances are covered.
Did they walk through all the floors?
See, there's no other entrance
to Lok Sing from the street.
But if they came from
the building behind it,
the basement could still have
a connecting door underground.
Street level, you'd never know
you could get to the restaurant that way.
[Laughs] We should have known.
They're too smart to walk
through the front door.
It's a guess.
- You're right.
- We looked.
- Are you absolutely sure?
- Mm-hmm.
Because it's your call. It's on you.
And if I'm right, and they're in there,
then we gotta go in right now.
We don't have shit on them.
We can't bust in there and arrest them
for just having lunch.
I just want to see his face, Greg.
[Sighs]
I want to see him and know who he is.
Once we I.D. that distributor,
we're this close to turning
him and getting Lobos.
[Camera shutters clicking]
We're going in.
I guess Anibal can't tell time.
So...
how's everybody doing?
We'd be better if we had product to sell.
- I'm losing corners.
- Me too.
Is that why you've been
stepping all over mine?
Those aren't my people.
Just 'cause they black don't make 'em mine.
- They flying your flag.
- Bullshit.
And if they say they are, they lying.
- Shut up.
- You're lying, Rolla.
Kiss my ass, Ruiz.
Shut the fuck up!
We may beef on the streets,
but in here, we're business partners.
Speaking of partners, where's yours?
We call this big, important meeting
and Ghost doesn't even bother to show up?
[Tires screeching]
So not only is he not getting us product...
but he doesn't respect
us enough to be here?
I got a connect in Mexico.
Says he can get us fish scale
for half of what we're paying now.
Out of where?
Nueva Leon.
Ghost has been overcharging us.
We can do better.
I'm turning shit back on.
I'm gonna start moving
weight to all of you again.
- Hey.
- [Gasps]
Let the agents clear
the room first, Angela.
You wanna go with Ruiz
and try another connect,
go right ahead.
We're happy with you and Ghost, Tommy.
We don't do business with the Spanish.
What do you mean, Spanish?
I look to you like I'm
from Spain, motherfucker?
- When you come back...
- FBI! Let me see your hands!
On your knees 'cause our shit is purer,
we're gonna charge you double, Ruiz.
- Don't move!
- [Overlapped shouting]
Spring rolls up in this spot
ain't got shit on Lok Sing.
In fact, I'd consider
sucking a dick right now
for some of them Lok Sing green beans.
- Oh, hell, no.
- [Laughs]
Why you switch up the spot for
the meeting at the last second?
Can never be too careful.
Always keep 'em guessing.
Can I get a fork, please?
We gotta know who's been hitting us.
Where the fuck is Anibal?
- [Sirens blip]
- How long?
It could be one or two hours,
three at the most.
And it was just the cut to the neck?
That's all she wrote. Looks professional.
Excuse me for a minute.
Who are you, and why the fuck
are you in my crime scene?
- DEA.
- Fuck off.
This is NYPD business.
We were surveilling Santalises
for involvement with Felipe Lobos.
You mean you were right
outside when this happened?
Wow.
Bang-up criminal
interdiction there, gentlemen.
I think I'll handle it from here.
- Detective...
- Beat it!
Let's go.
- [Elevator dings]
- Where you at?
This sit-down should've ended a while ago.
Hit me back.
What sit-down?
Just trying to find Tommy. Hey.
Tommy went to a sit-down alone?
No, he took Shawn with him.
Shawn?
Since when do Tommy and
Shawn do meetings without you?
Tommy needs to start stepping it up.
Why? You going somewhere?
No, I'm not going anywhere, Tasha.
I'm stuck here, right where you want me.
What was the sit-down about?
[Phone vibrating]
Senor Lobos. Que paso?
[Line trilling]
Shawn, it's Tasha.
I need you to pick up
some groceries for me.
Fantasma, how are you?
How's things?
Things are under control, Jefe.
Are they?
I find it interesting that
the death of one Primera
and the insubordination of another
meet your definition of... "Under Control."
Death?
_
I was hoping he was the problem,
and you eliminated him.
But now I see I was wrong.
_
NYPD should pay better.
The question is not why I know
that Anibal is dead,
the question is why you don't know
Anibal is dead,
and why your friend, Vibora Ruiz,
is so anxious to take your position
in my organization.
He reached out to you directly?
Of course.
I said no to his proposal
out of deference to you,
and the promise that you would handle
the problems in your network...
[Groans]
A promise that is yet unfulfilled.
[Crying]
You see, Ghost, I refuse
to tolerate disloyalty
in the men that work for me.
The moment I detect disloyalty,
I cut it out like a cancer.
If you don't, it will grow and
the whole organism will die.
_
- _
- [Crying]
- Have a good night, Ghost.
- [Line disconnects]
I specifically told you not to tell them
when we're turning shit back on.
Ruiz said he had another
connect with a better price.
The whole point of the meeting
was to figure out who's robbing us.
You said the motherfucker who ain't thirsty
is the guy who's hitting us.
Anibal didn't even show to the meeting.
Is that not thirsty enough for you?
- Anibal's dead.
- Get the fuck out of here.
- Lobos called and told me.
- How the fuck does he know?
- He got people in NYPD.
- Jesus Christ!
You do it?
- Do what?
- Anibal.
You seemed pretty fucking
sure it was him hitting us.
Are you taking shit
into your own hands, huh?
- Come here to me.
- I'm already here.
Get out of my face.
You fucking kidding me?
You think I killed Anibal?
You think I'd play you like that?
Hmm?
We had a conversation.
You told me sit tight, and I did.
I also told you not to tell them
we were gonna start moving shit.
I didn't fucking kill Anibal, Ghost.
Lobos said Ruiz is behind this shit.
Said he met with him about stepping it up.
He was gappin' the fuck
off as this meeting.
Ruiz has to go, Tommy.
Fuck, yeah. Do or die, baby.
- [Laughs]
- Do or die.
[Sighs]
Girl, it's like you said.
You know, if I wanna
know what Ghost is up to,
then who better to tell me than
the cat who's with him all day?
[Laughs]
I mean, I wouldn't say
he's wrapped around my little finger yet...
but he will be.
[Huli Shallone's Make It Twerk]
♪ Now hold up, let's turn up now ♪
♪ Hold up, let's turn up,
turn up, turn up, hold up ♪
♪ Let's turn up, turn up, turn up ♪
You should follow me on Instagram.
You should get your hand off my ass.
♪ I think they like my appearance ♪
♪ That's how I do ♪
♪ And when I walk out the building ♪
♪ I get the tap on my shoulder ♪
♪ Like the party is
over, I leave with you ♪
♪ They got me feeling like
a celebrity, heavenly ♪
♪ More than just what they telling me ♪
♪ 'Cause they feeling the lyrics ♪
♪ Ch-ch-check out the
melody, good, you got it ♪
♪ When I play this out on the block ♪
- ♪ The whole hood be rockin' ♪
- _
- How we feeling?
- You hear from Cynthia yet?
No. But don't worry, Boss.
- Line outside's a block long.
- Damn.
Hey.
That guy, the one with the bad blow?
He's at table seven.
Son of a bitch came back.
- Should I call NYPD?
- Nah.
But you told those cops we'd hit 'em up
- if he showed again.
- Yeah, I know what I told them.
Move him up to VIP, let him drink for free.
- I don't get it.
- Just do it.
♪ Yeah, it's a party ♪
♪ Got loud music and
women drinking Bacardi ♪
♪ Got the fellas in the VIP ♪
♪ Throwing up dollars,
getting bottle after bottle ♪
♪ To let 'em know that
we got it, hold up ♪
♪ Let's turn up now ♪
[Crying]
[Inhales deeply, exhales]
[Sniffles]
♪ Into the roads, it's open ♪
♪ Bare to your left,
my heart sits here ♪
♪ They say my dreaming is hopeless ♪
♪ This is the bed I lie in, yeah ♪
♪ I remember... ♪
Mrs. St. Patrick!
♪ Seeing your pain... ♪
Mrs. St. Patrick.
Tasha!
Mrs. St. Patrick?
I'm back from the store
with that stuff you wanted.
[Shower running]
Mrs. St. Patrick, hey.
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Can I come, come, yeah ♪
♪ Can I come, come ♪
♪ Come, come ♪
♪ Come, come, yeah ♪
♪ Can I come, come ♪
♪ Come, come ♪
♪ Come, come, yeah ♪
♪ Can I come, come, yeah ♪
[Techno music playing]
Whoa! All right, yeah!
Which one of you lovely ladies
wants to get on this dick?
[Overlapping chatter]
[Inaudible]
Mm, mm, mm.
We're about to cancel
Christmas on this motherfucker.
[Door opens]
I can't keep it.
I tried...
but I look at it and I think of you and us
and everything that didn't happen
and can't happen and won't happen.
I can't live my life like that, Jamie...
thinking about what could've been.
We can't be friends.
It'll never be enough.
I gotta go.
Don't.
I can't be friends with you either.
[Sighs]
[Pusha T's No Regrets]
♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Ah, yeah ♪
♪ I'm on the move,
can't, can't look back ♪
No way!
♪ Screaming, "No regrets,
no regrets at all" ♪
♪ Wasted time, I can't get that back ♪
♪ Can't get that back! ♪
♪ So every day I go hard ♪
♪ No regrets ♪
♪ Ahh ♪
♪ Say hi to the bad guy,
say ah to the Champagne ♪
♪ Got a call from my jail niggas ♪
♪ Said I'm doing my damn thing ♪
♪ Whoo! ♪
♪ They see I'm doing my damn thing ♪
♪ Magazines, videos, they
ain't missing a damn thing ♪
♪ Nowadays I sell hope ♪
♪ What, you rather I sell dope? ♪
♪ What I sell is a lifestyle ♪
♪ Naked bitches on sailboats ♪
♪ Foreign cars on a freight train ♪
♪ For every nigga they rail road ♪
♪ Rent-a-cars
we road run ♪
♪ Money longer than train smoke ♪
♪ I done been in that same boat ♪
♪ I ain't letting this chain go ♪
Hey. Hey!
Oh!
♪ Till they free 'em like Django ♪
- ♪ It's the same old ♪
- [Both panting]
♪ Just the same old ♪
♪ How the game go, where the pain go ♪
♪ Where the blame go ♪
♪ My mind wanders on a PJ, my
mama brought up in the PJs ♪
♪ In the club sippin' P&J ♪
♪ On the same arm as my piaget, whoo! ♪
♪ If I leave today,
throw the keys away ♪
♪ But I'ma live today,
I wanna see tomorrow ♪
♪ I wanna lead the way, ow! ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm on the move,
can't, can't look back ♪
Ugh!
[Grunts]
Don't ever go back to that club.
You hear me?
Get out the damn drug business, dummy.
Your shit could kill somebody.
[Grunts]
♪ No, no, no regrets ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ I'm on the move,
can't, can't look back ♪
♪ No way! ♪
♪ Screaming, "No regrets,
no regrets at all" ♪
♪ Wasted time, I can't get that back ♪
♪ Can't get that back! ♪
♪ So every day I go hard ♪
♪ I'm a real nigga, and
all my niggas real niggas ♪
♪ Came from making the real figures ♪
- ♪Too much money! ♪
- ♪ Nothing less ♪
♪ No regrets ♪
♪ No, no, no regrets ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ I'm on the move,
can't, can't look back ♪
♪ No way! ♪
♪ Screaming, "No regrets,
no regrets at all" ♪
♪ Wasted time, I can't get that back ♪
♪ Can't get that back! ♪
- [Moaning]
- ♪ So every day I go hard ♪
♪ I'm a real nigga, and
all my niggas real niggas ♪
♪ Came from making the real figures ♪
- ♪ Too much money! ♪
- ♪ Nothing less ♪
- ♪ No regrets ♪
- [Both moaning]
♪ No, no, no regrets ♪
♪ Ah ♪
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com