You recognize the name Simon Stern?
He's one of the biggest
nightlife investors in New York.
You got some fine-ass-looking girls
serving drinks in there, by the way.
There was this one red hair,
tall... what's her name?
Her name is don't touch the
merchandise, motherfucker.
Not everybody understands us, Jamie.
I'm not going anywhere, Tasha.
I'm stuck here, right where you want me.
We have us a meeting.
I sit across the table.
I look all those motherfuckers in the eye,
and I'll find out who's
hitting me once and for all.
Until then, no one gets product.
The Lobos' New York distributor
is meeting with his network.
So not only is he not getting us product,
but he doesn't respect
us enough to be here.
FBI! Let me see your hands!
Why you switch up the spot for the meeting
at the last second?
You can never be too careful.
Where the fuck is Anibal?
I never stopped thinking
about you all these years.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Hey, hey.
Oh, yeah?
It feels like we're 15 again
sneaking out of my parents' apartment.
It ain't like that.
My driver's parked in the back.
Of course, just like when we were 15.
I could've taken a cab.
What kind of guy do you think I am?
- Um, Angie, are we...
- What?
Okay, I guess.
Better than okay, I think.
Good night, Angie.
Good night, Jamie.
♪ Stand out a mile, stand out a mile ♪
♪ but, brother, you're never ♪
♪ fully dressed without a smile ♪
Watch that turn now, Raina, okay?
- Mm-hmm.
- ♪ You're never ♪
♪ fully dressed without a smile ♪
Hold that out a little.
- You sound really good.
- Thank you.
And you will, too, if you do what I said.
Good morning, sleepyhead.
Morning.
I didn't hear you come in last night.
Yeah, the count was off,
so we stayed to make sure it was right.
And then y'all woke me up
with those beautiful voices.
You keep singing like that,
I guarantee you'll get the lead.
The fifth graders never get it.
Yeah, but, baby girl, they never seen
a fifth grader like my Raina St. Patrick.
You come from good stock,
girl, you know hear me, huh?
Your daddy's looks and your mama's voice.
Mm-hmm. Whatever, negro.
- Gross.
- "Gross"?
- Give me some sugar.
- No, no.
Wait, wait. You trying to run...
Mm.
- Mwah. I love you.
- Love you too.
- Have a good day at school.
- Okay.
All right.
Keep practicing that song.
_
So we got fuckups all around, don't we?
The meeting information
from Nomar Arcielo was bogus.
And I take full responsibility
for that, Frankie.
But it's no worse than the potential key
to the whole investigation getting murdered
while you two idiots were sitting outside.
Saxe, what were you doing there anyway?
You were supposed to write the warrant,
not go out on a field trip.
And you distracted Agent
Medina from good surveillance.
All due respect, Frankie I
hardly think I'm to blame.
You're right.
There's enough blame to go around.
But the question is,
where do we go from here?
If you were right
and Anibal was the distributor
Lobos was unhappy with,
then Lobos had the biggest
motive to call a hit.
If we find Anibal's
killer, there's a chance
we could connect Lobos directly.
We're gonna need NYPD cooperation for that.
Good luck with that.
The detective on the case, Meredith Haines,
is a power-tripping bitch.
Takes one to know one, Saxe.
I'll talk to Detective Haines.
Let you know what I find out.
I'll drive you to the precinct.
I've got some friends over there.
If Detective Haines is
as prickly as they say,
then I'm better off going alone
so we can talk woman-to-woman.
You want to try calling Nomar?
He's not responding to our calls.
Yeah, okay. But as some
point, we need to talk
about the dresser situation
from the other night.
Later, okay?
We're gearing up for my high holy day.
That some kind of religious shit?
No.
We're celebrating the day I got made
born into the mighty
Soldado Nation 25 years ago.
Boys in my crew are getting
snake tattoos on their arms
so they can honor me, Vibora.
Dos decades in the game.
Always seems like guys like us
should be able to not
look over our shoulder.
That's why Anibal's
death came as a surprise
to me and my partner.
Can't say it did the same for me.
Because you made the order?
Because he's straight up fat, man.
You ever see that motherfucker eat?
I'm a businessman like you.
I don't wish death on any man,
except if it benefits my pockets.
Maybe you're trying to
take over the Tainos' turf.
I got enough trouble
maintaining my own territory.
I don't want to expand.
What about that shit you were talking
at the Chinese spot, about another connect?
I know a guy who knows a guy.
But it's not your product's quality.
_
You're here to accuse
me of something or not?
Because not too long ago,
you came to me for help,
and I strapped your crew up.
_
Reason I'm here, papa.
Yeah? _
You'd open up that damn pipeline again
like you did for Rolla.
_
But I haven't seen shit.
Give me a couple days to get
some things back in order.
You'll be flying high again.
_
Vibora.
Hmm.
For a minute there, you had me thinking
you weren't gonna kill him.
Motherfucker straight up lied to my face,
didn't he, Tommy?
Knowing damn well he met
with Lobos about stepping up.
Told you it was Ruiz all along.
Yeah, except when you said it was Anibal.
Except then. I don't care.
Now I just want to kill a motherfucker.
Yo, Shawn. You ready to
finally get your dick wet?
- Tommy. - No, it's cool, Uncle G.
I want to help.
Did I ask you anything,
Shawn, huh? He ain't ready.
Hey, the kid handled himself
at the meeting, Ghost.
Ain't it time we let him step
it up like his dad did with us?
Kid ain't ready.
All right, get out of here.
What's wrong with you
man, huh? What's wrong?
How's he gonna get ready?
Driving you around ain't prepping him
- for no real shit.
- Ruiz is too hard of a target.
Shawn's green. He'll get himself killed. How
the fuck we supposed to explain to Kanan,
who gets out in a year, that he's
coming home to no money and no son?
Fine. I'll do it fast and clean.
Ruiz won't know what hit him.
Nah, I don't want any of our hands
getting dirty on this, okay?
We need to outsource, so we have plausible
deniability in case something goes wrong.
I do it, ain't shit gonna go wrong.
The important thing is it stops, all right?
The streets don't need to know we did it,
so long as it gets done.
Fine. You want to blow loot. Fuck it.
I'll just call in the dreads.
Good.
What? -I just can't help but think none of this
shit would be doing down if Kanan were here.
If Kanan were here, we'd
still be working the corner.
Cheer up.
Let the Jamaicans do their thing, man, huh?
It'll all be over, it
can go back to business
- the way you want it.
Right?
Right.
I just want to talk about
Anibal Santalises's murder.
Give me what you have, and I'll give you
whatever federal resources
you need to clear this case.
And you'll get all the credit.
The victim's throat was slashed,
and he was gouged in his chest
in the shape of a trident.
Calling card of the Soldado Nation.
It's damn near impossible to confirm.
Soldados don't so much
as talk to outsiders.
And what if I can get you an insider?
I'm listening.
I'll just need your help finding him.
Why am I not surprised to see you here?
I could've gone to any of
128 nightclubs in Manhattan.
Yet you wound up right here at Truth.
My clients signed off on your nightclub
when they found out what I
was getting on the back end.
What exactly is that?
Have your people draw up a contract.
You're getting all four parties.
You should know that Simon Stern
fired his entire event-management team
when he found out that he was underbid.
You're not making any friends.
It's not personal, just business, Cynthia.
For now.
Congratulations, James St. Patrick.
Every boldface name in town is gonna walk
through those doors this season.
Well played.
Thank you, Cynthia Sheridan.
I look forward to working together.
I'd like to order some soup.
Right now the only thing
we have is fish tea.
I had my heart set on some mannish water.
Sorry. We out of that at the moment.
But why you don't look at the menu and see
if there's anything else you want to order?
I was hoping to get some
in the next two days.
Let me talk to me son,
and contact you when he make another batch.
♪ They stand out a mile ♪
What part is your daughter auditioning for?
She's also going out for Annie.
That must be Suzie's fault.
She played the female lead last year too,
even though she was only in fifth grade.
Must make the other girls
think they have a shot.
♪ But you're never fully dressed ♪
♪ without a smile ♪
Thank you, Suzie. Nicely done.
Raina...
I just would hate for your daughter
to get her hopes up.
Raina will be just fine.
♪ Hey, hobo man, hey, dapper Dan ♪
♪ you've both got your
style, but, brother ♪
♪ you're never fully dressed ♪
♪ without a smile ♪
♪ ro dee oh doe dee oh ♪
♪ your clothes may be... ♪
For you.
Actually, I'm...
I was told to have this waiting for you.
_
No.
It's not polite to make a lady drink alone.
I just want to remember
everything that happens tonight.
Aren't you presumptuous?
What line of work are you in, Carlos?
I'm a salesman.
Oh. So what do you sell?
I sell people...
a fantasy.
That feels a little too real to me.
Hey.
Come on, don't do that.
Stay here...
in the moment...
you and me.
Jamie?
Who's Jamie?
Have we been here before?
I didn't think you'd remember.
I saved all my money
to bring you to the city
and then could barely afford
the tokens to get back.
I was going crazy...
trying to decide the
right moment to kiss you.
How about now?
Why is our fridge the first place you start
every time you come over here?
It's hard out here for a pimp.
Mm-hmm. Uh-huh, don't start.
You know how Ghost gets about his junior's.
He was supposed to meet me here at 9:00.
He's late. It's his fucking fault.
You noticing Ghost has
been M.I.A. a lot lately?
- Can you get more of this shit?
- How much do you need, boy?
It's just...
I got a girl.
I was thinking maybe I'd
bring her by for dinner.
Something ain't right.
You must be coming down with something
if you claiming girls, let
alone want to bring 'em by here.
I like this chick, and I
want to bring her to dinner
to see you what you think.
Stop making such a federal case of it.
You want me to pick
your girl for you, Tommy?
What, I'ma let my mom do it?
Look, T, I respect your opinion.
If you like Holly, that means a lot.
All right.
Bring her by tomorrow.
I'll fry up some chicken or something.
Ooh! Like old times.
Like old times you eating up all my food,
- that's what it is.
- Mmm, mmm.
What's wrong, Angie?
Come on, talk to me.
We've been friends since the eighth grade.
If you can't tell me what's on your mind,
we got real problems.
I want to know what we're doing here.
- Are we just fucking?
- Is that what you think?
- I don't know what to think.
- Maybe don't think.
Don't say that. Men always say that.
Look, last night was last night.
But if this happens again,
then I'm making a choice...
I am making a choice...
right here, right now...
with you.
What is this?
The wing?
That's something I got a long time ago.
I wanted to fly away...
escape.
I'm sure you wouldn't understand.
No, I understand.
I missed a lot, being away.
Oh, you're better at that now.
Some things have changed.
What's all this?
You know that show Hoarders?
That's my mom.
It's her oldies and goodies collection.
I took it out her basement to spin.
On what, a record player?
Hell, yeah.
It's the best way to listen to music.
Here...
Check this out.
♪ Beware ♪
♪ beware ♪
My mother used to play this song to death.
I never heard this. Who is this?
Smokey Robinson. You know, the Miracles?
♪ Beware ♪
♪ seems like love should be... ♪
Stick with me.
I'll teach you a lot.
I'm not going anywhere.
♪ Such a heavy load ♪
♪ worldwide traveler ♪
♪ you ain't been nowhere ♪
I want you to come to
dinner and meet my family.
Your mother?
No.
My family.
♪ I know I may be just a stranger ♪
He's all yours.
I should've known you were
behind these bullshit charges.
_
Mami.
You didn't return my calls.
What's a girl to do?
It's that damn coverage plan I'm on.
Phone company's a bitch.
So are you for feeding me
fake intel about that meeting.
Nah, there was a meeting.
The place got switched at the last moment.
Of course it did.
We're done here.
They hashed that shit out.
Now Vibora's gonna hook up
with the distributor again,
restock our drug supply.
Fucking time.
So you're serious?
That meeting actually happened?
That's what I said, isn't it?
You got trust issues, bruja.
See someone about that.
We need to get you close to Ruiz
so you can identify this distributor.
I'm not high enough on the
depth chart to find out.
Bullshit, you were high enough
to set up that meeting with Lobos.
And when that went south, I did too...
in terms of juice.
Well, here's your chance to get it back.
According to our files,
Ruiz's high holy day is coming up.
I'm going to the party.
But I won't get anywhere
near the inner circle.
I got you here, didn't I?
Let me worry about getting you in there.
It's okay, baby.
It's all right.
It's okay.
What happened?
The school called.
Raina didn't get the part in the play.
I don't know why they didn't pick me.
I did my best.
Come here, baby girl.
It's totally unfair that's why.
Raina was the best singer on that stage,
and they gave it to the little white girl.
Tasha.
They should've picked her,
not Suzie Spencer.
I know how disappointing it is to work hard
for something and not get it.
She busted her ass on this,
and they took it from her.
Everything you want in life
you don't get the first time.
You got to keep going for it.
- You think?
- I know.
You keep practicing,
and next year you will be
the lead, I'm sure of it.
Okay, daddy.
That's my girl. Give me some sugar.
I know you're not gonna
run from me this time.
- Her school made a decision.
- And it was the wrong decision.
We need to do something about it.
And that happens sometimes in life.
We're supposed to prepare her for that.
We can't go around correcting
every goddamn wrong!
And we can't roll over
and chalk up everything
as a loss either.
I'm not letting Raina go
through the same shit I did.
Just because you didn't
make it into Destiny's Child
don't mean somebody's
out to get our daughter.
Fuck you, Ghost.
You know what my mother did to me,
telling me I would never make it.
I gave up because of her.
This ain't about your singing career.
It's about Raina, and I'm
not telling her to give up
- the opposite.
- Mm.
But she's not always
gonna win, and that's life.
You need to let this shit
go, okay? Leave it alone.
You hear me? Leave it alone.
Are we clear?
We're having dinner with
Tommy and his girl tonight.
Just make sure you're here.
Tommy got a girlfriend? Since when?
Let's go, Shawn.
So how'd it go at the meeting with Tommy?
It was good... being out in the field.
Yeah.
Listen, man, I know you
want to get in the action
- and be like your old man.
- No doubt.
I get it. Felt the same way.
Your pops brought me in the game,
schooled me on everything.
Make sure your word is your bond.
Never turn your back on your friends
and most importantly, know when to talk
and when not to.
God gave you two ears and
one mouth for a reason.
You volunteered to take a man's life today.
Is that what you want?
I'm ready to step up.
If you want the street
side of the business,
it'll happen, but not until I say so.
Understood?
Yes, sir.
Because before you get out there,
it'll be like your dad.
I got to be sure, 100% sure,
I can trust you with my
life, with everything.
I got your back, Uncle G...
100%.
You like this fabric?
Yeah, it's tight. You getting another one?
No. You are.
Acting the part is one thing, Shawn.
You got to look the part as well.
Vibora Ruiz has a thing
for poisonous snakes, huh?
Been caught smuggling illegal species
into the country a couple times.
You know anyone over at Ice?
Yeah, I got a customs guy. Why?
Nomar confirmed the meeting
with the distributor actually happened.
The guy we've been
looking for is still alive.
And I'm gonna get my C.I. to I.D. him.
That guy just screwed over
the whole goddamn department,
and you're talking about using him again?
Next to you, I got the biggest hard-on
for Lobos in this place.
And this is the best lead either of us has.
So let's pool our
resources and bust his ass.
All right.
If I do this for you,
maybe you can clear something up for me.
Sure.
How long have you been fucking Agent Knox?
Excuse me?
I'm an undercover agent
trained to read people.
Obviously there's something
going on between you two.
There's nothing going on.
Whatever.
Melissa, have you seen Holly?
She called in sick, again.
I guess she thinks 'cause
she's fucking the boss,
she doesn't have to follow the rules.
Wait. What?
Not the black one the white guy, Tommy.
You ask me, he's an asshole.
No argument from me there.
Boss wants us starting the
secret V.I.P. entrances tonight,
and I need her here.
I got to call her.
Chasing down these fucking employees.
I'm sorry, sir.
We're not open to the public yet.
It's okay.
I'm not the public.
Mr. Stern.
- Are you kidding me?
- What?
You haven't gotten a shower yet?
Babe, we got plenty of time.
They're gonna be here any minute.
You're the reason why they say black folks
are always late.
No, they say black folks are always late
'cause we always late.
Hell, no.
Not tonight.
Hello.
Good evening, Mrs. St. Patrick.
It's Joshua Kantos from Truth.
I left a message for the
boss on his cell phone,
but it's very important that I talk to him.
- Is he available?
- He's in the shower.
I'll have him return when he gets a minute.
This is very important.
It always is, Kantos.
- I'll be sure to let him know.
- Please, Mrs. St. Patrick.
It's very important that I get a hold
all right, babe, the doorman just buzzed.
Tommy and his date are on their way up.
By the way, you see my cell phone?
Oh, yeah. It's right here, babe.
- Oh, cool.
- You get the door, okay?
I got to go freshen up a bit.
All right.
- Hey, Tommy.
- What's up, G?
I think y'all know each other.
Holly... Holly from the club.
Nice to see you, Mr. St. Patrick.
Oh, you can call him James.
Hello.
- My lovely wife.
- Hi. I'm Tasha.
Hi. Tommy told me all about you.
I had no idea Mr. St. Patrick,
the big boss, was actually the brother
he's always talking about.
Yo, it's time to drink. I'll pour.
T, why don't you show Holly around.
I'll take your coat.
Holy shit.
This thing is bigger than my apartment.
Is this Louis Vuitton?
This thing costs, like, $1,000.
2,000.
My husband brought it back
from his last business trip.
That's what I want.
That is real love.
It's not about the gift.
It's about the fact that
he's thinking of you,
and he thinks you're worth the money.
I'm sure Tommy will get
you anything you ask for.
Tommy wouldn't know that bag
if I hit him in the face with it.
You guys got it made.
Yeah, I guess so.
Nice.
The good stuff. Cheers.
Cheers.
I am really impressed
with how you bounced back,
got your own club.
I do have one question for you.
How did you raise the money so fast?
I'm only a limited partner here, sir.
It's James St. Patrick's money.
But you're the reason this place
is turning out to be so successful.
I couldn't say that.
For a guy who's never been in the business,
James knows what he's doing.
We're full every night,
extremely tight door,
and once they're in, every kind of customer
gets specific treatment.
The drinks they ordered last
time, the booth they loved,
the waitress they wanted to fuck.
Well, you'd know about that, wouldn't you?
We've got a great system here, sir.
Seeing as it's just the two of us,
what is St. Patrick's deal?
Where's he from? What's his background?
I tried looking into him
myself and came up empty.
What did he do before this?
Remember JSP and Tommy-Toms?
Oh, please tell me Tommy-Toms
was not your stage name.
It was the '80s. Everybody had two names.
- Lisa Lisa, Marky
Mark. - And Tommy-Toms.
That shit sounded like
a bad Chinese restaurant.
You're not gonna sit there
and just blaze us up like that?
Yo, let's bust out a verse, B.
My husband used to always do
this rap about how we first met.
Go for it, Tommy.
I don't remember the words.
♪ I like it, she... she love it ♪
♪ no hesitation, I
had to push up on it ♪
♪ I like it, she... she love it ♪
♪ no hesitation, no hesitation ♪
♪ her breathtaking
beauty had me gasping ♪
♪ me and her together,
this was simple math ♪
♪ and at least for me, it was destiny ♪
♪ perfect recipe ♪
♪ was me and baby girl ♪
Oh, come on, man, you know I
hung my mic up a long time ago.
Boo.
Party pooper.
- That's my husband.
- Fine.
If you ain't gonna rap,
I need you to work a bit.
That club sure keeps them busy, huh?
Like you couldn't imagine.
Mind if I you use your bathroom?
Sure. It's right down the hall.
We're all set with the
Jamaicans for tomorrow.
Didn't I tell you not
to fuck the merchandise?
Let's get one thing straight from jump.
You don't tell me shit.
I'm not a fucking child.
You're acting like one
bringing breezies over to
my house for show-and-tell?
This ain't some skank-ass broad.
Holly's different. She's special.
Tonight she is. Tomorrow
morning she might be.
Give me a fucking break.
Come on, Tommy, you... you and I both know
you ain't gonna feel that
way in a month or a year.
Why you care who I'm boning anyway?
Because you're fucking someone
who works at my business,
which makes this about my business.
Last I checked, this
was a 50-50 partnership,
which makes Holly just as much
my employee as she is yours.
Look, man, that just means
I can't fuck her either.
But you better not have told
her about our other thing.
This ain't my first rodeo. Do
you think I'm fucking stupid?
The department splurged on this?
I may have submitted it as
a slightly different expense.
We get Lobos, no one will care.
You manipulated NYPD and Customs?
You don't give two shits
about protocol, do you?
Just like you fucking Knox
right under Frankie's nose.
Not this again.
_
Why do you care?
'Cause I don't want you to fuck up again.
If Knox's dick is the reason
you got distracted last week,
- I want to know.
- Were you sucking Saxe off?
Is that why you missed Anibal's doer?
Your head was under the dashboard,
Saxe's eyes were closed.
_
Where's your fucking key?
I heard voices.
I wanted to make sure the coast was clear.
I got you just the ticket to get you
in the high council of the Soldado Nation.
You must be offering
yourself or a ton of drugs,
'cause pussy and powder are the only things
- that'll get me next to Ruiz.
- Whoa.
Can you watch your mouth?
There's a lady present.
Who the fuck is this?
Nomar, this is Joe Gonzales,
a reptile specialist with the department.
Why you always bringing new people?
This is supposed to be
an "A" and "B" situation.
Reptile man needs to see his way out.
Okay, but not until I show you...
how to handle this.
Whoa.
- _
- Holly!
I got your coat! Come on!
We out of here.
_
Bye, Tasha.
Bye, James.
Uh, I'll see you at work tomorrow.
See you, T.
Thank you.
Yeah.
They're like the Cosby Show, you know?
She seems to have it all...
other than the fact that her
husband's cheating on her.
What did you just say?
I was dropping some receipts off
in the office the other night,
and I walked in on Mr. St. Patrick
nailing some latina.
You need to mind your own fucking business.
- What did I do?
- Just shut the fuck up!
Damn!
Tommy!
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
What are you apologizing for?
That made you angry.
And I don't like seeing you that way.
I like it when you feel good.
- Where you been?
- You're not gonna believe this.
But Medina finally got on board,
helping me with a Nomar thing.
Nomar should be in at
Ruiz's party tomorrow night.
Look, I'm not trying to be a dick,
but technically, Nomar is my C.I.
So, if you want to let Medina in,
you should have at
least consulted me first.
I know you're upset, but
can we talk some other time?
Because I'm running late
to meet some friends.
Yeah, sure. Some other time...
Like when you're ready
to be honest with me.
You know, whenever that is.
- Greg.
- Are you sleeping with Medina?
What?
It's not like it's not your M.O.
To fuck somebody at work.
- Fuck you, Greg.
- Not lately.
We're gonna talk about this tomorrow.
No. No, we're gonna talk about this now.
I got to go.
I'm not letting you walk out that door.
Can I at least tell my
friends I can't show up?
Rolla, what up?
I heard the fat man got marked.
I don't know who you
got on them corners, but
rock street Killahz are ready to step up
- and take one for the team?
- No question.
I done kept it 100 with you
and white boy from the jump.
Good. Tommy filled me in on the meeting.
But we still haven't found
out who's hitting us...
unless you got something you want to spill.
Negative.
Well, Tainos got Anibal's
number two in place already.
I don't see any reason for
him to lose his territory,
unless you doing some serious ear hustling
and want to help me kill
the motherfucker behind this shit.
- On it.
- All right. Later.
_
First of all, I'm not fucking Medina
- or anyone at the office.
- Anyone else, you mean.
People get into
relationships at work, Greg.
When you spend 20 hours a
day together in an office,
it happens.
- I'm not a whore.
- I never said that.
Funny, I heard it loud and clear.
Medina asked me today if I was fucking you.
- And what did you tell him?
- That nothing was going on.
He was asking because I fucked up
the raid the other day.
I don't want to fight with you, Greg.
I just want to catch
Lobos and call it a day.
I got to be able to talk
to our other colleagues
without you thinking
I'm sleeping with them.
I got to be able to meet our C.I.
without you breathing down my neck.
I got to have some space, Greg.
You know what? You can
blame this on our jobs
as much as you want, but
this is a "you" problem.
So, whatever it is,
whatever's going on with you,
Jesus, good luck.
Here's your space.
Morning, Shawn.
Hey.
Is that a new suit?
Yeah.
Let me see how it looks.
This has my husband written all over it.
Yeah, yeah, I'm going to visit
my dad again in a few days.
G wanted me to look nice.
You and Ghost are getting pretty close.
You probably see a lot
driving him around, huh, Shawn?
This suit fits you perfectly.
And I love how it feels.
I think he's keeping something from me,
and I want to know how
long it's been going on.
Uh, I wish I knew what
you were talking about.
Hmm, you're a terrible liar.
What's going on between
my husband and Tommy?
Well, um...
They've been having a lot
of disagreements lately.
Disagreements about what?
You can tell me.
It'll be another one of our little secrets.
I don't really know.
They've been beefing ever since
we got back from that meeting.
Tasha.
Is Shawn out there?
Yeah, he's reading the paper.
Morning, boss. You ready?
Morning. Yeah.
- Have a good day.
- You too.
Whatever you want.
Hey, let me call you back.
You got my messages?
What messages?
Simon Stern came into the club last night.
You better be shitting me.
You were M.I.A., so I bonded with Stern,
skinning and grinning my
way around a conversation
about us underbidding
him for those parties.
You trying to angle to
get a job with him, huh?
No, I left you a message
on your voice mail,
and I tried you at home.
Your wife said you were in the shower.
I did my job.
I didn't see one missed call
or a fucking voice mail, Kantos.
You were hooking V.I.P.s
up with bottle girls
at the last club you worked.
No one would hire you
with a fistful of 50s.
So don't stand there acting
like your ass don't stink,
or I'll send you back
to your P.O. to air out.
Next time you get in your fucking car
and you drive to my
fucking house, you hear me?
I heard Raina's audition. She sang well.
Obviously not well enough.
These roles are limited
and typically granted to sixth graders.
Except Suzie Spencer got the lead last year
as a fifth grader.
Mrs. St. Patrick, three
generations of Spencers
have matriculated through our school.
I'm sure you understand.
The decision's been made in the matter.
Oh, has it?
- Vibora.
- Mira quien es.
- How are you?
- Felicitaciones.
What's that?
A tribute for Vibora.
_
How did you get this in the country?
Happy high holy day, Vibora.
_
Venga. Dame la botella.
Thank you.
Toma ahi. Toma, toma.
_
I'll be right back, babe.
Uh, babe, you want to tell
me why you didn't tell me
Kantos called last night?
I must've forgot,
with all the running
around with the dinner.
I missed a very important
meeting with Simon Stern.
I'm sorry.
Hello?
May I ask who's calling?
Raina, pick up the phone!
- Mom, dad, I got the part.
- What?
That was the drama director.
They made a mistake.
I've been double-cast
with Suzie to play Annie.
What? Congratulations, honey.
Oh, I'm so proud of you.
Look at that.
I told you it would work
out in the end, baby girl.
I got to go call all my friends!
Call 'em.
Um, I'll be right back.
We're out of milk.
_
Yo, I ain't got a 420 text
from you in a minute, T.
Got some extra-good shit
to mark the occasion.
You must really need to hit this.
Yeah, but don't be rolling
up in front of my building.
Damn.
Ghost hates it when I smoke.
Fuck that. He don't need to know.
That girl Holly is way too fast for you.
Seriously?
I mean, you like her, you like her,
but that's just my two cents.
Noted.
- Relax. I'm a pro with this.
- Yeah, all right, I can't tell.
Nigga, I got kids.
Look, I know I'm starting to
sound like a broken record,
but your boy's head ain't in the game.
You know Ghost is always on some next shit.
Come on, we'll be out
your hood in a minute.
Ain't no one gonna see your ass.
I'm just saying, he depends
on us to keep him grounded.
But now he's talking to me sideways,
- disrespecting you and shit.
- Nah.
Don't lie to me to my face
you left early the other night
because you and Ghost
got into a fight, right?
You think Ghost is drinking again?
This ain't no bottle problem, T.
Maybe Ghost is just going through
some sort of midlife crisis.
It's too early for that.
I think it's just this club shit.
That's a symptom, not the disease.
Ghost is changing, Tommy.
I'm starting to think it
ain't a temporary thing.
It's starting to get crowded.
Stay by me and keep your head on a swivel.
- Salud.
Otra.
I'll be in the champagne room.
_
Shit.
Coño!
Vibora's hurt!
Something's wrong!
What the fuck happened?
You remember Tommy and I had a rap group?
JSP and DJ Tommy-Toms?
You remember the rap I made up for you?
♪ I like it, she... she love it ♪
♪ no hesitation, I
had to push up on it ♪
♪ uh, uh, I like it,
uh, uh, she love it ♪
♪ no hesitation, I
had to push up on it ♪
It's a good thing
you became a businessman.
Be quiet.
You know you like it.
It's work. I should probably get this.
I'll take it in the other room.
Tommy, what's up?
What do you need?
Nomar just called. Ruiz has been stabbed.
Are you serious?
Ruiz got stabbed, right in the chest.
Excellent.
Apparently Nomar's in with him,
and they're headed somewhere
to get medical attention.
It wasn't the Jamaicans we hired.
Someone went after him and missed.
He ain't dead.
Where are you?
I'm on my way in right now.
So, if someone else swung at him,
that means he's not the source
of our problem after all.
We got to meet up, sort all this out.
Work is blowing up. I got to go.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -