Previously on Power...
Vibora Ruiz has a thing
for poisonous snakes.
I got you just the ticket to get you
in the high council of the Soldado Nation.
Happy high holy day, Vibora.
What's going on between
my husband and Tommy?
You can tell me.
It'll be another one of our little secrets.
I want to know what we're doing here.
Are we just fucking?
I am making a choice with you.
This ain't some skank-ass broad.
Holly's different. She's special.
You better not have told her
about our other thing.
I told you it was Ruiz all along.
Yeah, except when you said it was Anibal.
Except then. I don't care.
Now I just want to kill a motherfucker.
Ruiz got stabbed.
It wasn't the Jamaicans we hired.
Someone went after him and missed.
He ain't dead.
Back then, Kanan kept us in line,
taught us the business, made us men.
Ghost and I owe your father big.
That's why you're here.
- Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Check.
You ain't gonna get me this time, K.
I've been practicing.
Yes, you have.
Checkmate, motherfucker.
What the fuck you talking about?
You see it.
Don't make me smile you up
right here, motherfucker.
Your mama won't appreciate
no closed casket.
Kanan, you got a visitor.
Yeah?
You need to stop
with that Ruy Lopez bullshit.
Rack 'em back up.
I'll be back.
I been saying the same shit all along.
We're calling it prosecutorial misconduct.
I don't give a fuck what you call it,
as long as it means I get out.
The police officer that stopped you
admitted that the prosecutor
told him to omit
certain elements from his report,
including the fact
that your back headlight,
the reason why he stopped you
in the first place,
wasn't blown out, but rather, had been
removed.. - The bulb unscrewed.
Somebody wanted me to get pulled over
with drugs in the trunk.
I told my first lawyer that shit.
They set my ass up.
It doesn't matter that you were set up.
It matters that the prosecutor
had material evidence
to support that theory
and hid those facts,
- so the jury never knew.
- Okay.
The D.A. figured, Kanan's
young and black, he's guilty.
Who gives a shit about the rules?
This D.A. has a bunch of cases
under judicial review.
That's why you're getting out fast.
When?
Ain't you cold in that shit?
Stopped standing on the corner years ago.
Don't need no puffy
working from the inside.
You could do it too, boy. You're smart.
No, man. I love the streets.
I ain't trying to be no house nigga.
Change come from inside the house, Rolla.
Who the fuck want to change?
I heard Ruiz got hit.
Stabbed inside a motherfucking strip club.
God damn.
Strip club supposed to be
sacred, you feel me?
One minute you getting a good dick burn,
next, you getting gutted open like a fish.
Yeah.
Streets are saying you did it.
You ask for the weather report,
don't get mad when they say
it's gonna rain.
You believe what you heard?
If y'all was behind it,
we'd be at Ruiz's funeral
right now.
But first Anibal, now this?
You can't blame niggas for wagging tongues.
Looks like you cleaning house.
Or you eliminating the competition.
'Sup, Em?
I told you to stop it with that shit.
If I was Eminem, I would be getting
my dick sucked by some actress right now,
not freezing my balls off
out here with you.
Yo, Rolla says folks are saying
we called the hit on Ruiz.
That's some bullshit.
I say we go by tomorrow
and make sure he knows where we stand.
I wouldn't walk in unprotected.
Soldados shoot first,
ask questions after the fact.
You want to come with me, Rolla?
I'll let you go in first.
- Good to see you, G.
- My man.
Night, Marshall.
Fuck you.
I never get why you like him so much.
He's loyal, and he's smart.
He's too smart to try some shit with Ruiz
without knowing our play.
You think cool runnings gapped off?
Gapped off about what?
Why would the Jamaicans brag
about a botched hit?
They didn't even hit Ruiz.
Owe us a motherfucking store credit.
I know Ruiz didn't check
into no real hospital.
Make sure you know where he's hiding.
We'll go there tomorrow.
Rolla is right about one thing.
If the Soldados suspect us,
they'll have itchy trigger fingers.
I better go alone.
No fucking way.
I ain't gonna let you get clipped
right before Tasha's birthday.
If the worst happens,
she'll never forgive me.
You forgot about her birthday?
Damn, man, she's your wife.
How come I remember, you don't?
I got a lot on my mind, Tommy.
Well, you're welcome.
I'll call you when I get out.
Do that.
We could've met you during the day.
This is the only time I could get away
without them knowing I was gone.
That's live, so from now on,
try to get yourself
near Ruiz and his top guys
when you're talking business.
Especially if they mention
Lobos or the distributor.
We'll be able to hear everything.
Everything, so take your jacket off
before you rub one out, okay?
I don't want to hear that shit.
I thought you were the reptile guy.
You were supposed to.
[Speaking Spanish]
If anything happens,
we'll be on you in 30 seconds.
It takes less than a second
for someone to pull the trigger.
Then we'll be 29 seconds late.
Fuck this.
Get someone else to be your snitch.
Agent Knox is just fucking with you.
Nothing's gonna happen to you.
- You have my word.
- Your word?
I'll remember that when I'm bleeding out.
Look at it this way.
Either wear the mic, or try
your luck up at sing sing.
Pedos do really good up there, I hear.
- Fuck you.
- You flirting with him, Nomar?
Enough!
[Speaking Spanish]
You don't have a choice.
Fuck all of you then.
You're home early.
Figured you'd be at the club all night.
Wasn't at the club. I was with Tommy.
I'd ask you what's up with Tommy,
but you ain't gonna tell me anyway, so...
Well, I don't want your pretty little head
to worry about any of that.
I want you to concentrate
on throwing yourself
the biggest, best birthday
party money can buy.
I thought you forgot.
Now, you see that?
You thought wrong.
Mmhmm.
Yeah, well, it would've been nice
to know a couple of weeks ago.
But that would've ruined
the whole surprise now, wouldn't it?
Sounds like bullshit to me.
Look, baby, I had
this whole thing planned.
I did, and then I thought,
well, who better to design
your party than you?
You'd hate what anyone else
put together anyway.
You got me there.
I already called Kantos.
You and Lakeisha go down tomorrow,
get whatever you want, invite whoever.
Your husband's got you.
Mm.
- Thank you, baby.
- Mm-hmm.
Okay, I promise I won't
break the bank, okay?
Don't make no promises
you can't keep, woman.
- I promise.
- Okay.
You can't sleep?
Something on your mind?
Look.
I know.
It sucks to hear your best friend
is cheating on your other best friend.
Skanks throw themselves at club owners
all the time.
He'll come back to his senses.
Whatever. I'm over that.
I'm fine.
It's just work stuff.
What time are you gonna be home?
I was thinking
I'd make you some Cincinnati Chili.
You know, over spaghetti, with cinnamon?
I bet you never had that.
Sounds fucking disgusting.
You... Are gonna eat it and like it.
Look, Hol, I...
I might be a little late tonight.
How late?
I...
you can make that shit
for me another night.
Another night?
You like having me around, huh?
Yeah, I do.
I need to go shopping today anyway.
I'll see what you got in the kitchen.
There ain't shit in there.
This box of cereal expired two years ago!
Told ya.
Tommy, what's this?
Cash.
No shit.
Thank you for that
comprehensive explanation.
From where?
From the club.
Bullshit it is!
I don't like banks, that's all.
What's the problem?
There are four more
of those in the kitchen.
You are a bank.
You shouldn't be fucking snooping.
Fuck you, Tommy.
I told you not to fucking lie to me.
Look at you, all G'ed up.
You stacking?
What? Nah, nah, nah.
- Uncle G bought me this suit.
- Sign of respect.
You must be stepping it up.
Yeah, and maybe
when you get out in a year,
you know, maybe I'll be somebody.
Maybe.
Hey, I hear motherfuckers
out there beefing.
Is it the Soldados, the Tainos?
- Um...
- It's okay.
It's safe to talk here.
- The Tainos got hit.
- Yeah?
Yeah, and somebody took Anibal out too.
- No shit.
- Yeah, yeah.
And Ruiz got hit.
Maybe in retribution or maybe not,
but I don't really know.
Why you don't know?
'Cause I don't ask no questions.
Your Uncle G pulled you in,
so he expects you to ask questions.
He expects you to come to play, son.
I'm just his driver.
As long as you see yourself as that,
it's all you'll ever be.
We all start off small, man.
Runner, corner, cash-kid.
Question is, what are you
gonna make of yourself?
- I'm working hard.
- That's good.
But not good enough.
How you supposed to learn how G thinks
if you don't know his next move, hmm?
I don't know.
Yeah, I'm telling you.
G waiting on you to prove yourself.
Show him you got the hustle. Get in there.
Take what's yours.
Please tell Mr. Stern
that I called to set a meeting.
I bet he did forget your birthday.
Now it's your chance to make him pay.
Let's put the man-quarium right here.
Girl, what the fuck is a man-quarium?
A giant fish tank filled with men.
You're out of your mind.
- It's your 30th birthday.
- Exactly.
And I want it to be grown and sexy,
but not with no ghetto-ass shit.
Mrs. St. Patrick's right.
I was thinking we can come up
with a birthday shout out
at the top of every hour.
We can come up with a signature cocktail
or maybe even do a balloon
or a confetti drop.
First of all,
she's turning 30, not 13.
So enough with the
balloon stomping, all right?
And make sure there's plenty of Ciroc,
because that's all my people drink,
and no coconut
because I'm allergic to nuts.
Thank you.
I really couldn't wait to see you.
- Yeah.
- I'm starting...
I'm starting to get distracted at work.
It's bad.
Not all bad.
Hello?
Yes, that's fine.
I'll be right there.
You okay?
Everything good?
It's my father.
He's, uh, not well.
I gotta go.
I can pay for the room if you want.
No, are you kidding? I got the room.
Don't worry about the room.
He's out in Long Island.
Gotta get the train.
Paz said he was unhappy there,
and I should've listened.
I could hear him screaming
in the back room.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
He's gonna be okay.
Look at me.
He's gonna be okay, all right?
My ride's downstairs. I can take you.
I want to take you.
[Shouting in Spanish]
You're not listening!
Why is that man in Mr. Williams' bed?
Papi, Papi.
[Speaking Spanish]
Angela!
We're good here. Thank you.
[Speaking Spanish]
You're safe here.
- [Speaking Spanish]
- Shh.
The doctors are looking out for you, Papi.
We all are.
Paz will be by later, okay?
[Speaking Spanish]
That's my friend, Jamie St. Patrick.
He drove me here.
The punk from the corner?
The drug dealer?
I thought I told you
to stay away from that boy.
- He's no good.
- Pap... Papi, shh.
[Speaking Spanish]
He's finally asleep.
It's so hard to believe he's the same man
that grilled me on spelling,
grounded me when I got a "B."
God, he could be an asshole sometimes,
but now he's...
He's helpless, so scared.
I'm sorry.
I'm a mess.
Angie, is there anything I can do?
[Speaking Spanish]
I don't think so,
unless you can make this all go away.
This is Holly.
Obviously I'm doing something
more important than taking your call,
so leave a message.
Hey, call me back.
If I don't answer...
Nevermind.
Just call me.
- Ruiz is expecting me.
- Yeah, yeah.
I've got a nine on my waist.
And one on my ankle.
Hold up.
Oops, I must have forgot about that one.
Who the fuck is you, Rambo?
Can I go see your boss now?
Come on.
[Speaking Spanish]
He's here to see Jefe.
- He clean?
- Yeah.
All right.
Yo. Yo, we got a visitor.
You look like shit.
I can't go to a regular hospital.
Too many fucking questions to answer.
Gracias.
Can we talk alone?
They already patted me down,
took my gat.
Nice of you to visit. Where's Ghost?
She won't let me fuck her in the ass.
Her sister will, though.
I been stabbed twice. I'd rather get shot.
It wasn't us, Ruiz.
- I heard different.
- We ain't got no beef with you.
You're drug dealers.
You got beef with everybody.
They say the same thing about you.
Maybe it was Anibal's people.
Maybe it was Rolla.
Neither of those motherfuckers
any love for you,
and really, nobody else wants you dead?
You're a drug dealer too, Ruiz.
You got more enemies than you even know.
Look.
If me and Ghost was behind this hit,
I wouldn't be here right now,
and neither would you.
[Speaking Spanish]
Who's watching the elevator?
Jefe wants somebody there all day.
I got it.
[Speaking Spanish]
Can you clean it up?
Uh, uh, I don't know.
Would you even know if Ghost
put out a hit on me?
Your compai's been acting
kind of strange tely,
going out of his way to be all nice to me,
but then not showing up
at meetings he arranges.
With all this bullshit going on,
he's trying to keep a low profile,
something you might want
to consider doing.
Celebrating my high holy day,
and this puta sticks me.
The hitter was a girl?
What'd she look like?
She looked like ice cream and sunshine
till she stuck me.
Great tits, beautiful ass,
Latin girl, strong.
A girl hit us too.
Anything else you remember?
I wasn't looking at her face, man.
Light hair, curly.
We find this girl, we find out
who's been hitting us.
Oh, you're goddamn right, Ruiz.
We in this together.
I haven't been back here since I left.
The Bodega got replaced, of course,
with this pet store.
But otherwise
just like the old days.
I thought you could use a milk shake.
Hmm?
You think they still make
black-and-whites?
Well, that's why we here.
Only one way to find out, Miss Big-time.
Oh.
Just give me a second, baby.
What's up?
- Are you on your way in?
- No, I'm having lunch out
in Forest Hills.
You just want to hear my voice? What?
Your wife's birthday...
you sounded serious,
and I'm trying to make it work,
but I'm gonna have to call in
more staff, pay overtime.
Th's fine.
The other woman wanted 20 cases of Ciroc.
Yeah, whatever they need,
just do it. I gotta go.
Wait, there's one more
thing. Simon Stern...
just make it happen.
Fuck are you doing?
Just staying close in
case he needs something.
I was the one who saved his life
while you were all rubbing asses.
Who's the blanquito in there with Ruiz?
That's the guy who gets us the products.
Distro.
I'm going in.
Yo, yo, yo, yo. You'll blow our cover.
You want to call your girlfriend and ask
if you can pretty please do
your fucking job,
you go for it, all right?
I've been on this case three years now.
If Lobos' distributor's in that building,
I'm getting a look.
Son of a fucking bitch.
Who would know a girl like that?
Anibal's dead,
I don't think Rolla would use
a female for wetwork.
- Lobos.
- Ghost don't think so.
You, Ghost...
Have taken your eye off the ball.
Nah, man.
We just waiting for our pitch.
Now, I'm gonna find this bitch.
I'm gonna make things righ with us.
I'ma find that girl. Don't you worry.
[Speaking Spanish]
Yo, that's one crazy motherfucker.
Yo, yo, yo.
[Speaking Spanish]
One floor down, homey.
You feel better now?
A little, but only because
of the milk shake.
I gotta take this.
Go ahead. I understand.
Everything cool?
I'm still alive, if that's what you mean.
- Good, let's talk later.
- No, we need to talk now.
I can't talk right now. I gotta go.
All right, you got my undivided attention.
Fuck.
You've reached 347-555...
Kantos, it's Tommy. Where's your boss?
Is he talking to some
club asshole over there?
I thought he was having lunch with you
out in Forest Hills.
- He's in Forest Hills?
- That's what he said.
Got off the phone in a hurry.
- I'm sorry my dad said that...
- Ah.
About you being a punk, a drug dealer.
Yeah, he remembers what he remembers.
He remembers wrong.
You don't just become a good guy, Jamie.
To get where you are now means
you were always one inside.
I was right about you all along.
You're always taking me someplace to eat
like you're trying to
fatten me up or something.
No, I just like the look on your face
when something gets real good to you.
Mm, you must see that look a lot.
No, it's different, though.
It's your body and your smile
and your mind, the way you think.
It's all of you.
It's not what you are. It's who you are.
Look, Jamie...
Mmhmm, what?
Do you want to come over tonight?
What about Greg?
There is no more Greg.
Hmm.
No more hotels, okay?
Okay.
Thank you.
What are the odds?
My God, Tommy.
- How you doing, Angie?
- Not bad.
- How about yourself?
- Look at you.
I'm holding my own, holding my own.
Get me a black-and-white, large.
I was just visiting a sick friend of mine
not too far from here.
He sends his regards, so I figured,
why not pick up the best black-and-white
in New York on my way home?
I thought you'd be at the club.
What are you two doing way out here?
Oh, you know, just
catching up on old times.
It seems like forever ago.
I'll never forget the time
you tried to hook me up
with your friend, the hot one, Italian.
Silvana, she had a thing for you.
Oh, not enough
to let me get to second base,
and trust me, I tried.
I got my hand up in there.
She cancelled Christmas
on your boy with a quickness.
Kicked me right out onto the street.
You know who would love
these crazy stories
about when we was kids?
His wife, Tasha.
Tomorrow night, we're having
a big birthday party
for her at the club.
You should come.
I work late Thursdays.
Aw, too bad.
Another time.
I'm gonna go.
I don't want your ice creams to melt.
- Thanks.
- You got it.
Thank you.
- Call me later.
- You bet.
I think I'm just gonna catch
the train back to the city.
Angie, I'm sorry.
Sorry about what... that you're married,
that your best friend knows your wife,
that he mentions her name
casually in conversation
because he doesn't know
we're sleeping together?
I'm sorry about Tommy.
Forget about everything he said.
Look, I want to be here with you
and later at your place.
I'll call you, Jamie.
We had a shot, and I took it.
No, you jeopardized the entire
operation on your own.
Who knows when or if we would've had
an opportunity like that?
- And what if someone made you?
- Nobody made me.
- You're sure about that?
- Positive.
Because I know how to handle myself
on and off the field,
unlike some of us in this room.
Fuck you, Medina.
I'll have Ankie call
your S.A.C. Over at the D.E.A.,
get you sent back where you came from.
Oh, really?
Vaya. Take it to Frankie.
This way, um,
I can get a few things
out in the open myself.
Excuse me.
I did the best I could
to keep him from going in.
He didn't even get a good look at the guy?
No.
I sent the audio to forensics
to see if they can clean it up.
We should hear something within 24 hours.
Yeah, well, I'll be here.
Reached Angela Valdes.
I'm unable to take your...
So...
Lunch was nice yesterday.
How was the rest of the date?
None of your fucking business.
That's funny, since the other night,
you were all up in my business
about me seeing Holly.
Look, when you get tired of this girl...
I'm not gonna get tired of her.
Okay, well, when you do,
she's gonna get fucking pissed.
She's gonna fuck up our whole club,
the money, every fucking thing, Tommy.
You worried about me fucking up the club?
If Tasha ever found out that
you were nailing another broad,
she'd blow up your family
and our whole fucking game.
She'd take you to the cops
just to see your
cheating ass rot in prison.
First of all, lower
your fucking voice, man.
Secondly, Tasha wouldn't
do that, and thirdly,
she ain't gonna know shit 'cause
you ain't gonna tell her shit.
Oh, you're damn right
I ain't gonna tell her.
That don't mean she won't find out.
I bet your phone
is full of texts from Angie
and cute little voice messages.
"So good to see you again
after all this time"
after I broke your heart
"and threw it in a fucking dumpster."
- Forgot all about that, huh?
- It's different now.
Yeah, you're married.
That's what's different now.
Look, I got the whole
situation under control.
Yeah.
You always think
you got everything on lock.
Ruiz says a girl stabbed him.
Same as hit Liliana and chased 'Bueso.
Ruiz says it was a Latina
chick with nice tits
and long, light-colored hair.
Bet we could get a better description
if we could ask Liliana,
but, whoa, my bad.
We can't, since we had her iced.
Didn't know I knew about that, huh?
I been looking at that bitch for weeks,
waiting for you to say something.
"Hey, Tommy, I know we agreed to kill her,
but I changed my mind."
That would've worked.
Thought she was more useful alive.
I made a judgment call.
Now we can have Julio go back to Liliana
to see if Ruiz's description
lines the fuck up,
- if she remembers anything.
- Yeah.
We gotta find this girl, man,
and who she's working for.
That's all that matter Tommy.
None of this other bullshit.
Yo, G.
Angela was trouble before,
and she's trouble again.
I just don't want
to see you get fucked up.
That's all.
Hi, Shawn, we're almost ready.
Mama, you look beautiful.
Yeah, that's a real
nice dress, Mrs. St. Patrick.
Thank you both.
Raina, have you seen
my diamond hoop earrings?
No, I'm smart enough
to stay away from your stuff.
But not smart enough
to figure out your fractions.
Did you finish your homework, son?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Game off until you're finished, okay?
- All right, let's roll out.
- Let me find my earrings first.
Watch your mama blame me for that somehow.
Join the club, dad.
Yeah.
Shawn, you went to visit your pops?
- How'd it go?
- Yeah, he's good.
I don't think he's eating enough, though,
so he's looking a lot leaner and
tighter from all the push-ups.
- Tell him I sent my regards?
- Of course.
And he sent his back too.
Cool.
Can you tell my dad I'm old enough
for Assassin's Creed now, Shawn?
What you trying to do, get me killed?
Do your homework.
- Did you find them?
- No.
They'll pop up sooner or later.
Come on, let's go.
Okay, you two, listen
to big mama, all right?
- Okay.
- I'll see you in the morning.
Good night, baby girl.
Take care of your sister.
You want to keep that PS3,
you do your homework for real, now.
- Good night, babies.
- Good night.
How long you gonna duck my calls?
Until you're straight with me,
there's nothing to talk about.
It's just fucking money. Why do you care?
I have it. Enjoy it.
Tommy, if it was about your money,
I wouldn't be in these heels
and this slutty dress.
I would be home on my night off.
Kantos made you come in for this?
Let me talk to that little bitch.
Do you really not understand
why I'm mad at you?
You're mad because you don't believe me.
But that's on you, all right?
That's not my problem.
Then why are you fucking
calling me all day?
You don't get to pick and choose
what part of your life you let me into.
Look, Holly.
I'm not lying to you, all right?
- I got work to do.
- Holly!
We want to give a big shout-out
to the first lady of truth,
Mrs. Tasha St. Patrick.
Happy Birthday, Tasha!
All right, let's make our way over
- to V.I.P., all right?
- Okay.
All right.
Specl treatment, here we go.
Quick thing.
No business tonight.
But this is the kind
of business you want to hear.
Simon Stern called.
He wants to meet.
Tomorrow morning.
Happy Birthday, sis.
- Thank you, Tommy.
- Mwah.
Rather than give you
money, like I always do,
figured I'd put some thought into it.
What?
Very nice, Tommy.
You went to the spa to buy this?
Hell, no, I know a guy who knows a guy
that had the hookup to a real fancy joint
with a sauna, jacuzzi.
Thought maybe you could get
a facial or some shit.
You didn't have to do this, Tommy.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, I did.
You supported us for so long,
always had our backs.
You deserve the best.
Tasha, Tasha!
- Hi
- Hey!
What?
I just want to say
Happy Birthday, Tash!
I'll bright back.
Oh.
Hey, Tasha, I was just about to come over
and wish you a Happy Birthday.
Where did you get those earrings?
These?
You stole them from my damn house.
No, I didn't.
Shut your lying ass up,
and give me back my shit
while you still have a job.
Tasha, these aren't yours. They're mine.
Tommy bought them for me.
Good, then he can tell me that himself.
Come on.
- What's going on?
- Please tell her...
You buy those earrings for her?
Yeah, I bought 'em. Why, you like 'em?
I would've got you a pair too.
Yeah, I do like them.
They remind me of a pair I used to have.
Great minds think alike.
Come on! I got a surprise for you.
Holly!
Oh, just come on.
Ladies and gentlemen!
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'd like to introduce
the lady of the hour,
Mrs. Tasha St. Patrick, to rock the mic.
I'm not singing
at my own damn birthday party.
Why not? Beyonce did it at hers.
I'm not Beyonce.
You would be in her group if she'd let you.
Now, come on. Come on.
♪ I will love you anyway ♪
♪ even if you cannot stay ♪
♪ I think you are the one for me ♪
♪ Here is where you ought to be ♪
♪ I just want to satisfy you ♪
♪ Though you're not
mine I can't deny it ♪
♪ Don't you hear me talking, baby? ♪
♪ Love me now, or I'll go crazy ♪
♪ Whoa, sweet thing ♪
♪ don't you know you're my everything? ♪
♪ Yes, u are ♪
_
♪ I wish you were my lover ♪
♪ But you're so undercover ♪
Hey, I was beginning to think
your phone was broken.
No, not broken.
I told you I would call you.
Well, I couldn't wait that long.
You're at the party now?
Yeah, but I'd rather be with you.
I think you mean that.
You're there with all those people,
and I'm here, alone.
But I'm alone too, Angie.
You know, yes, I mean,
there's a lot of people here.
Most of them are supposed to be my friends,
but I'm alone when I'm not with you.
Can I come see you?
You need to give me some time, Jamie.
♪ You are my heat ♪
♪ you are my fire ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
Thanks.
Thanks, everybody.
Give it up for Tasha!
Great party last night.
How tired are you?
I'm not. I'm ready.
Gentlemen, welcome.
Thank you for venturing up here.
Pleasure, sir.
Ah, the elusive James St. Patrick.
Simon Stern. Pleasure.
Come in. Make yourself comfortable.
Here, have a seat.
Let me cut to the chase.
Cynthia Sheridan took her business from me
to come to you and your club...
- Truth.
That vexed me a great deal.
- It wasn't personal, sir.
- Of course not.
But it made me think either you're stupid
and don't care about profit...
because you basically gave
the whole cow away for free...
or you're smart and have something I don't.
Other than the Cynthia Sheridan parties?
We have a full house every night,
another 500 waiting out in the cold,
two DJs on retainer,
a back entrance for celebrities.
Something tells me
Simon knows our stats already.
You're asking what makes us
more than just lightning
in a bottle.
You're right, I am.
You're wanting to know
what I have to offer you.
Well, you have to make me an offer.
I see.
Holly! Hoy.
Yo, Holly! Been looking all over for you.
- Get in the car.
- Fuck you.
You stole from Tasha,
and I lied to cover your ass.
Now get in the fucking car!
What kind of fucking criminal are you?
You owe me one now.
Come on, get in the car.
What the fuck you thinking
stealing from Tasha, my family?
I didn't think she would miss them.
Her closet, it's like
a fucking department store.
It doesn't matter how much shit she has.
She's like my sister.
I told you that before
we went to their place.
Look...
I like to take shit.
That's just who I am.
I'm sorry, though. It was a dick move.
You can rat me out to her if you want.
Whoa, where you going now?
All that money I found
in your place, Tommy...
that's not from the club.
No, it's not.
But if you're gonna be my girl,
I gotta be able to trust you, Holly.
What I tell you,
you... Can't tell nobody
'cause nobody else knows.
I want to know.
Thing is,
I sell some dope on the side
to make a little extra money.
I'm a drug dealer.
I'm not fucking stupid.
Your phone isn't ringing day and night.
You don't live in some shitty wackup.
And there's no way "some dope"
pays for a nightclub.
Whatever you're doing
ain't a goddamn hobby.
Tell me the truth, Tommy.
I'm at the top of the food chain.
I got a crew of motherfuckers
hustling for me,
and we move serious weight.
If I go away, I go away for good.
You wanted the truth.
Yeah, I did.
So what you think?
I am a fucked-up thief,
and you are a crazy drug dealer.
I think
you and I were made for each other.
You're here.
I'm here.
Unannounced.
I like the element of surprise.
You said you and Greg are over.
We are.
So can I come in?
I think that's a bad idea.
I saw Simon Stern today.
It went great.
He wants to have dinner,
keep talking about a future.
Congratulations, Jamie.
I'm really happy for you.
You're the first person I wanted to tell.
In fact, you're the only
person I wanted to tell.
When I'm with you,
I can't hold myself back.
I want to.
I want the reality to matter,
but it doesn't.
I just see you.
I get wrong when I'm away from you.
I need another hit to get right.
Another hit?
That's exactly how it feels.
[Speaking Spanish]
I was so committed to not seeing you,
and then you just knock on my door,
and I let you in.
A girl only has so much resolve.
Sorry.
No, you're not.
What were you even
supposed to talk about anyway?
Stern.
My meeting.
Tell me.
Come on.
Well, I don't want to get ahead of myself,
but we talked about partnering,
expansion,
Vegas, Miami.
Mm, I like Miami.
Sorry, babe.
I know.
I don't want you to go.
I don't want to go.
I mean, is there any way...
could you stay the night?
Never mind, I know the answer.
Reality calls.
I wish I could, Angie.
Hey, hey.
It won't always be like this.
Yeah, okay.
I promise.
Thank you so much, Shawn.
I hope you got a chance to enjoy
some of the party the other night.
Yeah, I did.
Actually, um...
I got you a little something myself.
Shawn, you did not have to do that.
You do enough already.
Nah, it's just a little something.
I hope it makes you smile.
I heard you say you lost
a pair of earrings, so, um...
They're beautiful.
But I can't accept them.
I wouldn't want Ghost
to get the wrong idea.
Yeah.
Yeah, right.
Excuse me?
What was that?
Shawn, what did you just say?
Nothing. I didn't say anything.
I mean,
you deserve someone who's
as loyal to you as you are to him.
What the hell does that mean?
He's always just putting
other stuff ahead of you.
But what the hell do I know?
I'm just the driver, right?
I need men down in the garage
and at all the doors.
Someone coming.
Security needs to be tight.
Who knows what this fucking
[Speaking spanish] has planned.
Who?
I'm expecting Ghost,
the pendejo who supplies us
and most likely put
these fucking holes in me.
What this fucking
[speaking spanish] Has planned.
Who?
I'm expecting Ghost,
the pendejo who supplies us
and most likely put
these fucking holes in me.
- You want me to frisk him?
- What do you think?
I'm telling you this piece of shit
tried to have me killed,
and you're asking me
if you should see
if he's carrying a weapon?
What the fuck?
- [Speaking spanish]
- Has planned.
Who?
I'm expecting Ghost,
the pendejo who supplies us
and most likely put
these fucking holes in me.
You want me to frisk him?
I'm expecting Ghost.