Xem Phim Online HD Nhanh Nhất Tại VIPHD.VN
Good day, sir.
Welcome to the Sofitel.
Good morning, ladies.
Sorry, there
does really sorry, but ... me
I got yesterday evening
some celebrated, woke up ...
... wanted to go to the bathroom and I ended up in the hallway.
The door is simply fallen. Click and ...
Here you have a towel.
I'll get you.
-- Yes.
-- What room are you?
-- 207th
-- Ah yes, the 207th
-- Thank you, thank you.
-- Here you go.
-- I'm really sorry.
-- My pleasure.
Damn.
Do you hips hurt again?
This damn rain.
-- Hello, Olivier.
-- Good evening, sir.
This ring, I can appreciate it.
It is worth nothing.
Junk, can you imagine that?
People put such a
shitty ring in the safe.
They make fun of us, really.
You ought to show, Albert.
This is the diamond.
He will be auctioned.
"The incredible story
the sinister diamonds. "
137 carats. can
you imagine that?
Quite a large diamond.
Estimated cost:40 million euros for
a stone. Do you know what that means?
Scylla is very reliable.
I do not care.
That's not my problem.
He wants to meet you, and
You do not move.
I can not Paris
leave, you know that.
If I do not come to work, call
they immediately my probation officer to.
That's the problem.
You do what they tell you.
You're a thief, yeah right.
Like everyone else, the bankers, the people who
us go up to the alarm clock on television.
Your problem is that you're not a political
matic conscience have. Thee is all the same.
I can prove it to you immediately.
If you make a wish
had, what would it be?
Do you see that?
-- What?
-- The ancients there.
As they are. This is my wish.
Damn. This is proof.
Absolutely no political conscience.
As this old guy to be.
Listen, love fairy, I'm just
out of jail and I feel lonely.
Will not you once and for all
out of all this shit?
Finally we get to know us.
Quite difficult
get at you.
Have I told you so. He is a
Genius, but he prefers to work alone.
He broods too much.
These are the plans of the security system,
that is installed by the company LINVAS.
Check it out.
The diamond is at the Grand Hotel
issued by Antwerp.
And we have the list of all
Those during the auction
are responsible for the security.
That probably means you're at it.
I trust Albert and Albert trusted you.
Who is responsible for the auction?
Well, until next month.
Simon.
Hello.
Sit down.
The workshop called me yesterday.
How did you do that again?
Shit happens. I'm just
slipped on the stairs.
I do not like that
you can not work.
Who does not work, hanging out, and who
hanging around, comes silly ideas.
What will you do with your free time?
Stop smoking.
I do not smoke.
You think I'm stupid?
Here smoking is prohibited, and
what you've got in your hand?
It is not.
To or not, I do not care.
You smoke.
Are you going with me to just
as with your cigarettes?
You act as if you
playing by the rules
and secretly want
again turn a thing.
Am I your probation
cancel? Do you want that?
I'll put them away.
I should perhaps you under
stricter security questions.
Here, I'll put them away. Hopp.
And stop smoking.
Good day.
Come on in.
I met Marie,
when she and her daughter Julia
on our family estate after
the diamond, the Florentin, was looking for.
She has been looking a long time.
12 years.
And they found him.
Marie was a very warm woman.
Your charisma, intelligence,
their persistence will be missed.
Marie and her daughter have us
shown that you should never give up
no matter what ever you are looking for.
That is what our
Existence is a real sense.
Pierre, my sincere condolences.
-- Madame de Courcy.
-- Good day, Monsieur Galley.
I would like you
Francois Malleyssie imagine.
He cares about our
Sales in New York and London.
Madame, very pleased.
Francois is the man of the
Format has to carry out this auction.
Monsieur Galley before with
Monsieur Malleyssie talk,
we should ask Julia if she is not the
Wishes to continue her mother's work.
Are you serious?
You need not only to the
Presentation of the diamond care,
but also the
Safeguards the media.
For this you need experience.
She has my full confidence.
See only.
Where is Julia now?
How is one to
leave someone
who does not even go to the funeral
her own mother comes.
Papa?
Dad, come on come on.
Put you to bed.
Come on.
My little girl.
Look at all these flowers.
You are responsible for your mother.
Papa, I will ...
... and the sale take over.
The sale take?
You talked to Blanche.
She called me.
I have to go for mom.
I can not give it all up now.
You could have asked me,
what I think about it, right?
This decision I make alone.
I am the one who is
takes care of the insurance.
You will work with me!
Do you know what I would have said,
if you had asked me?
I would have said no. this stone
is cursed. He just brings misfortune.
Your mother
therefore lost their lives!
The jewelry is in this particular konstru--
ated, secure stand presented.
He is electromechanical with two
Security locks closed.
The key
precision mechanical indentations
and an electronic chip.
Is it possible to imitate?
Impossible. They are different
and can not be faked.
During the presentation will be a key
kept by the head of the security company.
In the command center
on the fourth floor of the hotel.
To get this code,
coat of a team the command center,
to which they over the tubes
the air conditioner reach.
The second key is the whole
Guarded evening of Julia Neuville.
It organizes the sale.
-- Does she have it with you?
-- Yes, it is.
To get to the key heranzu--
come, you have to replace it.
And for that we need a perfect copy,
both in terms of optics
As for the weight as well.
We need a reprint of the original.
A silicone impression of
two pages and photos.
The key for which it is responsible
is located in the safe of her room ...
... in her closet, at
Ground screwed.
Easy to get into the suite?
This is exactly the problem.
It is the safest
Apartment of the whole hotel.
Has the key
the security officer.
And the floor has only one entrance.
We have someone in the hotel?
His name is Jean--Louis Sudek.
-- Very well, sir.
-- Goodbye, Monsieur.
-- Yes?
-- Have a nice day.
-- Goodbye.
-- Grand Hotel, good day.
-- Good day, mademoiselle.
How is it going? -- Good day.
-- Good and you?
-- Also good.
-- We have the suite prepared for you.
-- Thanks, that's nice.
Marie Neuville died of an overdose
their drug against diabetes.
Was found dead in her car.
The vehicle was locked from the inside.
Michael Wurst, auctioneer.
A diamond in my school.
Death of Marie Neuville.
Will you give them Derteau?
Yes, I'll meet him immediately.
The Florentin is not
just a precious stone.
He is a legend.
We have considered the following,
to bring it to bear.
A stand in a
spiral space that is both open ...
... is closed and in themselves.
Guests can here him in an intimate,
admire mysterious atmosphere.
The focus of our sales
are the only jewelry,
as the Florentin.
There are only three objects
auctioned, which are unique.
And thus, this
Detailed auction in history.
No one has ever dared
an auction with only a diamond
and a single further
Perform gem.
I hope Julia that we
so do not ruin us.
Sorry.
I have an important
Message for Mademoiselle Neuville.
Yes?
Thank You.
Gentlemen, we are all
More again in our ...
-- Wait.
-- ... The next meeting to speak on Friday.
-- Who gave you that?
-- A man who wanted to talk.
I told him, you
were in a meeting.
-- Where is he? -- He's gone.
He could not wait.
If we take the Florentin not
more than 40 million sale,
we need this auction
regarded as a failure.
And you have a responsibility.
Simon Farrell, National Security Advisor.
-- Hello?
-- Simon Farrell?
Julia Neuville here.
-- If you are Simon Farrell?
-- This is me.
What makes it out, go out to you?
This money from you in the
Envelope, I do not understand.
These are the 12,000 euro that your
Mother had given me an advance.
And of course the
Plans. Here you are.
Since everything is in there. And there are
no reason to keep her here.
The plans of what?
The plans of the security system,
and the display tray of LINVAS
in the auction house Galley.
I could not but
leave at the reception.
The display tray? My mother has given you
given the plans of the safety system?
Yes, I should carry out an audit.
And what the issues are in your work?
Her mother did not trust
the safety concepts,
follow a simple matrix.
You say to them:"jewelry,
Antwerp ", and think:
"No problem, easy money."
My task was to
To check the security.
Since when do you work for them?
I work for about
ten years, along with your mother.
I'm sorry.
I have to go.
For which auctions?
The Potemkine, the Petit Sancy 2005
the issue of the British
Crown Jewels at the Petit Palais ...
A total of about ten.
Your most important auctions,
She never told me about it.
Could a
take the later train?
I'm sorry, I have
an appointment in Paris.
How did you meet her?
I was the security system of a
great jeweler on the Place Vendôme
was in the broken renew.
Her mother has the expertise
created for the insurance.
That was '99, I think.
-- Lorenz Bäumer?
-- Julia ...
Sorry, your death ...
I know how
close they were.
They have with them
Lorenz Bäumer know?
I really have to go now.
Goodbye.
We must this
Information not pass,
but your mother was a friend.
I'll make an exception.
-- Thank You. -- These data are still
not in the computer. You're too old.
-- Good day. -- Good day.
Do you have the documents to Farrel?
-- Good day.
-- Yes.
Explore alone everything.
Simon Farrell has worked '99 for us
when my father
Security System renewed.
He has chosen the concept
the monitor monitoring care.
I leave you to Mr Derteau.
Many Thanks.
Electrical Engineer ...
Anxious depressed state
due to the death of the mother.
On the right side
you can see the cathedral.
It is one of the highlights of the architecture ...
... and belongs to
World Heritage Site by UNESCO.
It originated from a
Lady Chapel and was ...
Good day.
Thank you for coming.
See in this jacket
They are very similar to your mother.
I'm thinking about
Their contracts to take over.
But I have to more
know about their collaboration.
I am not sure,
whether this is a good idea.
Why are you here,
if you do not want?
I just ask only
if you want to mimic your mother
or whether the benefits
my services are convinced?
Galley, the director, has everything
done to get rid of me.
I stand on my first
major auction alone.
And there is one more thing.
My father is around
the insurance care.
So what?
He has the death of my
Mother not yet been overcome.
Do not trust him?
Have fun with Michael Wurst
talked about our meeting?
Her mother told me,
what he means to you.
If you are referring to our affair,
the thing of the past.
No, I have Michael
said nothing about it.
I just want the plans
My mother pursue,
therefore I met you. But ...
... that was probably not a good idea.
I see.
Nowadays it is very difficult,
trust someone opposed to accommodate.
Nice to have met you.
Another bit of advice, Julia.
Ask the security company,
whether the drivers for the
Transport of Florentins are divided,
have a driving license.
Has anyone of them Somehow
which comments on the procedure
or the proposed contracts?
No.
-- Good.
-- Yes.
I want to see the list of drivers,
for the transport of jewelry
from the airport to
Are responsible hotel.
Julia if you name the
all people want to know
dealing with the security
jewelery employ,
we sit here next year.
I would also like
see their driver's licenses.
Is there anything in this way?
I will not sign,
without having seen the papers.
You are not serious?
Very seriously.
-- Would you please tell us the
Get Treaty? -- Yes of course.
-- If you please wait briefly.
-- Yes.
Here is the list of names
the people from the transport.
We will give you the
Give licenses, the driver still.
The license of
Monsieur Burlini was collected.
I learn just that the
License of Monsieur Burlini,
of more than 15 years for us
works, was drafted to August.
But he's only replacement and
is of course not drive.
What happens when a
the driver something happened?
What happens if Monsieur Burlini
has to step in for some reason?
Then the diamond is not insured.
So you actually place
a driver than a representation ...
... which, if it has to take the wheel, all
Contractual clauses overrides.
We will Monsieur Burlini
exchange, Mademoiselle.
I hope so.
Ask LINVAS
several deals
for the installation
the hidden cameras.
More deals?
Was at 80 per cent of all thefts
it complicit in the security companies.
You should so many different
Contract service providers as possible.
Thank You.
Everything is recorded.
The order, times,
the due dates.
And all this time without the cherry.
You forgot the cherry.
This is the only
Copy that I keep.
They are the same agreements,
as I had with your mother.
Many Thanks.
I'm sorry that I
was the last time so harshly.
But this sale
is something special.
My mother has her
life dreamed.
Here you are.
Julia. Oops, you here?
-- Simon, a friend of mom.
-- Well, Michael Wurst.
I am the auctioneer of
Sale, the Julia organized.
Louise, my wife.
-- Good Evening.
When is the meeting tomorrow?
At ten clock.
-- Well, I'll see you then.
-- Good.
Have a good evening.
-- Have a good evening.
Do not you find it strange
that he shows up here?
I'm sorry if the
out of tune. But it's just a coincidence.
Pure coincidence.
One last thing.
I have yet to secure your room.
And that means?
Check to see if someone Microphones
or cameras has mounted,
to gain access to information.
For that I need with my
Equipment unnoticed in your room.
If it were up Thursday by 17 clock?
Mademoiselle Neuville!
Mademoiselle Lombard!
Good day. Julia, the
Jean--Philippe Robier,
Journalist of the newspaper
"Children ask".
I'm really sorry.
They are much too late, I have
yet another appointment.
Listen, I know it's
only a newspaper for children,
but a job like yours,
dream of the kids.
We got several mails, since the
Sale of diamonds was announced.
I have read, you have the
Project presented in a second class.
thousands of children
Read our newspaper.
Christelle, accompany the Lord,
please. I'll be there in five minutes.
-- Come on.
-- Thank You.
I have the questions in this
Answer journalists.
I'll let you in my suite,
then you can start ever.
I would prefer if you were there.
Do not worry, there will be nobody bother.
Your stuff is there next door.
You are welcome
take something to drink.
I'm waiting for you.
Has your mother somehow
influence in the choice of your profession?
My mother gave me her
Shared passion.
As I recall, was
it always gems with us.
-- To consider ...
-- Sorry.
One second. I believe,
we have to stop short.
-- I have a feeling that ...
-- Monsieur Robier?
... there is a little problem.
-- Only ten minutes for the interview.
-- Yes, yes, yes.
-- Thank You.
Well, I've got it now.
They said that ...
-- That's it? -- Yes.
-- Very good.
I would just like to
take a few photos.
Photos were not provided.
It will not take long.
-- For the newspaper, of course.
-- All right.
-- Make quiet a few photos.
-- It is better ...
... if you imagine the column.
Oh, but look seriously at the photo.
Ah, that's better.
-- Thank you, really.
-- Goodbye.
I'm your press officer
Send a copy of the issue.
Yes, yes, very good.
Sorry, it has
took longer than I thought.
I'm done.
Seems all right.
I have a Frequenzaufzeichner
built into the phone,
to determine whether you will be listened to.
The security company has given me the
Overview where you wanted.
Here is a copy of the
Insurance contracts of my father.
-- Please, take a look at it.
-- I will.
And the first installment.
This is my mother's money.
They would approve it, that we
cooperate in this sale.
Excuse me, please.
Hello?
Yes, until then.
So do I.
I'm sorry.
I'll be over in a few days,
pick up the recorder.
-- I'll call you.
-- Good.
Do you mind if my
Suitcase while staying here?
No.
-- Go back to Paris today?
-- No.
Wait for me downstairs?
Only five minutes
I'm right with you.
-- Agreed.
-- Good.
-- Then to the same.
-- Yes.
-- Hey, how are you?
-- Good, and you?
Come on.
Oh, hello, my beauty.
-- What do you do?
-- Good, and you?
Nice to see you.
This is Simon, a friend.
Jerry, our host.
Good Evening,
pleasant, I am pleased.
Ta--da!
What do you think?
-- Fantastic.
Come on. I shall
imagine Sam.
Sam!
-- This is Julia.
-- Hi. -- Hello.
Very beautiful.
Can your friend might be in the photograph?
Would you come up with on the photo?
No thanks.
Come on.
Come on, do not worry.
-- Okay, sit down.
-- Come, sit down.
Do not panic.
It's just a photo.
Julia, could you stand behind him?
You slip it
another piece over.
Okay, quite loose. Yes.
Take the high, yeah?
Very beautiful.
Julia, come a little
closer to your face.
Put it around your hand.
No, the other.
Yes, just like that.
Look at me.
Think of something funny.
Perfect.
Hey, I could be you
both times kidnap short?
-- Will you please also Julia?
-- I'll be right back.
-- Here.
-- Will not you keep it?
-- No, it's ok.
-- Are you sure?
-- But yes.
-- Good.
Then I'll take it.
Excuse me
One moment please.
Good Evening.
-- A Mitraillette, please -- Could
You pick me up on the market?
-- Yes? Thank You.
-- I ordered a Mitraillette.
-- What do you want?
-- What is a Mitraillette?
-- Two Mitraillette, please.
-- Coming right up.
-- And please, with lots of ketchup and mustard.
-- Sure thing.
You will see
it tastes great.
You burn down everything swells out ...
... dropped on the clothes.
And fat is not.
-- You are welcome.
-- Many Thanks.
-- What is it?
-- Eight Euros. -- Thank You.
Thank You.
Honestly, I never would have
thought, something to eat sometimes.
Da.
Can I give you a
ask indiscreet question?
No.
I share it with you anyway.
Where are you from? I mean,
how did you grow up?
Is it true that you in your mother
lost the same age as me?
You are well informed.
Is your father still alive?
I suppose there.
Should we still somewhere
eat a dessert?
No, thanks, I think I
rather stay with the Mitraillette.
I'll call you when
I'm back in town.
Thank You.
Good Night.
Where have you been?
What do you mean,
where I've been?
Pass on the girl. you
now should not play the Casanova.
Good night, Albert.
The last number can
not be seen.
The system is by itself
the third failed attempt lock.
There is a Nine.
14.5.1979.
This is the wedding anniversary
their parents. May 14, '79.
Julia?
Simon Farrell.
No, I'm not submerged. I
have examined the documents of your father.
Tomorrow I will in Antwerp
be to pick up my stuff.
How much is your clock Dinner?
Well, then we could
meet by 19 clock 30.
Unfortunately I could not before. the
is hopefully not a problem for you?
I thought you had forgotten me.
Get me up after your dinner?
My Dinner fails. I shall
work while you reduce your devices.
I need about an hour.
If you go out
want, that's no problem.
Do not worry.
Your things are over there.
Yes.
Three days before the auction I can not.
We had so agreed.
All right, listen, call
me in the morning again.
Very good. I am looking at
and tell you about it.
Did you have time, the documents
To check the security company?
Yes. LINVAS has
done an excellent job.
Honestly, you would
it can not do better.
Here you are.
Thank You.
-- Yes?
-- It's me, Michael.
I've heard that the Russians
have enabled you?
Want to have dinner with me?
That's sweet of you,
but I have to do.
Julia, I need to talk to you.
You'll beautiful every day.
That makes me mad.
Well, we go together
a drink, okay?
-- Okay.
-- Just A Moment.
I'll get my coat only briefly.
-- Good Evening.
I leave you better off alone.
What's the matter with you?
This is it, Inès de Boissiere.
She lives alone, no
Members, no children.
It's tonight to Benefiz--
Gala Casino invited in the city.
You do not let them out of sight ...
... of the moment,
when she enters the casino,
until it leaves again.
-- I am delighted to see you.
-- Good Evening.
I wish you
a lovely evening.
It's done, you can
get started. She's in there.
You can begin.
I'll do a five minute break.
LIFT OUT OF SERVICE
I have to go.
-- What time is it?
-- Late.
Hey, still remains a bit.
-- Have a nice evening.
-- Good Night.
Thank you very much.
Here we are,
my darling. Come Over.
Come on, go. Mama
takes off her coat.
It's all right.
No.
No, no.
Hello?
Niko! Come here!
Go quickly, come here!
Take the curtain cords!
Come on!
-- Hello? -- God! What did
you built for a shit!
You had nothing else to do than
to monitor them and warn us!
Because of you, she is now dead.
What is this
hot, she's dead?
-- What is fucking wrong?
-- I messed up.
The old woman came home
while the others were there.
I am to blame for her death.
-- Who beat you up?
-- You hold out there.
Did you beat him?
It has nothing to with it
do. He was not there.
-- Come here, you asshole!
-- Take it easy!
I would have him
to kill.
If you see him again
touch her, I'll kill you!
He has ruined everything! this
Idiot! This old bag!
Let me go! Come here,
you asshole! Come here!
Let's go, go.
Yes?
Here.
I'm done.
I cut it off, Simon.
I'm going back to Paris.
-- Have you talked with Scylla?
-- Yes.
We have arranged for us
because of the coal.
I'm too old for this job.
Have a nice day, buddy.
What will you do with that?
Can you drive so ever?
Yes.
Simon.
I'm in a meeting.
I do not have much time.
There is one detail about the
We have not talked yesterday.
I thought we were
gone through everything.
Seriously, Julia,
listen to me. Okay?
It's about the key for the installer.
The Safety Officer
has the first key,
and I do not want
that you have the second.
Give him Galley.
Are you worried?
Tell the people of LINVAS that ...
... you do not feel comfortable,
if you have the key with you.
-- All Right?
-- Yes.
I'm serious, Julia.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I must return today to
Exhibition here I am again.
It is the key in the evening
the auction does not have with him.
The Security Service has
decided that Galley will have him.
The goal is now so someone else.
Have you bought a new clock?
Yes, I treated myself to something.
A little something, after all.
From time to time.
Do not you have
Boredom so out of work?
But already, but I am concerned.
Hello.
Listen ...
What?
No, I never said that!
Wait a moment, please.
Simon, please, go yet
and get us two coffees.
The machine is back in the hallway.
Just look at this! This may be the
Penner not do that to me!
Damn, what
all this shit?
How can my
Integrity question?
-- Sorry.
-- This is already.
-- If you already go.
-- Absolutely.
No.
Not look his game?
No, a second,
quite uncertain.
Yes, exactly.
Bye.
I stand by me here in the legs
the abdomen, just so he tells me,
I would have more
effort. I'm tired.
-- Thank You. -- I'm tired
more on this shit.
Come, age, let us
do something else.
I am what intervening
come. I need to court.
I'll take you with me.
We talk in the car.
No, not necessary.
Do Not Worry.
I come alone clear. yet
this, it is the other way.
Thanks for the coffee.
Goodbye.
-- Goodbye. -- Here you can read it
everything! What do you want more?
Hey, man, now tell
but also something.
Attention to track three,
incoming train from Marseille.
Arrival 16 clock past eleven.
Be careful when passing train.
-- All aboard.
-- Good day, Madame.
Be careful with the departure of the train.
The doors close automatically.
Your compartment is a
Little further forward.
Good day.
Lieutenant Fauré and Kopel of the Cid.
-- Monsieur Delcourt?
-- Yes. What's up?
Please get in.
What are you doing here?
One of my prisoners on parole
is on a train to
Antwerp risen, though he ...
Although he Paris
allowed to leave any circumstances.
Simon Carrera is on the way
Antwerp. He plans a robbery.
We wish him and his
Catch people in the act.
But I have to follow the rules
and inform the judge
and the gendarmerie.
If we arrest them before, are
they get out in three or four years.
Judge Rousselot has already been informed.
Until we have arrested them do
You as though everything as always.
Routine stop. If anything
happen, call me.
Understood in this country
you what it means to forge.
These are real forgeries. than
whether it would create.
The guy who did it, white
exactly as working time.
That should be sold as a masterpiece.
He has certainly taken days,
to select color.
He's got a zirconium with a very
high radiation reflective found.
Even the edges are sharp.
He does not even have a
used electric grinder.
Everything by hand.
With infinite patience, as
he had invented the loops.
Many Thanks.
-- Hello, Blanche.
-- Hello, Julia.
I'm happy to be here.
I'm sure you'll be thrilled.
Good Evening.
Thank you very much.
Monsieur Galley, tell us
about the safety precautions.
Furthermore, I would like
reveal too much.
As you know, was this diamond
long time as gone.
-- Because no other room is available?
-- Like I said, Madame,
i am very sorry,
All rooms are fully booked.
But do not worry.
3--2--2, I'll send someone.
-- Could you check that? Would that be possible?
-- Yes. I'll have a look.
Ground floor at the command center.
This command center.
An elevator is plugging--in
remained on the fifth floor.
-- Good Evening.
-- Here you go.
-- Thank you.
-- Have a nice evening.
-- Thank You.
I'll tell you everything
you want to know.
And respect.
Fantastic.
That was great.
Nice to have you here.
Julia, dear, many
Thanks for the invitation.
I have the Florentin
seen. He is wonderful.
This reminds me of the time when
did you get your mother to the studio.
You were still a very little girl.
It was just amazing.
So what I've never seen.
Have in this chandelier
We found the diamond.
It was founded in 1918 with a
Jeweler commissioned.
He had to cut 99 crystals in the form
a double rose, like the Florentin.
When we counted, it was the 100th
One too many.
The 100th was the Florentin.
Come Over.
Please make behind us.
-- Have you seen him before?
-- No.
My little girl.
-- You look gorgeous.
-- Thank you, Papa.
May I Simon
imagine a friend.
-- My father, Pierre Neuville.
-- Nice to meet you.
Are you here for the story
here or in case of diamonds?
-- I'm here because of Julia.
-- That's the best reason.
Excuse me,
I'll be right back.
-- Pierre.
-- Ah, Philippe.
Philippe de Mazières,
I can imagine, that's ...
-- Simon.
-- Simon, a friend of Julia.
-- Nice to meet you.
You can count themselves lucky.
familiar Julia
not so easy anyone.
-- How did they do it?
-- Do not reply.
Philippe was ambassador to Djibouti.
It is a kind of occupational disease.
He mixes everywhere
and creates a file on each.
Nice to have you here.
Please make behind us.
Here is a customer.
Got it.
The key is in there now.
They rise up again.
-- Hands up!
-- Get down!
On the ground! Get down!
You, hands up!
Come on, over here!
Thank You.
First, I would like to
Thank you all,
you to this
Exhibition came.
I feel by
Their presence very honored.
Let me begin by saying a few
Words about the diamonds to say.
maybe knew
Do not let it, but ...
... is Florentin,
without a doubt, the diamond,
the story
most coined.
For the first time in 1471 in the possession
mentioned the Bold Charles,
heard this famous gem ...
-- It's your turn.
... of more than 137 carats ...
... and with 126 facets to the first
European cut diamonds ...
... and the most beautiful
of the Christian era.
I should bring you.
Ah, okay. All right, thank you.
Murder and dramas revolve
around the historic jewel,
a showpiece of the
Ark of the Habsburgs.
From the beloved Mayer compact up to Empress
Sissi has this gem turned heads,
Sown discord and
incited to murder.
A diamond that -- the legend
for -- its owners bring bad luck.
No, thank you.
It means that all
Gems have a memory.
I believe that the Florentin ...
... an imprint of all
Person carries within itself,
in with him
Contact came.
I would like to mention one that
has helped to make new celebrity
by having rediscovered it.
My mother, Marie Neuville.
Thank you very much.
What's going on?
What's up?
Blanche.
Is there a doctor in the room?
What about her?
Excuse me, but
is there a doctor here in the hall?
-- Here we go.
-- Okay.
Driving off.
Hurry up!
This way!
-- Caution!
-- Out of the way!
Attention, please!
Monsieur?
This is the director. I am
the organizer of the auction.
I do need to
Key he has with him.
-- Do you belong to the family?
-- No, we work together.
If you want, we call
Safety Officers
will confirm that
they really need the key.
Okay.
You know what? Mind
you serve your guests.
I'm trying
find out what's going on.
Many Thanks.
Caution, let us through!
Do you have any idea what's going on?
A few guests fainting.
-- I'll go look.
-- Okay.
We are the gain. We guard
the diamonds until everything has calmed down.
Diamond in the command center,
Please confirm request.
Let them through.
If one has sent you? Good ...
-- Mademoiselle Neuville?
-- Yes?
-- Lieutenant Fauré, BRB.
You have just been mugged.
Evacuation or change your
Guests arises without panic.
Ladies and gentlemen, I beg you
To remain calm and to leave the room,
so that the doctors
undisturbed their work ...
Police! Come on, turn around!
-- Hands on your head!
Turn Around!
Hands on your head!
-- Go!
-- Go! Hands on your head!
Take it easy!
Out of the way!
The fire extinguisher.
Go, go!
-- Police!
-- Hands on your head!
-- I want to see your hands!
-- On the floor!
Monsieur, you are wrong,
this man works for me.
Simon, tell him.
Tell him yet.
Climbing because over there!
Mademoiselle Neuville, a comment!
Let's go through please.
-- Please, post a comment!
-- What happened?
Sorry, Telephone
for you, Monsieur Galley.
-- Hello?
-- The Key ...
I no longer have it.
Do not worry, I have.
The jewelry is safe.
Where are they?
Somewhere in the harbor at the docks.
Stay there, I'll call the police.
-- I need to talk to a police officer.
-- There's nobody more.
The police just moved away.
Call to the police.
We made it!
Okay.
But that's impossible!
They claim that there was
no police action.
Nothing.
Give me your mobile phone.
So what?
Could not have gone better!
The police this morning
an abandoned boat found.
It should involve the yacht,
with the gangsters fled.
It is believed that the
Complicity in the distribution of prey
have killed each other ...
... and in this massacre
were no survivors.
In one discovered in the water
Body was one of the earrings found
the necklace was in the dinghy.
Probably the Florentin is on the
Because of the Scheldt disappeared.
Simon Carrera
the theft organized.
Together with the
former soldiers Frank Scylla.
From him we have found blood.
See Carrera and Frank Scylla,
At the two closely.
Am I your photo
place in the middle of it?
This has the police on
boat found.
You have him complete the
Security plans handed.
And this shall have no meaning?
Did I say that this is not
Has meaning? Did I say that?
Calm down please, Julia.
He did not need the plans. he
just needed access to my room,
to get to the safe.
Was not too hard in your
Rooms come, that's for sure.
-- Hard to believe.
-- I have to ask though.
Make it clear to her that she in
Be reckoned with even more prison
than just sarcasm!
We witness a lot of witnesses.
Here, for example, by
a certain Michael Wurst.
He has underestimated its statement
written and is ready to swear
that he Neuville Julia and Simon Carrera
in the bar Le Vintage
has seen on 14 April.
And then, even in their private suite
at the Grand Hotel on the seventh May
Three days before the
Exhibition of diamonds.
And saw in his view,
not straight from work.
I know that with
this guy were in bed.
Is there more things, in which
You're stuck with it under a blanket?
Do not move!
On your knees!
Is he with you?
Answer me!
Scylla. I want to know where he is.
Scylla is dead.
What are you talking about?
He lives. what about me
was supposed to be dead.
Your little dispute, your return
to Paris, all just a false match.
-- What are you talking about? Have ..
-- Do not fuck with me!
Tell me what you're up.
I do not know.
I know nothing about it, Simon.
That is the truth.
We can no longer
keep in police custody.
Read your statement, which must
You sign before you go.
You can return to the hotel, but
You can not leave the country.
Please, go back.
Let us through.
First, I want all employees
and customers of the house Galley say
Julia Neuville of all
their functions was delivered.
And irrevocable.
Tell me everything,
what you know about Scylla.
Before this job, when did
you see him last time?
Twelve, thirteen years ago,
he was stationed in Djibouti.
He came for two weeks after
France returns. I was his driver.
What did he do in Djibouti?
He was military attaché at the
Message or something.
French Ambassador, Djibouti.
Chronological list of Ambassadors.
De Mézières, Ambassador 1999th
I know Philippe de Mézières.
He was on the auction.
He is a friend of Julia's father
and he was Ambassador to Djibouti.
You think that's not a coincidence?
Philippe de Mézières
under suspicion of corruption.
He has something to hide.
Death of Giullah, Angolep.
The commercial agent was
found dead in his car.
Circumstances unclear.
Car from the inside
closed, circumstances unclear.
Diagnosed coroner
Overdose of his medication.
Ambassador Philippe de Mézières
escapes assassination.
Thank You.
Meet in front of the hotel.
De Mézières behind Scylla.
And so it looks like a quarrel,
they all are slaughtered and
then disappeared with the diamonds.
-- I know you.
-- I am a friend of Simon.
Scylla was going to kill him, as the
else, but he managed to escape.
Wait.
Simon has a lot of chances,
when he came back here,
just to give you these documents
to give you the relief.
-- The he can give the police.
-- You need to decide
when you hold them in your hand.
The photograph is a
small part of the truth.
Did you see the picture?
Did you amused yourself well?
It was too easy. I was still
rumzukriegen easier than you thought.
What happened between us,
Julia had nothing to do with it.
Do you know what hurts the most?
That you my mother
have used, even though she's dead.
Not even you've respected.
Did you like
an asshole listed.
-- I'm like you, I've lost everything.
-- You're not like me!
You'll never be like me!
Julia. I will help you.
I've brought you documents with
which you can prove the truth.
-- Why should I view it?
-- Because you concerns directly.
Listen to me, what I have to tell you.
Then I'll take you to the hotel
back and you never hear from me again.
Why should I listen to you?
What can you tell me?
More lies?
Can you even three sets of
give you without lying? Three words?
Only three words without
to lie, can you?
You show up here on easy and I
to listen to your stories.
You used me.
Yes, I have used you. but what
happened, happened. It's over.
It's over?
That's all? No regrets,
Nothing? Simply, it's over.
Why are you here, if I do not even
can explain what I have to tell you?
I wanted to see you in the eye,
before you walk in the slammer!
Will you let me be arrested?
-- Come on, I'm here.
Take me behind bars! -- Yes!
-- That you want?
-- That's what I want!
So go ahead, to call.
Call! What is?
Are you scared?
How could I be so blind?
How could I trust you only?
Because of you have
humiliated me.
Do what you want.
I will never forgive you.
Damn, I need it to you
because rub their nose?
Listen, the Ambassador de Mézières
escaped yesterday just an assassination attempt.
Rather a settlement under
Gangsters as a political act.
-- Was that the reaction to the death of
Monsieur Giullah ... -- I do not listen.
... who was found dead in his car?
Do you understand, dead in his
Car under mysterious circumstances!
The doors were locked from the inside.
Cause of death:a
Overdose of his medication.
That's impossible.
That can not be.
Are you saying that
have killed my mother?
You have killed her,
and you did not know it?
-- No, I did not know.
-- You lie, you bastard!
-- You did it!
-- Stop it, calm down!
Stop it!
There's something Julia. Scylla
had a mole at the auction ...
... access to documents
had the security company.
Do you understand what that means?
No, I do not understand.
Someone who knew de Mézières ...
... the galley knew ...
... of your mother knew.
Someone you know.
No, I can not.
Only you can figure it out.
I do not have the strength.
What are you doing here?
I smoke again. So what?
What's this?
De Mézières with Frank Scylla.
De Mézières is your closest friend.
Did you know that he is suspicious, jeman--
to have murdered, who stood in his way?
The autopsy revealed that the victim
died from an overdose of a drug.
That was never proven.
She knew it, right?
Mama?
You knew that you give them the
Security concept handed had.
You told them,
that she is diabetic.
So it her death as a
Could make it look accident.
How can you believe such a thing?
I'm calling the police.
Then you can tell them everything.
Do not call the police.
I'll tell you everything I know
but I beg you, no police.
I would
Prison not survive.
I did not believe it.
You killed them.
No! That's not true!
When your mother's plans
had discovered, I was scared.
I talked to Philippe, and
He said I'll take care of it.
I was relieved. I thought he would
already find a solution to anything.
And then Scylla killed her.
He killed her.
But I did not want.
I swear,
I did not want.
Julia, we must do so,
like you know nothing about it.
If they find out that I with
have spoken to you, I'm dead.
Sit down.
No one will hurt you.
You just have us all
tell me what you know.
Are we clear?
The exchange is tomorrow
held in Luxembourg.
I do not know where I should at
Jacob Sturm wait with the expert.
It will examine whether the
Diamond is real.
The buyer will then pick me up.
Do you know the buyers?
Yes, he is a Russian,
Alexander Grenienko.
I've seen it in the gem market
introduced. He wants me to go with him.
And Scylla and de Mézières
bring the diamonds?
Yes, they are already there, but I
do not know exactly what they're up to.
I swear, the
is all I know.
The expert! Who is the expert?
Eleonore Gretel, a Dutch woman.
Scylla and de Mézières,
know it?
No.
You will call them and cancel it.
-- Hello.
-- Hello, Julia.
Come, come to my office.
I need your expertise.
-- Here you go.
-- Thank You.
Look at him.
You see, I have to support something
increased in order to hide the copy.
You have to copy the original
exchange. And since it gets tricky.
Look through.
It has to be fast. It must be so off
see, as if you position the stone.
So, try it.
You will not make it.
I can not make it.
Try it.
Please pass good care of yourself.
LUXEMBOURG
-- Hello, Alexander.
-- Hey.
-- May I introduce the
Eleanor is Gretel. -- Hello.
Hello.
A bench. You want to exchange
make in a bank. Unbelievable.
The Russian has the money safely
deposited in a locker.
If all goes well,
leave them as the diamond.
They go with anything purely
and come out with nothing.
Are you going to visit to see?
Good day.
This way.
Sit down there.
-- Monsieur Grenienko.
-- Hello, Philippe.
-- Hello.
-- Are you sure?
-- A fake.
A beautiful fake.
But made of zirconium.
-- What did you say?
-- He is the original.
Is there any doubt?
I'm 100 percent sure.
I have this thing since
Evening not lost sight of.
I'm just telling you what I see.
You can open. We are done.
Monsieur Grenienko, wait ...
I do not know what happened.
Bring back the money to the
Locker and let them out.
That's incredible.
Unbelievable.
Julia has issued a fake.
-- And did not you know?
-- If I had known it,
do you think I would have said nothing?
Can I have one? I have
My Hotel forgotten.
Yes, Philippe, I smoke again
after 30 years, even though Julia ...
Julia.
Is he in there?
Stop it!
You can not help it.
I have everything organized.
I will give you the diamond.
I'll give it to you.
Here.
Julia is in trouble!
I beg you.
Attempt to get out.
Running, Julia! Hurry up! Go!
Listen, we need to disappear.
Here everywhere bulls will be equal.
Come here!
Let her go!
Hands on your head!
Stand up! Stand up!
Police! Drop the gun!
-- Come on, on the floor!
-- On the floor!
-- Get down on the floor!
Do not move!
This afternoon were
the diamond robbers sentenced.
The jury followed this
applications submitted to the prosecutor's office.
the former
Ambassador Philippe de Mézières
was partly due to the
Establishing a criminal organization
sentenced to 15 years in prison.
Frank Scylla and Omar Rayes were
sentenced to life imprisonment.
Surprising was the
Appeal from Simon Carrera,
Thanks to the moving
Testimony of Julia Neuville
only two years
Has to serve detention.
We turn to
our local correspondents.
Eat!
TWO YEARS LATER
-- So you look like a cop.
-- You got a problem with that?
What's up?
Nothing, absolutely nothing.
That's okay, Albert.
Tell me what's going on.
Thee is anyway
no matter what is going on with me.
Albert, I know you.
Well, tell me.
I have a coup.
-- You're kidding me.
-- A brilliant coup.
But we need to do quickly.
Damn, Simon, I
soon have no more coal.
I'll be dead.
You make me mad!
Stop the car! Let me out!
It's about 30 grand, Simon. the Tip
comes from a reliable types.
Oh, excuse me.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I did yesterday night
bit celebrated too much, you know?
I wanted to go to bathroom, open
the door bin, but ended up in the hallway.
And the door is easy
closed behind me.
-- Which room?
-- 643rd