Xem Phim Online HD Nhanh Nhất Tại VIPHD.VN
Thebes, City of the Living...
crown jewel
of Pharaoh Seti the First...
home of lmhotep,
Pharaoh's high priest...
keeper of the dead...
home of lmhotep,
Pharaoh's high priest...
keeper of the dead...
birthplace of Anck-su-namun,
Pharaoh's mistress.
No other man
was allowed to touch her.
birthplace of Anck-su-namun,
Pharaoh's mistress.
No other man
was allowed to touch her.
But for their love,
they were willing to risk life itself.
To resurrect Anck-su-namun...
lmhotep and his priests
broke into her crypt and stole her body.
They raced deep into the desert...
lmhotep and his priests
broke into her crypt and stole her body.
They raced deep into the desert...
taking Anck-su-namun's corpse
to Hamunaptra, City of the Dead...
ancient burial site
for the sons of pharaohs...
and resting place
for the wealth of Egypt.
ancient burial site
for the sons of pharaohs...
and resting place
for the wealth of Egypt.
For his love, lmhotep dared the gods'
anger by going deep into the city...
where he took the black Book of the Dead
from its holy resting place.
For his love, lmhotep dared the gods'
anger by going deep into the city...
where he took the black Book of the Dead
from its holy resting place.
Anck-su-namun's soul had been sent
to the dark underworld...
her vital organs removed and placed
in five sacred canopic jars.
Anck-su-namun's soul
had come back from the dead.
But Pharaoh's bodyguards
had followed lmhotep and stopped him...
before the ritual
could be completed.
lmhotep's priests were condemned
to be mummified alive.
As for lmhotep...
he was condemned to endure
the Hom-Dai...
the worst
of all ancient curses...
one so horrible
it had never before been bestowed.
He was to remain sealed
inside his sarcophagus--
the undead
for all of eternity.
He was to remain sealed
inside his sarcophagus--
the undead
for all of eternity.
The Magi would never
allow him to be released...
for he would arise a walking disease,
a plague upon mankind...
an unholy flesh eater
with the strength of ages...
for he would arise a walking disease,
a plague upon mankind...
an unholy flesh eater
with the strength of ages...
power over the sands...
an unholy flesh eater
with the strength of ages...
power over the sands...
and the glory
of invincibility.
power over the sands...
and the glory
of invincibility.
For 3,000 years,
men and armies fought over this land...
never knowing
what evil lay beneath it.
For 3,000 years,
men and armies fought over this land...
never knowing
what evil lay beneath it.
And for 3,000 years...
we, the Magi, the descendants of
Pharaoh's sacred bodyguards, kept watch.
And for 3,000 years...
we, the Magi, the descendants of
Pharaoh's sacred bodyguards, kept watch.
You just got promoted.
Prenez vos positions!
Steady!
You're with me
on this one, right?
Oh. Your strength
gives me strength.
Steady!
Wait! Wait for me!
Fire!
Run, Beni! Run!
Get inside!
Hey! Don't you close that door!
Don't you close that door!
''Sacred Stones.''
''Sculpture and Aesthetics.''
Socrates, Seth,
volume one, volume two...
and volume three.
Socrates, Seth,
volume one, volume two...
and volume three.
And T--
Tuthmosis?
What are you doing here?
''T.''
''T,'' ''T,'' ''T,'' ''T.''
Tuthmosis?
What are you doing here?
''T.''
''T,'' ''T,'' ''T,'' ''T.''
l'm going
to put you where you belong.
Help. Ooh.
Whoa!
Oops.
What--
How c-- l--
H-How--
Oh, look at this!
Sons of the pharaohs!
Give me frogs!
Flies! Locusts!
Anything but you!
Give me frogs!
Flies! Locusts!
Anything but you!
Compared to you,
the other plagues were a joy!
l am so very sorry.
lt was an accident.
My girl, when Rameses destroyed Syria,
that was an accident.
You...
are a catastrophe!
My girl, when Rameses destroyed Syria,
that was an accident.
You...
are a catastrophe!
Look at my library!
Why do l put up with you?
W-Well, you put up with me
because l can--
l can read and write
ancient Egyptian...
W-Well, you put up with me
because l can--
l can read and write
ancient Egyptian...
and l can-- l can decipher
hieroglyphics and hieratic...
and, w-well, l am the only person
within a thousand miles...
and l can-- l can decipher
hieroglyphics and hieratic...
and, w-well, l am the only person
within a thousand miles...
who knows how to properly code
and catalog this library, that's why.
and, w-well, l am the only person
within a thousand miles...
who knows how to properly code
and catalog this library, that's why.
l put up with you because your father
and mother were our finest patrons.
That's why!
l put up with you because your father
and mother were our finest patrons.
That's why!
Allah rest their souls.
Now, l don't care how you do it,
l don't care how long it takes.
Straighten up
this meshiver!
Now, l don't care how you do it,
l don't care how long it takes.
Straighten up
this meshiver!
Hello?
Abdul?
Mohammed?
Bob?
Have you no respect
for the dead?
Of course l do!
But sometimes
l'd rather like to join them.
Of course l do!
But sometimes
l'd rather like to join them.
Well, l wish you would do it
before you ruin my career
the way you've ruined yours.
Now get out!
Well, l wish you would do it
before you ruin my career
the way you've ruined yours.
Now get out!
My dear, sweet
baby sister...
l'll have you... know...
that at this precise moment
my career is on a high note.
''High note.'' Ha! Jonathan, please,
l'm really not in the mood for you.
that at this precise moment
my career is on a high note.
''High note.'' Ha! Jonathan, please,
l'm really not in the mood for you.
l've just made a bit of a mess
in the library...
''High note.'' Ha! Jonathan, please,
l'm really not in the mood for you.
l've just made a bit of a mess
in the library...
and the Bembridge scholars have
rejected my application form again.
They say l don't have
enough experience in the field.
You'll always have me,
old mum.
Besides, l have just the thing
to cheer you up.
Oh, no, Jonathan,
not another worthless trinket.
lf l have to take one more piece
of junk to the curator to try and...
sell for you--
lf l have to take one more piece
of junk to the curator to try and...
sell for you--
Where did you get this?
On a dig down in Thebes.
My whole life l've never
found anything, Evy.
On a dig down in Thebes.
My whole life l've never
found anything, Evy.
Please tell me
l've found something.
Jonathan.
Yes?
l think you've found something.
You see the cartouche there.
lt's the official royal seal
of Seti the First, l'm sure of it.
- Perhaps.
- Two questions.
Who the hell was Seti the First,
and was he rich?
He was the second pharaoh
of the 19th dynasty...
said to be the wealthiest pharaoh
of them all.
He was the second pharaoh
of the 19th dynasty...
said to be the wealthiest pharaoh
of them all.
Good. l like this fellow.
- l like him very much.
- l've already dated the map.
lt's almost 3,000 years old.
And if you look at
the hieratic just here...
well, it's Hamunaptra.
Dear God,
don't be ridiculous.
We're scholars,
not treasure hunters.
Dear God,
don't be ridiculous.
We're scholars,
not treasure hunters.
Hamunaptra's a myth
told by ancient Arab storytellers...
to amuse Greek
and Roman tourists.
l know all the blather
about the city being protected
by the curse of a mummy...
but my research
has led me to believe...
that the city itself
may have actually existed.
Are we talking about
the Hamunaptra?
that the city itself
may have actually existed.
Are we talking about
the Hamunaptra?
Yes. The City of the Dead.
Are we talking about
the Hamunaptra?
Yes. The City of the Dead.
Where the earliest pharaohs were said
to have hidden the wealth of Egypt.
Yes. The City of the Dead.
Where the earliest pharaohs were said
to have hidden the wealth of Egypt.
Yes, yes, i-i-in a big,
underground treasure chamber.
- Heh!
- Oh, come on.
Everybody knows the story.
Yes, yes, i-i-in a big,
underground treasure chamber.
- Heh!
- Oh, come on.
Everybody knows the story.
The entire necropolis was rigged to sink
into the sand on Pharaoh's command.
The place would disappear beneath the
sand dunes, taking the treasure with it.
The entire necropolis was rigged to sink
into the sand on Pharaoh's command.
The place would disappear beneath the
sand dunes, taking the treasure with it.
As the Americans would say,
it's all fairy tales and hokum--
The place would disappear beneath the
sand dunes, taking the treasure with it.
As the Americans would say,
it's all fairy tales and hokum--
Oh, my goodness!
Look at that!
You've burnt it! You've burned off
the part with the lost city.
lt's for the best,
l'm sure.
Many men
have wasted their lives...
in the foolish pursuit
of Hamunaptra.
No one's ever found it.
Most...
have never returned.
Come, come!
Step over the threshold.
Welcome to Cairo Prison,
my humble home.
You told me that you got it
on a dig down in Thebes.
- Well, l was mistaken.
- You lied.
You told me that you got it
on a dig down in Thebes.
- Well, l was mistaken.
- You lied.
l lie to everybody.
What makes you so special?
- l am your sister.
- That just makes you more gullible.
- You stole it from a drunk
at the local casbah.
- Picked his pocket, actually.
- So l don't think it's a very good--
- Stop being so ridiculous.
- You stole it from a drunk
at the local casbah.
- Picked his pocket, actually.
- So l don't think it's a very good--
- Stop being so ridiculous.
-What exactly is this man in prison for?
-This l do not know.
- So l don't think it's a very good--
- Stop being so ridiculous.
-What exactly is this man in prison for?
-This l do not know.
But when l heard that you were coming,
l asked him that myself.
-What exactly is this man in prison for?
-This l do not know.
But when l heard that you were coming,
l asked him that myself.
And what did he say?
He said he was just looking
for a good time.
-This is the man that you stole it from?
-Yes, exactly.
- So why don't we just go
sniff out a spot of tiffin--
- Who are you?
-This is the man that you stole it from?
-Yes, exactly.
- So why don't we just go
sniff out a spot of tiffin--
- Who are you?
- And who's the broad?
- ''Broad''?
l-l'm just a local sort of missionary
chap, spreading the good word.
- But this is my sister Evy.
- How do you do?
- Oh, well.
Guess she's not a total loss.
- l beg your pardon.
- But this is my sister Evy.
- How do you do?
- Oh, well.
Guess she's not a total loss.
- l beg your pardon.
l'll be back in a moment.
Ask him about the box.
Um, we have found--
Uh, hello. Excuse me.
Ask him about the box.
Um, we have found--
Uh, hello. Excuse me.
We both found
your puzzle box...
Um, we have found--
Uh, hello. Excuse me.
We both found
your puzzle box...
and we've come
to ask you about it.
- No.
No. You came to ask me
about Hamunaptra.
- Shh. Shh.
- H-How do you know the box
pertains to Hamunaptra?
No. You came to ask me
about Hamunaptra.
- Shh. Shh.
- H-How do you know the box
pertains to Hamunaptra?
Because that's where l was
when l found it. l was there.
- Shh. Shh.
- H-How do you know the box
pertains to Hamunaptra?
Because that's where l was
when l found it. l was there.
But how do we know
that's not a load of pig's wallow?
Because that's where l was
when l found it. l was there.
But how do we know
that's not a load of pig's wallow?
Do l know you?
But how do we know
that's not a load of pig's wallow?
Do l know you?
No, no. l've just got
one of those faces.
You were actually at Hamunaptra?
Yeah, l was there.
- You swear?
- Every damn day.
- l didn't mean that--
- l know. l was there.
Seti's place.
City of the Dead.
Could you tell me how to get there?
l mean, the exact location.
- You want to know?
- W-Well, yes.
l mean, the exact location.
- You want to know?
- W-Well, yes.
- Do you really want to know?
- Yes.
- You want to know?
- W-Well, yes.
- Do you really want to know?
- Yes.
Then get me
the hell out of here!
Do it, lady!
Where are they taking him?
To be hanged.
Apparently he had
a very good time.
l will give you 100 pounds
to save this man's life.
Madame, l would pay 100 pounds
just to see him hang.
l will give you 100 pounds
to save this man's life.
Madame, l would pay 100 pounds
just to see him hang.
- Two hundred pounds!
- Proceed!
Three hundred pounds!
Any last requests, pig?
Yeah. Loosen the knot
and let me go.
Yahemar!
Of course we don't let him go!
Five hundred pounds!
And what else?
l'm a very lonely man.
- Yalla tlak!
- No!
Ha ha!
His neck did not break!
Oh, l'm so sorry. Now we must
watch him strangle to death.
He knows the location
to Hamunaptra.
- You lie.
- l would never!
Are you telling me this filthy,
godless son of a pig knows where
to find the City of the Dead?
- Yes!
- Truly?
Are you telling me this filthy,
godless son of a pig knows where
to find the City of the Dead?
- Yes!
- Truly?
Yes! And if you cut him down,
we will give you--
- Ten percent.
- Fifty percent.
- Twenty.
- Forty.
- Thirty!
- Twenty-five.
Ah! Deal.
Ahh! Cut him down!
Do you really think
he's going to show up?
Yes, undoubtedly,
knowing my luck.
Do you really think
he's going to show up?
Yes, undoubtedly,
knowing my luck.
He may be a cowboy, but l know
the breed. His word is his word.
Well, personally l think he's filthy,
rude, a complete scoundrel.
He may be a cowboy, but l know
the breed. His word is his word.
Well, personally l think he's filthy,
rude, a complete scoundrel.
- l don't like him one bit.
- Anyone l know?
Well, personally l think he's filthy,
rude, a complete scoundrel.
- l don't like him one bit.
- Anyone l know?
Um, hello.
Smashing day for the start
of an adventure, eh, O'Connell?
Um, hello.
Smashing day for the start
of an adventure, eh, O'Connell?
Yeah. Yeah, smashing.
Smashing day for the start
of an adventure, eh, O'Connell?
Yeah. Yeah, smashing.
Oh, no, no, l'd never steal
from a partner... partner.
That reminds me.
No hard feelings about the--
- Oh, no, no. Happens all the time.
- Mr. O'Connell.
That reminds me.
No hard feelings about the--
- Oh, no, no. Happens all the time.
- Mr. O'Connell.
Can you look me in the eye and guarantee
me this isn't some kind of a flimflam?
- Because if it is, l am warning you--
- You're warning me?
Can you look me in the eye and guarantee
me this isn't some kind of a flimflam?
- Because if it is, l am warning you--
- You're warning me?
Lady, let me put it this way:
My whole damn garrison
believed in this so much...
- Because if it is, l am warning you--
- You're warning me?
Lady, let me put it this way:
My whole damn garrison
believed in this so much...
that without orders,
they marched halfway across Libya
and into Egypt to find that city.
When we got there,
all we found...
that without orders,
they marched halfway across Libya
and into Egypt to find that city.
When we got there,
all we found...
was sand and blood.
Let me get your bags.
Yes, yes, you're right.
Filthy, rude, a complete scoundrel.
Nothing to like there at all.
Bright good morning to all.
Oh, no.
What are you doing here?
l'm here to protect my investment,
thank you very much.
Quit playin' with
your glasses and cut the deck, Burns.
Without my glasses
l can't see the deck to cut it, Dave.
O'Connell, sit down.
We could use another player.
- l only gamble with
my life, never my money.
- Never?
O'Connell, sit down.
We could use another player.
- l only gamble with
my life, never my money.
- Never?
What if l was to bet you $500
we get to Hamunaptra before you?
- You're looking for Hamunaptra?
- Damn straight we are.
- And who says we are?
- He does.
- You're looking for Hamunaptra?
- Damn straight we are.
- And who says we are?
- He does.
- Well--
- Well, how 'bout it?
ls it a bet?
- Well--
- Well, how 'bout it?
ls it a bet?
- All right, you're on.
- What makes you so confident, sir?
- What makes you?
- We got us a man
who's actually been there.
- All right, you're on.
- What makes you so confident, sir?
- What makes you?
- We got us a man
who's actually been there.
Oh, what a coincidence,
because O'Connell--
- What makes you?
- We got us a man
who's actually been there.
Oh, what a coincidence,
because O'Connell--
Whose play is it?
Oh, what a coincidence,
because O'Connell--
Whose play is it?
ls it-- ls it my play?
l thought--
Whose play is it?
ls it-- ls it my play?
l thought--
Gentlemen, we got us a wager.
Good evening, Jonathan.
Good night.
Sorry.
Didn't mean to scare ya.
The only thing that scares me,
Mr. O'Connell, are your manners.
Still angry about that kiss, huh?
Well, if you call that a kiss.
Um, did l miss something?
Are we--
Are we going into battle?
Lady, there's something
out there.
Are we--
Are we going into battle?
Lady, there's something
out there.
Something underneath that sand.
Yes, well, l'm hoping to find
a certain artifact.
A book, actually.
Yes, well, l'm hoping to find
a certain artifact.
A book, actually.
My brother
thinks there's treasure.
- What do you think's out there?
- ln a word? Evil.
The Bedouin and the Tuaregs
believe that Hamunaptra is cursed.
- What do you think's out there?
- ln a word? Evil.
The Bedouin and the Tuaregs
believe that Hamunaptra is cursed.
Oh, look, l don't believe in fairy tales
and hokum, Mr. O'Connell...
but l do believe one of the most famous
books in history is buried there.
Oh, look, l don't believe in fairy tales
and hokum, Mr. O'Connell...
but l do believe one of the most famous
books in history is buried there.
The Book of Amun-Ra.
lt contains within it all the secret
incantations of the old kingdom.
lt's what first interested me in Egypt
when l was a child.
lt contains within it all the secret
incantations of the old kingdom.
lt's what first interested me in Egypt
when l was a child.
lt's why l came here--
sort of a life's pursuit.
lt's what first interested me in Egypt
when l was a child.
lt's why l came here--
sort of a life's pursuit.
And the fact that they say it's made out
of pure gold makes no never mind to you?
- Right?
- You know your history.
And the fact that they say it's made out
of pure gold makes no never mind to you?
- Right?
- You know your history.
l know my treasure.
Um... by the way...
why did you kiss me?
l was about to be hanged.
lt seemed like a good idea at the time.
why did you kiss me?
l was about to be hanged.
lt seemed like a good idea at the time.
What?
What'd l say?
Surprise!
My good friend,
you're alive!
l was so very,
very worried.
Well, if it ain't
my little buddy Beni.
l was so very,
very worried.
Well, if it ain't
my little buddy Beni.
- l think l'll kill you.
- Think of my children.
Well, if it ain't
my little buddy Beni.
- l think l'll kill you.
- Think of my children.
You don't have any children.
- l think l'll kill you.
- Think of my children.
You don't have any children.
- Someday l might.
- Shut up!
So you're the one who's leading
the Americans. l might have known.
What's the scam? You take them into the
desert, and then you leave 'em to rot?
So you're the one who's leading
the Americans. l might have known.
What's the scam? You take them into the
desert, and then you leave 'em to rot?
Unfortunately, no.
These Americans are smart.
They pay me only half now,
half when l get them back to Cairo.
- So this time l must go all the way.
- Them's the breaks, huh?
They pay me only half now,
half when l get them back to Cairo.
- So this time l must go all the way.
- Them's the breaks, huh?
You never believed
in Hamunaptra, O'Connell.
Why are you going back?
You never believed
in Hamunaptra, O'Connell.
Why are you going back?
You see that girl?
She saved my neck.
You always did have
more balls than brains.
Yeah.
Good-bye, Beni.
O'Connell!
''George Bembridge...
in eighteen-sixty--''
Hmm. ''1865 was--
was--''
Oh, for heaven's sake, girl,
it wasn't that good of a kiss, anyway.
was--''
Oh, for heaven's sake, girl,
it wasn't that good of a kiss, anyway.
Where is the map?
lt's--
lt's... there.
Where is the map?
lt's--
lt's... there.
And the key?
Where is the key?
The key? The key?
What key?
Evelyn!
The map!
The map! l forgot the map!
Relax. l'm the map.
lt's all up here.
Oh, that's comforting.
- The key!
- Evy?
Hold on to this.
Can you swim?
- Of course l can swim,
if the occasion calls for it.
- Trust me.
Can you swim?
- Of course l can swim,
if the occasion calls for it.
- Trust me.
lt calls for it.
O'Connell! O'Connell!
What are we going to do?
- Wait here! l'll go get help!
- Right!
What are we going to do?
- Wait here! l'll go get help!
- Right!
Americans.
l say, bloody good show, chaps!
And did l panic?
l think not.
Get out of here!
Get 'em out of the water!
Come on, dogies!
Give 'em a smack, would ya!
This is a messed-up country.
We've lost everything!
All of our tools,
all the equipment!
All my clothes!
All of our tools,
all the equipment!
All my clothes!
O'Connell!
Hey!
lt looks to me
like l've got all the horses!
Hey, Beni!
lt looks to me
like l've got all the horses!
Hey, Beni!
Looks to me like you're on
the wrong side of the river!
Yeah.
Looks to me like you're on
the wrong side of the river!
Yeah.
l only want four! Four!
l only want four,
not a whole bloody herd!
l only want four! Four!
l only want four,
not a whole bloody herd!
O'Connell! Ohh!
Can you believe the cheek?
l only want four,
not a whole bloody herd!
O'Connell! Ohh!
Can you believe the cheek?
Just pay the man.
O'Connell! Ohh!
Can you believe the cheek?
Just pay the man.
Oh, for heaven's sake.
Can't believe the price
of these fleabags.
Oh, for heaven's sake.
Can't believe the price
of these fleabags.
Yes, happy.
Very good.
You probably could've
got 'em for free.
Yes, happy.
Very good.
You probably could've
got 'em for free.
- All you had to do
was give him your sister.
- Yes.
Awfully tempting, wasn't it?
- All you had to do
was give him your sister.
- Yes.
Awfully tempting, wasn't it?
Awfully.
Never did like camels.
Filthy buggers.
They smell, they bite, they spit.
Disgusting.
l think they're adorable.
Oh, baby.
Good morning, my friend.
What the hell we doin'?
Patience, my good barat'm.
Patience.
What the hell we doin'?
Patience, my good barat'm.
Patience.
Remember our bet, O'Connell.
First one to the city, 500 cash bucks.
A hundred of them bucks is yours
if you help us win that bet.
Remember our bet, O'Connell.
First one to the city, 500 cash bucks.
A hundred of them bucks is yours
if you help us win that bet.
Oh, my pleasure.
A hundred of them bucks is yours
if you help us win that bet.
Oh, my pleasure.
Hey, O'Connell.
Nice camel.
Get ready for it.
For what?
We're about to be shown the way.
Will ya look at that.
Can you believe it?
Hamunaptra.
Here we go again.
Oww!
So long, Beni!
That serves you right.
Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
Go, Evy! Go!
Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
Go, Evy! Go!
Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
Do they know somethin'
we don't?
They are led by a woman.
What does a woman know?
That's a statue of Anubis.
lts legs go deep underground.
According to Bembridge scholars,
that's where we'll find
a secret compartment...
lts legs go deep underground.
According to Bembridge scholars,
that's where we'll find
a secret compartment...
containing the golden
Book of Amun-Ra.
Jonathan, you're meant
to catch the sun with that.
So, uh, what are
these old mirrors for?
Ancient mirrors. lt's an ancient
Egyptian trick. You'll see.
Uh, here, this is for, uh, you.
Go ahead. lt's something
l borrowed off our American brethren.
l thought you might like it--
you might need it
for when you're, uh-- uh, yeah.
What are you lookin' at?
you might need it
for when you're, uh-- uh, yeah.
What are you lookin' at?
Hey! Look for bugs.
l hate bugs.
We're standing inside a room
no one has entered in over 3,000 years.
Whoo! What is
that god-awful stench?
We're standing inside a room
no one has entered in over 3,000 years.
Whoo! What is
that god-awful stench?
And then there was...
light.
Hey, that is a neat trick.
- Oh, my God. lt's a sah-netjer.
- Huh?
- A preparation room.
- Preparation for what?
- Oh, my God. lt's a sah-netjer.
- Huh?
- A preparation room.
- Preparation for what?
For entering the afterlife.
Mummies, my good son.
This is where they made the mummies.
For entering the afterlife.
Mummies, my good son.
This is where they made the mummies.
What the--
What was that?
Sounds like... bugs.
He said bugs.
What do you mean, bugs?
l hate bugs.
The legs of Anubis.
The secret compartment
should be hidden somewhere inside here.
The legs of Anubis.
The secret compartment
should be hidden somewhere inside here.
You scared the bejesus
out of us, O'Connell.
Likewise.
- Hey, that's my tool kit.
- l don't think so.
Okay.
Perhaps l was mistaken.
Have a nice day, gentlemen. We have
a lot of work to be getting along with.
Perhaps l was mistaken.
Have a nice day, gentlemen. We have
a lot of work to be getting along with.
- Push off! This is our dig site.
- We got here first.
This here's our statue, friend.
l don't see your name
written on it... pal.
This here's our statue, friend.
l don't see your name
written on it... pal.
Yes, well,
there's only four of you...
l don't see your name
written on it... pal.
Yes, well,
there's only four of you...
and 15 of me.
Your odds are not so great,
O'Connell.
and 15 of me.
Your odds are not so great,
O'Connell.
- l've had worse.
- Yeah, me too.
Your odds are not so great,
O'Connell.
- l've had worse.
- Yeah, me too.
Oh, look, for goodness' sake,
let's be nice, children.
lf we're going to play together,
we must learn to share.
There are other places to dig.
According to these hieroglyphics...
we're underneath the statue.
We should come up
right between his legs.
- When those damn Yanks
go to sleep-- No offense--
- None taken.
we'll dig our way up and steal that book
right out from under them.
- When those damn Yanks
go to sleep-- No offense--
- None taken.
we'll dig our way up and steal that book
right out from under them.
Are you sure we can find
this secret compartment?
we'll dig our way up and steal that book
right out from under them.
Are you sure we can find
this secret compartment?
Oh, yes, if those beastly Americans
haven't beaten us to it.
Are you sure we can find
this secret compartment?
Oh, yes, if those beastly Americans
haven't beaten us to it.
- No offense.
- None taken.
Oh, yes, if those beastly Americans
haven't beaten us to it.
- No offense.
- None taken.
Where'd our smelly
little friend get to?
Hey.
What have we here?
Blue gold.
This will fetch
a mighty fine price.
- Let's get us some treasure!
- Careful!
Seti was no fool.
l think perhaps we should
let the diggers open it, hmm?
Seti was no fool.
l think perhaps we should
let the diggers open it, hmm?
Oh, l think we should listen
to the good doctor, Henderson.
l think perhaps we should
let the diggers open it, hmm?
Oh, l think we should listen
to the good doctor, Henderson.
Yeah, sure.
Let them open it.
Zee-eda.
Let me get this straight.
They ripped out your guts
and stuffed them in jars.
They'd take out your heart as well.
You know how they took out your brains?
l don't think we need
to know this.
They'd take out your heart as well.
You know how they took out your brains?
l don't think we need
to know this.
They'd take a sharp, red-hot poker,
stick it up your nose...
scramble things about a bit and then
rip it all out through your nostrils.
They'd take a sharp, red-hot poker,
stick it up your nose...
scramble things about a bit and then
rip it all out through your nostrils.
That's gotta hurt.
lt's called mummification.
You'll be dead when they do this.
lf l don't make it out of here,
don't put me down for mummification.
lt's called mummification.
You'll be dead when they do this.
lf l don't make it out of here,
don't put me down for mummification.
Likewise.
lf l don't make it out of here,
don't put me down for mummification.
Likewise.
Oh, my God.
lt's a--
lt's a sarcophagus.
Buried at the base of Anubis.
He must have been someone
of great importance.
Or he did something very naughty.
He must have been someone
of great importance.
Or he did something very naughty.
Oh, Allah.
One more.
Help me! Help me!
Well, who is it?
''He That Shall Not Be Named.''
This looks like
some sort of a lock.
- Well, whoever's in here
sure wasn't getting out.
- Yeah, no kidding.
lt'd take us a month
to crack into this thing without a key.
- Well, whoever's in here
sure wasn't getting out.
- Yeah, no kidding.
lt'd take us a month
to crack into this thing without a key.
A key?
A key! A key!
That's what he was talking about!
A key?
A key! A key!
That's what he was talking about!
- Who?
- The man on the barge.
A key! A key!
That's what he was talking about!
- Who?
- The man on the barge.
The one with the hook.
He was looking for a key.
Hey, that's mine.
- What do you suppose killed him?
- Did you ever see him eat?
Seems that our American friends had
a little misfortune of their own today.
- What do you suppose killed him?
- Did you ever see him eat?
Seems that our American friends had
a little misfortune of their own today.
Three of their diggers
were, uh... melted.
- What?
- How?
Three of their diggers
were, uh... melted.
- What?
- How?
Salt acid.
Pressurized salt acid.
Some kind of
ancient booby trap.
Maybe this place really is cursed.
Some kind of
ancient booby trap.
Maybe this place really is cursed.
Oh, for goodness' sake, you two!
- You don't believe in curses?
- No, l don't.
l believe if l can see it
and l can touch it, it's real.
That's what l believe.
l believe in being prepared.
l believe if l can see it
and l can touch it, it's real.
That's what l believe.
l believe in being prepared.
Let's see what our friend
the warden believed in.
My God, what is it?
A broken bottle.
Glenlivet. Twelve years old!
He may have been a stinky fellow,
but he had good taste.
Glenlivet. Twelve years old!
He may have been a stinky fellow,
but he had good taste.
Take this. Stay here.
- No, wait, wait! Wait for me. Wait!
- Evy!
Excuse me, but didn't the man
just say ''stay here''? Evy!
- No, wait, wait! Wait for me. Wait!
- Evy!
Excuse me, but didn't the man
just say ''stay here''? Evy!
Mr. Henderson!
Wake up!
O'Connell!
Enough! Yallah!
We will shed no more blood,
but you must leave.
Leave this place or die.
We will shed no more blood,
but you must leave.
Leave this place or die.
You have one day.
Yallah! Nimshi!
Evelyn.
Hey.
- Are you all right?
- Yes, l'm fine.
- You sure?
- Thank you.
That proves it. Old Seti's
fortune's got to be under this sand.
For them to protect it like this,
you know there's treasure down there.
That proves it. Old Seti's
fortune's got to be under this sand.
For them to protect it like this,
you know there's treasure down there.
No, these men are desert people.
They value water, not gold.
You know, maybe just at night,
we could, uh, combine forces, hmm?
No, these men are desert people.
They value water, not gold.
You know, maybe just at night,
we could, uh, combine forces, hmm?
Hey, tough stuff, try a right hook.
You know, maybe just at night,
we could, uh, combine forces, hmm?
Hey, tough stuff, try a right hook.
Ball up your fist and put it--
put it up like that.
- Mm-hmm.
- And then mean it. Hit it right here.
- l mean it!
- Okay.
Okay, it's time
for another drink.
Unlike my brother, sir...
l know when to say no.
And unlike
your brother, miss...
you, l just don't get.
And unlike
your brother, miss...
you, l just don't get.
l know.
You're wondering...
what is a place like me
doing in a girl like this.
Yeah, something like that.
what is a place like me
doing in a girl like this.
Yeah, something like that.
Egypt is in my blood.
You see, my-- my father...
was a very, very
famous explorer...
You see, my-- my father...
was a very, very
famous explorer...
and he loved Egypt
so much...
he married my mother,
who was an Egyptian...
and quite
an adventurer herself.
l get your father,
and l get your mother...
and quite
an adventurer herself.
l get your father,
and l get your mother...
and, uh...
l get your father,
and l get your mother...
and, uh...
l get him, but...
what are you doing here?
Look, l--
l may not be...
an explorer...
or-or an adventurer...
or a treasure seeker
or a gunfighter...
Mr. O'Connell...
but l am proud
of what l am.
Mr. O'Connell...
but l am proud
of what l am.
And what is that?
l...
am a librarian.
And l am going
to kiss you...
Mr. O'Connell.
Call me Rick.
Oh, Rick.
Awam, awam!
Djaceb, djaceb.
- There is a curse upon this chest.
- Curse, my ass.
- Who cares?
- Have a care, Mr. Henderson.
ln these hallowed grounds, that which
was set forth in ancient times...
- is as strong today as it was then.
- We understand.
What's it say?
''Death will come
on swift wings...
to whomsoever
opens this chest.''
We should not be here.
This is not good.
lt says, ''There is one...
the undead...
who, if brought back to life,
is bound by sacred law...
to consummate this curse.''
who, if brought back to life,
is bound by sacred law...
to consummate this curse.''
Let's make sure we don't bring anyone
back from the dead then.
''He will kill all
who open this chest...
and assimilate
their organs and fluids...
and in so doing,
he will regenerate...
and assimilate
their organs and fluids...
and in so doing,
he will regenerate...
and no longer be
the undead...
but a plague
upon this Earth.''
Well, we didn't come
all this way for nothin'.
but a plague
upon this Earth.''
Well, we didn't come
all this way for nothin'.
- That's right.
- lt's the curse.
lt's the curse.
- That's right.
- lt's the curse.
lt's the curse.
lt's the curse!
Beware of the curse!
Beware!
lt's the curse!
Beware of the curse!
Beware!
Stupid superstitious bastard.
Oh, l've dreamt about this
since l was a little girl.
You dream about dead guys?
Oh, l've dreamt about this
since l was a little girl.
You dream about dead guys?
Look, his sacred spells
have been chiseled off.
You dream about dead guys?
Look, his sacred spells
have been chiseled off.
This man must have been condemned
not only in this life but in the next.
Look, his sacred spells
have been chiseled off.
This man must have been condemned
not only in this life but in the next.
- Tough break.
- Yeah, l'm all tears.
This man must have been condemned
not only in this life but in the next.
- Tough break.
- Yeah, l'm all tears.
Now, let's see who's inside, shall we?
Oh, my God, l hate it
when these things do that.
ls he supposed to
look like that?
No, l've never seen a mummy
look like this before.
He's still-- still--
No, l've never seen a mummy
look like this before.
He's still-- still--
- Juicy.
- Yes.
He must be more
than 3,000 years old...
and, well, it looks
as if he's still...
He must be more
than 3,000 years old...
and, well, it looks
as if he's still...
decomposing.
Hey, look at that.
What do you make of this?
My God, these marks
were made with...
fingernails.
This man was buried alive.
And he left a message.
''Death is only the beginning.''
Oh, my God.
lt does exist.
- The Book of the Dead.
- A book?
Who cares about a book?
Where the hell's the treasure?
- The Book of the Dead.
- A book?
Who cares about a book?
Where the hell's the treasure?
This, gentlemen...
this is treasure.
Hell, l wouldn't trade you
for a brass--
Look at that.
There's your treasure, gentlemen.
Now we're onto something.
l believe you need a key
to open that book.
Say, O'Connell, what do you think
these babies'll fetch back home?
We hear you boys found yourselves
a nice, gooey mummy.
Congratulations.
lf you dry that fella out, you might
be able to sell him for firewood.
Congratulations.
lf you dry that fella out, you might
be able to sell him for firewood.
Look what l found.
You're in her seat.
- Now!
- Yup.
Scarab skeletons,
flesh eaters.
l found them inside
our friend's coffin.
Scarab skeletons,
flesh eaters.
l found them inside
our friend's coffin.
They can stay alive for years
feasting on the flesh of a corpse.
l found them inside
our friend's coffin.
They can stay alive for years
feasting on the flesh of a corpse.
Unfortunately for our friend,
he was still alive
when they started eating him.
They can stay alive for years
feasting on the flesh of a corpse.
Unfortunately for our friend,
he was still alive
when they started eating him.
So somebody threw these in with our guy,
and then they slowly ate him alive?
Very slowly.
So somebody threw these in with our guy,
and then they slowly ate him alive?
Very slowly.
He certainly wasn't a popular fellow
when they planted him.
Well, he probably got a little
too frisky with the pharaoh's daughter.
He certainly wasn't a popular fellow
when they planted him.
Well, he probably got a little
too frisky with the pharaoh's daughter.
Well, according
to my readings...
Well, he probably got a little
too frisky with the pharaoh's daughter.
Well, according
to my readings...
our friend suffered the Hom-Dai, the
worst of all ancient Egyptian curses...
one reserved only
for the most evil of blasphemers.
our friend suffered the Hom-Dai, the
worst of all ancient Egyptian curses...
one reserved only
for the most evil of blasphemers.
ln my research, l've never heard of this
curse having actually been performed.
one reserved only
for the most evil of blasphemers.
ln my research, l've never heard of this
curse having actually been performed.
- That bad, huh?
- Yes, well, they--
They never used it
because they feared it so.
lt's written that if a victim
of the Hom-Dai should ever arise...
They never used it
because they feared it so.
lt's written that if a victim
of the Hom-Dai should ever arise...
he would bring with him
the ten plagues of Egypt.
lt's written that if a victim
of the Hom-Dai should ever arise...
he would bring with him
the ten plagues of Egypt.
That's called stealing,
you know.
According to you
and my brother...
That's called stealing,
you know.
According to you
and my brother...
it's called borrowing.
l thought the Book of Amun-Ra
was made out of gold.
lt is made out of gold.
This isn't the Book of Amun-Ra.
l thought the Book of Amun-Ra
was made out of gold.
lt is made out of gold.
This isn't the Book of Amun-Ra.
This is something else.
lt is made out of gold.
This isn't the Book of Amun-Ra.
This is something else.
l think this may be
the Book of the Dead.
The Book of the Dead?
Are you sure you want to
be playing around with this thing?
lt's just a book.
No harm ever came from...
reading a book.
That happens a lot around here.
So, what's it say?
''Amun Ra. Amun Dei.''
lt speaks of the night
and of the day.
''Amun Ra. Amun Dei.''
lt speaks of the night
and of the day.
You must not read from the book!
Run!
Go, go!
What have we done?
Where the hell
did they come from?
What have we done?
Where the hell
did they come from?
l ain't waitin' around to find out.
My glasses. My glasses!
Leave me! Leave me!
Hey! Hey!
Could you help me
find my gl-- Oh.
Wait for me!
Who's there?
Henderson?
Ah, Jon!
Scarabs!
- Run, Evy!
- Go, go, go! Run!
Scarabs!
- Run, Evy!
- Go, go, go! Run!
- Evelyn?
- Evy?
- Evelyn!
- Evy!
Oh. Oh, Mr. Burns.
Thank goodness.
l was just starting
to get scared.
l've lost everyone. l--
My eyes. My eyes.
Please help me.
My tongue. He took my tongue.
Please don't leave me.
Anck-su-namun?
Damn it!
lt's a trap door.
Anck-su-namun?
Damn it!
lt's a trap door.
There's gotta be a switch or something
around here someplace.
Run, you sons of bitches! Run!
Go.
Go! Go!
There you are!
Will you quit playing hide-and-seek?
Come on.
Let's get out of here. Whoa!
There you are!
Will you quit playing hide-and-seek?
Come on.
Let's get out of here. Whoa!
Evy!
- Move!
- Yeah, right. Did you see that?
lt was walking. lt was walking!
l told you to leave or die.
You refused.
Now you may have
killed us all...
l told you to leave or die.
You refused.
Now you may have
killed us all...
for you have unleashed a creature we
have feared for more than 3,000 years.
Now you may have
killed us all...
for you have unleashed a creature we
have feared for more than 3,000 years.
- Relax. l got him.
- No mortal weapon
can kill this creature.
He's not of this world.
- Relax. l got him.
- No mortal weapon
can kill this creature.
He's not of this world.
- You bastards.
- What did you do to him?
We saved him, saved him before
the creature could finish his work.
Leave, all of you, quickly,
before he finishes you all.
Yallah. Nimishi.
Leave, all of you, quickly,
before he finishes you all.
Yallah. Nimishi.
We must now go on the hunt
and try and find a way to kill him.
l already told you l got him.
We must now go on the hunt
and try and find a way to kill him.
l already told you l got him.
Know this.
This creature
is the bringer of death.
He will never eat,
he will never sleep...
This creature
is the bringer of death.
He will never eat,
he will never sleep...
and he will never stop.
He will never eat,
he will never sleep...
and he will never stop.
May the good Lord protect
and watch over me...
as a shepherd
watches over his flock.
No? Okay.
My prince.
l thought you said you didn't believe in
that fairy tales and hokum stuff. Shoo!
H-Having an encounter
with a 3,000-year-old
walking, talking corpse...
does tend to convert one.
H-Having an encounter
with a 3,000-year-old
walking, talking corpse...
does tend to convert one.
Forget it. We're out the door,
down the hall and we're gone.
- Oh, no, we are not.
- Oh, yes, we are.
Oh, no, we are not. We woke him up,
and we are going to stop him.
- Oh, no, we are not.
- Oh, yes, we are.
Oh, no, we are not. We woke him up,
and we are going to stop him.
''We''? What we?
We didn't read that book.
Oh, no, we are not. We woke him up,
and we are going to stop him.
''We''? What we?
We didn't read that book.
l told you not to play around
with that thing. Didn't l tell you?
Yes, then me, me, me, me, l, l,
l woke him up and l intend to stop him.
Yeah? How? You heard the man--
no mortal weapons can kill this guy.
Yes, then me, me, me, me, l, l,
l woke him up and l intend to stop him.
Yeah? How? You heard the man--
no mortal weapons can kill this guy.
Then we are just going to
have to find some immortal ones.
Yeah? How? You heard the man--
no mortal weapons can kill this guy.
Then we are just going to
have to find some immortal ones.
- There goes that ''we'' again.
- Will you listen to me? We have to do--
Once this creature has been reborn...
- There goes that ''we'' again.
- Will you listen to me? We have to do--
Once this creature has been reborn...
his curse is going to spread until
the whole of the Earth is destroyed.
- Yeah? ls that my problem?
- lt is everybody's problem.
his curse is going to spread until
the whole of the Earth is destroyed.
- Yeah? ls that my problem?
- lt is everybody's problem.
Evelyn, l appreciate you saving my life
and all, but when l signed on...
- Yeah? ls that my problem?
- lt is everybody's problem.
Evelyn, l appreciate you saving my life
and all, but when l signed on...
l agreed to take you out there
and to bring you back.
l have done that.
End of job. End of story.
- Contract terminated.
- That's all l am to you? A contract?
You can either
tag along with me...
or you can stay here...
and try and save the world!
- What's it gonna be?
- l'm staying.
- Fine!
- Fine.
- Ooh!
l'm the last of the Royal Air Corps
still stationed out here, you know.
Some bloody idiot
spilled his drink.
All the other laddies died in the sky
and were buried in the sand.
Some bloody idiot
spilled his drink.
All the other laddies died in the sky
and were buried in the sand.
Good chaps,
every one of them too. Ooh.
All the other laddies died in the sky
and were buried in the sand.
Good chaps,
every one of them too. Ooh.
- Hi, Winston.
- Ye-- Uh-- You know, O'Connell.
Ever since the end
of the great war...
- Hi, Winston.
- Ye-- Uh-- You know, O'Connell.
Ever since the end
of the great war...
there hasn't been a--
a single challenge...
Ever since the end
of the great war...
there hasn't been a--
a single challenge...
- worthy of a man like me.
- Yeah?
We all got our little
problems today, Winston.
- worthy of a man like me.
- Yeah?
We all got our little
problems today, Winston.
l just wish l could have
chucked it in with the others...
and gone down
in flame and glory...
l just wish l could have
chucked it in with the others...
and gone down
in flame and glory...
instead of sitting
around here...
rotting of boredom and booze.
Cheers. Mmm.
Mmm. Oh, well, back to the airfield.
- Tell me, has your sister always been--
- Oh, yes, always.
Mmm. Oh, well, back to the airfield.
- Tell me, has your sister always been--
- Oh, yes, always.
We're all packed up, but the damn boat
doesn't leave till tomorrow morning.
Tail set firmly
between your legs, l see.
You can talk. You don't have
some sacred walkin' corpse after ya.
So, uh, how's your friend?
He had his eyes and his tongue
ripped out. How would you be?
So, uh, how's your friend?
He had his eyes and his tongue
ripped out. How would you be?
l'm so pleased...
He had his eyes and his tongue
ripped out. How would you be?
l'm so pleased...
to meet you.
Prince lmhotep
does not like to be touched.
A silly Eastern superstition,
l'm afraid.
Prince lmhotep
does not like to be touched.
A silly Eastern superstition,
l'm afraid.
Please forgive me.
Oh-ho. Whoops.
Mr. Burns...
Prince lmhotep thanks you
for your hospitality.
Mr. Burns...
Prince lmhotep thanks you
for your hospitality.
And for your eyes...
- and for your tongue.
- Wha--
- But l am afraid more is needed.
- and for your tongue.
- Wha--
- But l am afraid more is needed.
The prince must finish the job...
and consummate the curse
which you and your friends...
- have brought down upon yourselves.
- Wait! No!
and consummate the curse
which you and your friends...
- have brought down upon yourselves.
- Wait! No!
Good luck, boys.
Sweet Jesus!
Tasted just like--
Blood.
Sweet Jesus!
Tasted just like--
Blood.
''And the rivers and waters
of Egypt ran red...
and were as blood.''
''And the rivers and waters
of Egypt ran red...
and were as blood.''
He's here.
Oh, looks like
there's gonna be a storm.
- Oh, Evelyn!
- Oh, so you're still here.
Oh, looks like
there's gonna be a storm.
- Oh, Evelyn!
- Oh, so you're still here.
We've got problems.
Hey!
Beni, you little stinkweed.
Where you been?
We are in serious trouble.
We are in very serious trouble.
He does seem to like Evy.
Yeah, what's that about?
- What's this guy want?
- There's only one person
that can give us any answers.
- You!
- Miss Carnahan.
- What's this guy want?
- There's only one person
that can give us any answers.
- You!
- Miss Carnahan.
- Gentlemen.
- What is he doing here?
Do you really want to know,
or would you prefer to just shoot us?
- Gentlemen.
- What is he doing here?
Do you really want to know,
or would you prefer to just shoot us?
After what l just saw...
l'm willing to go
on a little faith here.
After what l just saw...
l'm willing to go
on a little faith here.
We are part of
an ancient secret society.
For over 3,000 years
we have guarded the City of the Dead.
We are sworn at manhood
to do any and all in our power
to stop the High Priest lmhotep...
For over 3,000 years
we have guarded the City of the Dead.
We are sworn at manhood
to do any and all in our power
to stop the High Priest lmhotep...
- from being reborn into this world.
- Because of you, we have failed.
You think this justifies
the killing of innocent people?
- from being reborn into this world.
- Because of you, we have failed.
You think this justifies
the killing of innocent people?
- To stop this creature?
Let me think. Yes!
- Yes!
Question:
Why doesn't he like cats?
Cats are the guardians of the
underworld. He will fear them
until he is fully regenerated.
- Then he will fear nothing.
- You know how he gets hisself
fully regenerated?
Cats are the guardians of the
underworld. He will fear them
until he is fully regenerated.
- Then he will fear nothing.
- You know how he gets hisself
fully regenerated?
- By killin' everyone
who opened that chest.
- And suckin' 'em dry!
Jonathan, will you stop
playing with that?
- By killin' everyone
who opened that chest.
- And suckin' 'em dry!
Jonathan, will you stop
playing with that?
When l saw him alive at Hamunaptra,
he called me Anck-su-namun.
And then just now in Mr. Burns'
quarters, h-he tried to kiss me.
lt's because of his love
for Anck-su-namun that he was cursed.
And then just now in Mr. Burns'
quarters, h-he tried to kiss me.
lt's because of his love
for Anck-su-namun that he was cursed.
- Apparently, even after 3,000 years--
- He is still in love with her.
Yes, that is very romantic,
but what has it got to do with me?
- Apparently, even after 3,000 years--
- He is still in love with her.
Yes, that is very romantic,
but what has it got to do with me?
Perhaps he will once again
try to raise her from the dead.
Yes, that is very romantic,
but what has it got to do with me?
Perhaps he will once again
try to raise her from the dead.
And it appears he has already chosen
his human sacrifice.
Bad luck, old mum.
On the contrary, it may
just give us the time we need...
to kill the creature.
On the contrary, it may
just give us the time we need...
to kill the creature.
We will need all the help we can get.
His powers are growing.
''And he stretched forth
his hand towards the heavens...
and there was darkness
throughout the land of Egypt.''
We must stop him from regenerating.
and there was darkness
throughout the land of Egypt.''
We must stop him from regenerating.
- Who opened that chest?
- There was me and Daniels here.
- And Burns, of course.
- And that Egyptologist fellow.
- Who opened that chest?
- There was me and Daniels here.
- And Burns, of course.
- And that Egyptologist fellow.
- What about my buddy Beni?
- No, he scrammed outta there
'fore we opened the thing.
- And Burns, of course.
- And that Egyptologist fellow.
- What about my buddy Beni?
- No, he scrammed outta there
'fore we opened the thing.
- Yeah, he was the smart one.
- Well, that sounds like Beni.
We must find the Egyptologist and bring
him back to the safety of the fort...
- Yeah, he was the smart one.
- Well, that sounds like Beni.
We must find the Egyptologist and bring
him back to the safety of the fort...
- before the creature can get to him.
- Right.
We must find the Egyptologist and bring
him back to the safety of the fort...
- before the creature can get to him.
- Right.
She stays here.
You three, come with me.
- before the creature can get to him.
- Right.
She stays here.
You three, come with me.
You can't leave me behind
like some old carpetbag.
She stays here.
You three, come with me.
You can't leave me behind
like some old carpetbag.
Who put you in charge? O'Connell,
what do you think you are doing?
- Jonathan! O'Connell!
- Sorry, but he's a bit... tall.
Coward that you are! O'Connell,
you are not leaving me in here!
- Jonathan! O'Connell!
- Sorry, but he's a bit... tall.
Coward that you are! O'Connell,
you are not leaving me in here!
Jonathan, if you don't open this door
in one minute flat--
- O'Connell, let me out of here.
- This door doesn't open.
Jonathan, if you don't open this door
in one minute flat--
- O'Connell, let me out of here.
- This door doesn't open.
- She doesn't come out,
and no one goes in, right?
- Right.
- Right?
- O'Connell! Jonathan!
- Let's go, Jonathan.
Oh, l thought l could just stay
at the fort and, uh, reconnoiter.
- Now!
- Yeah, right. We're just
gonna rescue the Egyptologist.
Well, well, well.
Let me guess. Spring cleaning.
Nice shot.
Oh, Beni, did you fall down?
Let me help you up.
You came back from the desert
with a new friend, didn't you, Beni?
What friend?
You are my only friend.
What the hell are you doing
with this creep? What's in it for you?
lt is better to be the right hand
of the devil than in his path.
What the hell are you doing
with this creep? What's in it for you?
lt is better to be the right hand
of the devil than in his path.
As long as l serve him,
l am immune.
lt is better to be the right hand
of the devil than in his path.
As long as l serve him,
l am immune.
- lmmune from what?
- Piszkas allat.
- What did you say?
- l don't wanna tell you.
You'll just hurt me some more.
- lmmune from what?
- Piszkas allat.
- What did you say?
- l don't wanna tell you.
You'll just hurt me some more.
What are you looking for?
And try not to lie to me.
The book! The black book they found
at Hamunaptra. He wants it back.
What are you looking for?
And try not to lie to me.
The book! The black book they found
at Hamunaptra. He wants it back.
He said to me it would be
worth its weight in gold.
- What does he want the book for?
- l don't know.
He said to me it would be
worth its weight in gold.
- What does he want the book for?
- l don't know.
Something about bringing
his dead girlfriend back to life.
But that's all.
He just wants the book, l swear.
Just the book, l swear.
And your sister.
But other than that--
Just the book, l swear.
And your sister.
But other than that--
That's two down,
two to go.
Then he'll be coming after Evy.
Guards in place!
Reporting all clear, sir!
Then he'll be coming after Evy.
Guards in place!
Reporting all clear, sir!
To hell with this.
l'm goin' downstairs, get me a drink.
You want somethin'?
- Yeah. Yeah, get me a glass of bourbon.
- All right.
- A-And a shot of bourbon.
- Yeah, okay, okay.
- And a bourbon chaser.
- l'll get your damn bourbon!
- A-And a shot of bourbon.
- Yeah, okay, okay.
- And a bourbon chaser.
- l'll get your damn bourbon!
Don't worry about the door.
- And a bourbon chaser.
- l'll get your damn bourbon!
Don't worry about the door.
Anck-su-namun.
Hey, get your ugly face off of her!
Look what l got.
- You all right?
- Well, l'm not sure.
Well, according to legend,
the black book the Americans
found at Hamunaptra...
is supposed to bring people
back from the dead.
Well, according to legend,
the black book the Americans
found at Hamunaptra...
is supposed to bring people
back from the dead.
- Until now it was a notion
l was unwilling to believe.
- Believe it, sister.
That's what brought
our buddy back to life.
- Until now it was a notion
l was unwilling to believe.
- Believe it, sister.
That's what brought
our buddy back to life.
l'm thinking that if the black book
can bring dead people to life--
- Then maybe the gold book can kill him.
- That's the myth.
l'm thinking that if the black book
can bring dead people to life--
- Then maybe the gold book can kill him.
- That's the myth.
Now we just have to find out
where the gold book is hidden.
lmhotep. lmhotep.
Now we just have to find out
where the gold book is hidden.
lmhotep. lmhotep.
Last but not least...
my favorite plague--
boils and sores.
They have become his slaves.
So it has begun,
the beginning of the end.
Not quite yet, it hasn't.
Come on.
lmhotep. lmhotep.
Not quite yet, it hasn't.
Come on.
lmhotep. lmhotep.
According to Bembridge scholars,
the golden Book of Amun-Ra...
is located inside
the statue of Anubis.
According to Bembridge scholars,
the golden Book of Amun-Ra...
is located inside
the statue of Anubis.
- That's where we found the black book.
- Exactly.
- Looks like the old boys
at Bembridge were mistaken.
- They mixed the books up.
Mixed up where
they were buried.
- Looks like the old boys
at Bembridge were mistaken.
- They mixed the books up.
Mixed up where
they were buried.
So if the black book
is inside the statue of Anubis...
Mixed up where
they were buried.
So if the black book
is inside the statue of Anubis...
then the golden book
must be inside--
- Come on, Evy. Faster.
- Patience is a virtue.
Not right now it isn't.
Uh, l think l'll go
and get the car started.
l've got it. The golden
Book of Amun-Ra is at Hamunaptra
inside the statue of Horus.
Take that, Bembridge scholars.
l've got it. The golden
Book of Amun-Ra is at Hamunaptra
inside the statue of Horus.
Take that, Bembridge scholars.
lmhotep.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
- Get this thing in gear, boy.
Let's get outta here.
- Evy!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
- Get this thing in gear, boy.
Let's get outta here.
- Evy!
- Come on, Evy. Hurry up.
- lmhotep!
You're gonna get yours, Beni!
You hear me?
- You're gonna get yours!
- Oh, like l've never heard that before!
You're gonna get yours, Beni!
You hear me?
- You're gonna get yours!
- Oh, like l've never heard that before!
Hang on!
Hey! O'Connell!
O'Connell!
Okay! Go, go!
Back! Back!
lmhotep. lmhotep.
lt's the creature.
He's fully regenerated.
Keetah mi pharos...
aja nilo, isirian.
''Come with me, my princess.
lt is time
to make you mine forever.''
''For all eternity,'' idiot.
lt is time
to make you mine forever.''
''For all eternity,'' idiot.
Koontash dai na...
aja nilo.
''Take my hand...
and l will spare
your friends.''
Oh, dear.
and l will spare
your friends.''
Oh, dear.
- Have you got any bright ideas?
- l'm thinkin', l'm thinkin'.
You better think of something fast,
because if he turns me into a mummy...
you're the first one
l'm coming after.
You better think of something fast,
because if he turns me into a mummy...
you're the first one
l'm coming after.
Don't!
He has to take me to Hamunaptra
to perform the ritual.
She is right.
Live today, fight tomorrow.
He has to take me to Hamunaptra
to perform the ritual.
She is right.
Live today, fight tomorrow.
l'll be seeing you again.
Evelyn!
- Hey, that's mine.
- Thank you.
No! Let go of me!
- lmhotep.
- Let go of me!
- Good-bye, my friend.
- Come here, you little--
lmhotep. lmhotep.
- Good-bye, my friend.
- Come here, you little--
lmhotep. lmhotep.
Come on!
- What about my sister?
- We're gonna get her back! Go!
Come on!
- What about my sister?
- We're gonna get her back! Go!
You're next!
- What about my sister?
- We're gonna get her back! Go!
You're next!
Come on!
Give me your hand!
- You go!
- Come on!
Go!
Morning, Winston.
Uh, a word?
What's your little problem got to do
with His Majesty's Royal Air Corps?
Not a damn thing.
What's your little problem got to do
with His Majesty's Royal Air Corps?
Not a damn thing.
- ls it dangerous?
- You probably won't live through it.
Not a damn thing.
- ls it dangerous?
- You probably won't live through it.
By Jove, do you really think so?
- ls it dangerous?
- You probably won't live through it.
By Jove, do you really think so?
Everybody else we've bumped into
has died. Why not you?
By Jove, do you really think so?
Everybody else we've bumped into
has died. Why not you?
What's the, uh--
What's the challenge then?
Rescue the damsel in distress,
kill the bad guy and save the world.
Oh! Winston Havelock
at your service, sir.
Are you all right?
Do l bloody look all right?
How you doin'?
See that?
l've never seen one so big.
- Never?
- No!
See that?
l've never seen one so big.
- Never?
- No!
Get off of me! Get off!
l need a new job.
Oh, my God.
We're back.
O'Connell.
Oh, my God.
Hey, Winston!
Pedal faster!
Hang on, men!
Stop it!
You'll kill them!
That's the idea.
Here l come, laddies!
l love the whole
sand wall trick.
lt was beautiful. Bastard.
Excuse me.
Um, a little help
would be useful...
if it's not too much trouble!
Um, a little help
would be useful...
if it's not too much trouble!
Yeah, yeah. All right.
Winston! Hey, Winston!
Quicksand!
Get back! lt's quicksand.
Keep moving!
Nasty little fellows such as yourself
always get their comeuppance.
Really? They do?
Nasty little fellows such as yourself
always get their comeuppance.
Really? They do?
Oh, yes. Always.
l'd take
those bigger stones first.
Take them from the top, otherwise
the whole thing will cave in on us.
l'd take
those bigger stones first.
Take them from the top, otherwise
the whole thing will cave in on us.
Come on.
Put your backs into it.
Yes, well, you've got the idea.
Chop-chop.
l say!
Gents, you should come
and have a look at this.
What?
lt's in my arm!
My arm!
Whoa!
- Do something!
- Hold him!
Whoa!
- Do something!
- Hold him!
Do something! Do something!
Not that! Not that!
O'Connell.
Shatay Wapay Ku Ra Eck!
Bembridge scholars
never wrote about this.
Get off me.
Get off!
Wha-- Wha--
- Can you see--
- Yeah.
- Can you believe--
- Can we just--
- No.
- Can you believe--
- Yeah.
- Can we just--
- No.
- Who the hell are these guys?
- Priests.
lmhotep's priests.
- Who the hell are these guys?
- Priests.
lmhotep's priests.
All right then.
There he is!
Hello, Horus, old boy.
Time to close the door.
Let's go.
Anck-su-namun.
O'Connell!
Jonathan!
Damn.
- These guys just don't quit, do they?
- Keep digging.
Damn.
- These guys just don't quit, do they?
- Keep digging.
Oh! The Book of Amun-Ra.
Save the girl.
Kill the creature.
What are you waiting for?
Get out! Get out!
You all right?
Let's go.
The Book of Amun-Ra!
l found it, Evy! l found it!
Shut up
and get me off here, Jonathan!
Open the book, Jonathan.
lt's the only way to kill him.
You have to open the book
and find the inscription.
Open the book, Jonathan.
lt's the only way to kill him.
You have to open the book
and find the inscription.
Well, l can't open it!
lt's locked or something.
- We need the key, Evy!
- lt's inside his robes.
O'Connell!
lm Yub Set Na.
Mummies.
Look out! There's one down--
O'Connell!
Here's an inscription.
''Rasheem-- Rasheem oola--
Rasheem oola Kashka!''
Oh, boy.
Oh, yeah.
This just keeps gettin'
better and better.
Oh, yeah.
This just keeps gettin'
better and better.
- Do something, Jonathan.
- Me?
This just keeps gettin'
better and better.
- Do something, Jonathan.
- Me?
- You can command them.
- You have got to be joking.
Finish the inscription
on the cover, idiot.
- Then you can control them.
- Oh. Right.
Uh-uh.
Oh, oh, oh!
Hurry up, Jonathan!
- l can't figure out this last symbol.
- What does it look like?
lt's a, uh, a bird--
a stork!
A-Ahmenophus!
Oh, yes, l see.
Whoa!
Uh, Hootash im Ahmenophus.
Fa-Kooshka
Anck-su-namun!
- lmhotep!
- Anck-su-namun!
Evy! l've got it.
Keep him busy.
No problem.
Hurry, Evy!
- Hurry!
- You're not helping.
Hurry, Evy!
- Hurry!
- You're not helping.
Oh! l've got it.
Kadeesh mal.
Pared oos.
l thought you said
it was gonna kill him!
He's mortal.
''Death...
is only
the beginning.''
- Time to go.
- Ohh!
You've lost the book!
- Jonathan, l can't believe--
- Come on!
- Couldn't we just--
- No, Jonathan!
O'Connell!
- O'Connell! Wait!
- Come on, come on.
Wait! Please!
Come on, come on! Beni!
Good-bye, Beni.
Go away.
Shoosh ma! Shoosh ma!
Shoosh ma!
Get away!
Look out, look out!
Oh! Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You've earned the respect
and gratitude of me and my people.
Yes, well, it was nothing.
You've earned the respect
and gratitude of me and my people.
Yes, well, it was nothing.
May Allah
smile upon you always.
And... yourself.
May Allah
smile upon you always.
And... yourself.
Yes, anytime.
Stay out of trouble.
He's just... leaving us here.
Well, l guess we go home
empty-handed... again.
l wouldn't say that.
Well, l guess we go home
empty-handed... again.
l wouldn't say that.
Oh, please!
How 'bout you, darling?
Would you like a little kissy-wissy?
Whoo! Ohh.