Jacob!
What are you up to?
Watch this guys!
Fire!
Hey!
- Hey get down!
- Fuck!
Jacob!
We're talking about school
suspension this time.
Six months at Rawlins.
Sheriff Armstrong says if you
cooperate he might consider.
I was the only one.
- Don't bullshit me.
- I don't rat on my crew.
Look at me!
You almost dragged
your brother in all this.
Is that what you wanted?
Take responsibility Jacob.
Alright.
- It's gone.
- Fuckin' asshole!
Jacob!
- Let me go!
Step back, Jacob!
How am I supposed to ride?
By getting your act
together, that's how.
Mom gave it to me, and I hate you...
so fucking much.
'The fuck you lookin' at?
Look I didn't mean
to push you like that.
I will take
ownership for my actions.
And the consequences
of those actions.
Again.
I will take ownership for my actions.
And the consequences of those actions.
You've got something to say, son?
We're all ears.
'Just been here first week, I'm gonna
cut you some slack, alright?
Son, you got it easy
on this side of the fence.
You understand?
You get to go home at night,
sleep in your warm snuggly bed.
But you best start giving a dam.
Else you'll wind up over there
in Juvie with the big boys.
'You sure as hell ain't going
home to your mommy and daddy.
You'll be locked up.
Crying and pissing
yourself to sleep every night.
On the ground.
Gimme 50.
Now!
Again.
I will take ownership for my actions.
And the consequences of those actions.
Again.
I will take ownership for my actions.
And the consequences of those actions.
Come on, let's go.
In your bed.
Hey, go back to sleep, alright?
Triple-D's, holy shit!
Hell, I'd give her the "D".
Like that one?
Hey, put that shit away.
It's all good. -He's my fucking
brother, get up you're going home.
I wanna stay with you guys.
- I said no, go!
'Hear about that kid Ray Martin
got stabbed in Juvie last year?
Fuckin' died, man.
Who's next?
- Me go home.
Sorry, little man.
Let me have some.
- Get your own bag!
He's gotten way faster.
- Oh yeah.
Yeah, he has.
You should totally race again.
- Yeah, I know.
Holy shit look, more at Linden.
Hey girls!
More at Linden.
- God dam!
'Things I would do to that.
You talk to her or what?
I don't know.
Show us your tits!
- WTF Lance!
Talk to the ladies it's all good.
They're leaving, great going!
Come on don't be like this, come back.
- Fucking idiot, dude.
Gimme a sec.
Well, well, well.
Hey.
- Hi honey.
What are you trouble makers up to?
Just hanging out.
- Yah, hangin' out.
It's all we're doing, I swear.
- Where's your dad?
Pff! 'Fuck if I know.
You know, you're getting yourself
quite a reputation around here.
Come on Jacob.
- Hey, Jacob.
Hey, whatever.
Dude, she's hot. -Shut up.
-It's his aunt.
Get over here and sit down.
- I'm not hungry.
You gotta eat somethin'.
Don't make me get up outa this chair.
Here.
Come on.
Dad was out in Galveston today.
- Wes.
I'm taking another
crack at the place.
God, destroyed it for a reason.
We're gonna move there.
- Wes, eat your dinner.
I'm not moving there.
Sit down.
Dick!
What was that?
How many times you' gonna
play that stupid song?
Leave your brother alone.
Wes, come on, sit up.
Hey, Wes, get up.
Come on.
Wes, let's go.
Hurry up.
Alright, let's go.
It's all you.
Look, you're the one who
wanna be part of the crew.
He ain't gon' do it.
- Shut up.
Holy shit, he did it.
Shit.
- Come on, come on.
We gotta go.
Hey, stop right here.
Jacob.
- Let's go, Wes, come on.
Go, go, go.
Come on, speed up.
Stop.
Call the cops Jenks.
Look, you can't tell anyone, okay?
No one.
It's okay, I swear.
I won't let anything happen to you.
Hey.
You did good, alright.
You're gonna stop crying.
Go to sleep.
Jacob.
What if we really went
to Galveston like Mom wanted?
I'm not going anywhere.
"Would you like to try
our new 'quiet' burger.
- No thanks Ted, I'll just have
an order of crazy fries.".
- Hey, you want ham or peanut butter?
- Ham.
"Watch out, there's enough
rat poison in this dip-cone ".
I want some.
Hey, you asked for ham.
Who is it?
Hi boys!
I'm Mrs. Roberts and this is
Officer Gardner, how are you doing?
It's yours?
No.
Well, how about I leave it here
just in case it is.
Whatever.
Is your dad home, boys?
Why you all here?
Let's go inside, come on.
- What do you want?
It's alright.
Look, I told you, yo'all
can't be here, okay?
Look, my dad will be back later,
you can come back then.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Let's go in here, come on.
Come on.
- You can't do this.
- No.
Where do they take me, Jacob?
I need you to get in the car.
Enough.
Come on Jacob, okay.
- Come on, you'll be alright.
- Jacob.
It's alright let him go.
Pam, open up.
Where is he?
- Calm down.
- Wes, get down here.
- Hollis, he's asleep.
- What do you think you're doing?
- You think that was my idea?
- CPS just dumped him on me.
And you need to start
getting your shit together.
I can't keep playing
baby sitter for you.
I can take care of my boys.
I'm just taking Wes for
a little while.  That's all.
- I can take care of my kids.
- Really, can you?
Rebecca would be so
heartbroken and you know it.
She loved those boys way too much to see
you abandon them the way you did.
You told them.
That's what this is about.
You told that case worker?
Back up.
Back up Hollis.
I didn't say a damn word.
Just calm down.
- What did they say?
- Go to bed.
- When is he coming back?
- Go to bed Jacob.
Hollis!
I ain't troublin' no one.
Your neighbors are complaining again.
You gotta turn that music down
and go back inside, son.
It's a free country
I can do what I want.
Come on man, don't cause
any more trouble, we don't
wanna bring you in again
if we don't have to.
It's you?
Huh?
Fuckin' ugly coward.
Hey, you got something
to say to me, Harrold.
- You say it to my face.
- Hollis! Hollis!
Hollis, that's enough.
Going to have to sleep this off.
Come on, let's go.
Get your hands off me.
- Come on.
- No.
- Get your hands off me.
I'm going!
I'm going.
My co-worker had it,
sorry about that.
Now.
You know I can't be letting a 10 year old
boy go unsupervised like you've been doing.
And trust me, a 13 year old kid on probation
is not our idea of a good care taker.
Well.
The judge has allowed
you to keep Jacob.
But you gotta go to the court
appointed counselor once a week.
Make every single court date.
Hm.
And stop drinking.
We'll give it a month
and revisit the situation.
You're just lucky judge
Bradley is a big baseball fan.
He said he went to all your games.
Look I know that you and your
family have been through a hard time.
It seems to me that...
you could use a little help.
So you look to me and your
sister-in-law because
we're just trying to help
you out, you understand.
Hollis!
This is just temporary.
You know that.
It's not like last time, okay?
You been practicing your moves?
Hum.
You're better than me.
Alright, come here.
Here we go.
You be good.
- Alright?
- Ok.
I love that.
Go to bed.
Aunt Pam?
- Your okay?
- Can you sit with me until I fall asleep?
Yeah of course.
You want me to read you a story.
Or I could actually make one up.
You can just sit in that chair.
"I wanna come home."
- Turn it down there!
- You turn it down.
- I wanna come home
- Move.
- You there?
- Aha!
You remember when Carmichael won 24 motos?
Like before you were even born?
And like, after he hurt his knee,
he won all 24 again.
Yeah.
He's like an American
hero you know.
I mean who doesn't
respect that guy?
"Bookstore is closing soon."
- I gotta go.
- Wes.
What?
I'm gonna make it right, okay?
Okay.
Who's that?
Jacob.
Alright, kid, come on.
You know Ricky just has to drive,
he wasn't afraid of the work.
He always trained harder than anyone
else, he's a role model for young ones.
He shows them you get out of life
whatever you put into it.
But you can't hide in a motocross
world, that's crazy.
Every time he goes out
there he's thinking about
nothing else but cross that
finish line first.  And he does.
- Go!
- Awesome.
Oh nice little job!
- That dude is awesome.
- Oh yeah!
Go Jacob.
Jacob!
- You alright man.
- Take the helmet off.
- You took that corner way too fast.
- No shit.
Come on get up.
Faster.
I wanna go again.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, fuckin.
I turned too quick.
- So, you talked to Lorne yet.
- Yeah, I talked to her yesterday.
- What did she say?
- I don't know.
- You on date?
- Yeah.
Since when?
- Since yesterday.
Where did you guys go?
- We really didn't go anywhere.
There's your house but
- What do you mean nowhere?
- No where.
- Wait.
So you haven't been on a real
date yet, like your dating.
Yes it's been one day,
how can we go anywhere?
- You're not dating her then.
- Take her to your house.
- Have you gotten anywhere yet.
- Nope.
- I would have done it in the first 20min.
- Shut up man.
- Anyway she invited me to this
kid's party Saturday night
- It's a rich kid's party.
- It's nice, like it?
- Yeah.
Was this 250?
-How much?
- Way too much. That's how much.
My mom is baking a chocolate
cake tonight, for
Tim's birthday if anyone
wants to come over.
I can't, my parents wanna
have some bullshit big talk.
That sucks.
I thought Tim and your mom broke up.
She took him back, fucking dick,
treats her like crap.
You remember that one time when your
mother kicked me outa the house?
Your mom wouldn't take shit from
no one, she was so fuckin cool.
Look Jacob, I'm sorry man.
Whatever, just go.
Hey, do you hear Bailey's
renovating that bowling alley?
- Yeah?
- Yeah man.
- Saturday night specials, baby.
- We're the worst in the league.
Me, you, Rebecca.
Janey Donovan.
That girl had an ass on her.
Every time she grab that pink little
ball and bowl walk up to that line.
I'm about hurt myself.
I still got that last place
trophy Rebecca made us.
She always said we're the
best to be the last.
Yeah.
She sure did
Mind if say something?
Why don't you sell this place, man?
She'd want you to let it go.
This ain't the dream home she
thought it was gonna be you know.
You owe me a 6-pack.
Shiyea' who's helpin who here boy?
Seriously where's my saw at?
Hey Jacob!
Wes here?
I don't think it's a good idea
that you all hang out right now.
Look, I'm gonna win a bike
race next month.
You gonna see me at nationals this year.
You know who Ricky Carmichael is?
I don't.
That's really great!
Your mom would be real proud of you.
Look, can I at least come
in hang out with him?
Not today  I'm sorry.
Come on.
Hey Jacob get in here.
What's wrong?
You wanna go get some
ice-cream after the game.
We can celebrate.
Celebrate what?
I got the back deck finished finally.
- Fuck Houston.
- Watch your language.
Don't go in my room.
If you change your mind let me know.
Dad!
My best friend at school
he told me a joke.
Yeah?
What is that?
You got 30 cows and 28 chickens.
- How many didn't?
I don't know.
There are 30 cows and 28 chicken.
How many didn't?
Didn't what?
- That's the punch line?
- No.
There are 30 cows and 28 chickens.
I don't know what you're saying.
I wanna know the joke.
There are 30 cows, twenty
'eight' chicken.
There's only 30 cows,
28 chickens, okay.
There are 30 cows, twenty
of them 'ate' chickens.
Ahh!
20 cows ate the chickens.
"I must confess he said that
I found it very difficult to row".
For so long a time,
though I assure you.
I did my best and did not
spare my strength.
I noticed that though the wind
blew strong in my face,
the current continued
to carry us out".
Aunt Pam, you should
probably go to bed.
Yah you're right.
- I love you.
- Love you.
- Hey.
Shhh, get your shoes on.
Let's go.
Wes don't be a pussy, let's go.
He's getting cosy.
Lucky him.
Hey, that could be us
in a few seconds.
So gross.
Katy! Katy?
No shit?
Have you been in that
old bookstore on 12th?
There's like this whole
section on pirates.
And that weird guy Max was there.
He would show me these
old rap records.
She's just trying to buy your love
and your too dumb to realize it?
You'll like aunt Pam, she bought your bike
helmet and took care of us when dad left.
You're just jealous cause
she took me to Six Flags.
As if I could give a shit about
Six Flags, your stupid pirate bookstore.
She's not your mom.
You miss her?
I miss dad.
Did you grab the field trip slip?
Huh, I'm sorry uh.
I'm really late I've a 5:30
with Carla Raines.
I'm sorry Mr. Wilson she had
to leave she waited 45min for you.
Call us back in the morning.
We'll re-schedule, okay?
- Yes ma'am.
- Okay.
I just saw the case,
it kinda spoke to me.
- Well.
- Said "buy me!".
- Looks nice.
- It's badass cheap.
- It's a good purchase.
Wait Anders.  Are you're talking about that
girl you were with last night, or that gun?
- That gun.
- She was a bargain.
From the bargain bid, she was a little
husky, she was a good deal for him.
Very funny.
You know Danny that new kid
at the barber shop.
Just got himself a Smith & Wesson
model 10.  It's a beaut' man.
- I might be better at this than him.
- Hell yeah.
Hey Capes, watch where you point
that thing, we gotta kid in here.
- Are you talking about Jackie-boy?
- Uh.
Jackie-boy, are you a kid?
- You ever held a gun?
- Why man, I own no guns.
He's gotta learn sometime, right?
- We gotta make a man outa him.
- That's not the way to do it.
- Alright, get outa that armpit boy.
- Come on Jackie-boy, you're up.
Have a seat.
Do it Jackie-boy.
Come on.
It ain't even loaded, man.
Alright Jacob, grab that
with your right hand,
now you cradle the butt right
here with your left hand.
"Cradle the butt".
This is an advice that'll
work all year round now.
You keep this tight like that,
push it tight.
Now when you go in ready to fire
you just drop that in like that, okay?
"Booo", squeeze it don't pull.
That's enough, give it back Jacob.
Dad it's fine.
Come on man, he's already got a record.
- Alright.
- Go hang out in your room.
- Alright Jacob.
- Night Jackie-boy.
- One last.
- No, I'm good.
These are the precious moments.
- They don't come back.
- These are the precious moments.
You're right.
What, I'm serious
Alright, come on.
It's time to get up.
Hey, get up, get dressed.
Put your shoes on.
I need you ready in 10 minutes, okay?
'Serious Jacob.
Just hold. 37 hold.
Ready!
Come on, Wes.
Go, go, go.
Hold on, Wes.
Wes, hey.
That was really good!
- You saw the game?
- Yeah, whole thing.
How are you doin' Hollis?
Alright.
That was really great.
- Thanks.
- Hm.
That was really good, man.
Alright, we better get going, we're gonna
meet some of the families for pizza.
Hey, we can meet you guys there,
we don't got anything goin' on.
Maybe I d meet your team, hm?
I don't think that's a good idea.
What do you mean?
I don't think that's a good idea right now
with everything that's been goin on, okay?
Just because some damn court saying
you play mommy for a few weeks.
- Don't mean I get...
- Not in front of the boys, okay?
I'm his father.
Alright, come here.
Gimme a hug.
I'm real proud of you,
and I love you.
You know that right?
- M-hm.
- I miss you.
- I miss you too.
Okay, hey, you be good.
Alright, come on kiddo.
Easy in this corner here,
you slow in that corner.
- I don't know about that but
- You're going outside, then you take inside.
- Come on man let me see it.
- Shut up.
- Hey, you see that Carmichael move?
- That was awesome.
- Let me see it.
- Chill out.
- He's so fricking fast.
- Stop.
- You fuckin dick.
- Oh shit, Lance.
Shhhhit!
Come on.
- It's over let's go.
- Get off him.
- You got it come on.
You're lucky.
Your friend Lance here
takes full blame.
I don't wanna see you boys
back in this park ever.
This is a public place for little
kids, not a bunch of teenage punks.
Alright, go on.
Nathan, except you get back over
here, and sit down.
Lance you too.
Rest of you get outa here.
Lance's parents are getting a divorce.
That fuckin sucks, man.
Yeah, Charlotte told me Lance's dad
was having an affair with Nathan's mom.
How the hell would Charlotte know?
Her mom ***.
She probably knows everything.
Fuckin hate cops.
- Man, your dad's gonna kick your ass.
- Shut up.
That's not like mom's but.
Hm.
What?
You washed my uniform?
It's on your bed.
Where did you get the shiner?
Some kid at the park.
You hit him back?
Good.
Where did you get the girl make up?
Andrew's sister.
She used to tell us about that...
kid from the Burger Palace.
He got his face bashed in so bad in
Juvie, he couldn't talk for a month.
It's why he's got the weird scar.
Hm.
I saw the kid who got stabbed
and died like two months ago.
Well, I guess it's best you
stay out there then, uh?
Hey.
You gotta do better.
The qualifier for nationals
is in two weeks.
Good.
Hey, we need the video camera
- Yeah Lance, get some clothes on.
- Just open the door?
Hey man, you're grounded?
You come out?
My brother's taking us to the track.
- Hey man, where's your mom?
- Shit, I don't know.
- So you wanna come or...
- I said I don't wanna fucking go,
now take the camera.
Jesus.
Alright, I'm gonna be right
back here to pick you up, okay?
What do you want Pam?
I need to talk to you.
It's important.
So, I got offered a job,
a couple days ago in Houston.
And I've been giving
it a lot of thought.
And I'm gonna take it.
You remember how much we all wanted
to get out of here when we were kids?
And you guys always had Galveston.
So Wes's lawyer told me that
you missed counseling.
So she's advising me that it is...
in Wes's best interest...
that he come with me to Houston.
Get out of my house.
Get out!
Wait, Hollis.
Jacob's gonna end up in Juvie and
you know it, and then what?  Wes too?
Next time you come back over
here, you'll be bringing him home.
I just want what's best for him.
Travis left 'cause
you didn't want kids.
You never wanted kids, Pam.
Why the hell are
you tryin' to take mine?
Dad!
Hi you've reached Pam...
and Wes.  Leave us a message.
Hey Wes, this is Jacob.
Just call me back okay?
Look at this jackass.
You're gonna win this shit, man,
the cat's in the bag.
I heard about Robert Ramirez, he put
some kid in the hospital yesterday, dude.
He wasn't in the hospital but,
I think he's messed up pretty bad.
They took Robbie in handcuffs.
- Shit.
'You seen it?
Have you seen Wes lately?
Nope.
You got this, man.
You'll win the whole race.
I have to.
- You've seen my belt?
- No.
Damn.
Find that nice tie mom got you?
Yes, it's right here.
I don't know how to tie it.
- She always did for me.
- I know.
Come here.
Lift up your chin.
Here you go.
Here.
It's good.
I'm not dragging you in here with me.
You boys are.
I'm not threatening you with
anything, I'm trying to keep what.
like you said there are children and
I gotta keep every other weekend.
- Come on.
- What 'they say? Dad where's Wes?
Jacob.
We'll get him back.
Wes!
What are you doing here?
- Why you never call me back?
- What's that?
- I don't know.
- What do you mean you don't know?
Look, I'm gonna race next week.
Alright?
I'm gonna win for you and dad,
whole town's gonna see it.
- Okay.
- I need you to be there, okay?
You gotta tell Pam.
Wes?
Let me go.
Hey mom's still at her bridge club,
you wanna come in for a cold one.
I gotta get back.
Everything's gonna work
out just fine, man.
What 'you worried about.
Yeah.
Put some clothes on.
You scaring the kids.
You alright with riding this one?
Well, come on.
Get in.
If you're just pulling
in at the front gate
you can tune in at 87.
5 on your fm radio.
for today's voice action.
...just now finishing up race number 2.
We got race number 3 loading
in the gate.
Open amateur class for 85cc
and larger bikes.
Everyone's trying to earn their way to the
Texas amateur all-star amateur nationals.
Top 12 qualifiers, and today's
qualifying race.
Again race number 3 at the starting line.
Right now race number 3 is on...
Yeah Jacob.
Jacob wooo.
The 45 are about to enter the first
turn here at cow-boy Badlands MX park.
Again the top 12 qualify for
the Texas amateur all-star.
Jacob Wilson now starts to put up a
little bit of pressure running up front.
Jacob.
Gary Owens also appears.
Couple of laps in, here we go with
Gary Owens, Jacob Wilson and Jason.
Come on.
All three frontrunners here...
And Jacob Wilson now
takes over the lead.
Good, good, good.
We gonna have Gary Owens
on our thrilling...
Owen makes the pass,
puts Jacob Wilson over the berm.
Is Wes here?
No.
Come on.
Hey, you were great.
Okay.
Anything else I can get you boys?
- I think that's it, thank you.
- You're welcome.
- And a coke.
- Yeah sure.
Here you go.
Your mom would be real proud of you.
Proud of a reject Juvie kid?
Close your mouth when you eat.
- Real nice.
- Hyder.
So?
- How is school boys?
- I hate school.
It's fine.
This whole thing's a joke.
Dad of the fucking year over here.
- Not here.
- Why not uh?  Everyone
knows CPS took your kid.
Whole town knows.
- Shut your mouth now.
- They don't know about Galveston.
- That's enough.
- He fucking left us.
- Stop.
- Don't tell me what to do.
It wasn't my responsibility
to take care of everything.
Take care of Wes while
you boozed up down there.
Alright, come on.
3 weeks dad, 3 whole
weeks you were gone.
Admit it, you wanna
drink yourself to death.
Cause when Duncan found you, you were
gonna leave us for good, weren't you?
- Let's go.
- We're not leaving.
- Enough now.
- Now what are we supposed to do uh?
How are we supposed to get him back?
This is all your fault.
This whole thing is your fault.
You wanna play that game?
You really wanna go there?
Take a hard look at yourself, son.
Come on, let's go.
Get your hands off me.
Don't touch me.
Fuck all of you.
Come on.
I left money on the table.
I'm sorry about this.
One of these .
Get another one.
Get it.
Nice one.
- Let me see that thing.
- No, you'll burn yourself.
- Come on, give me
- Stop.
- Hyder, stop.
- Would you give me the friggin lighter.
Jacob let me do it.
Don't hit anyone, Hyder.
Just shut up.
The retard's gonna hit his own face.
- Shut up you asshole.
- Holy shit no more house arrest.
Gimme the bat, let me
show you how it is done.
Alright.
Hold that for me.
Fuck you.
- Stop being such a little bitch.
- Lance stop motherfucker, quit it.
- Obviously it's you.
- Fuck you.
- Don't be a pussy just hold on.
- Stop Lance, this isn't funny.
- Get it away from me.
- Stop Lance.
Fuck you.
What the fuck is he doing?
What the hell?
Cut it out man.
Jacob, what are you doing?
- Stop Jacob.
- Leave me alone.
- Will you stop?
- Fuckin go away.
- Stop.
- Fucking go away.
Get the fuck off me.
The fuck.
- Get the fuck off me.
- Get off of Jacob.
Get off him.
I was supposed to protect him.
She's taking him to Houston.
Fuck that bitch.
Come on, man, get up.
Let's get outa here.
You finished?
Yeah.
Alright.
I saw your probation report
signed on your bed.
Mr. Dominguez said that you'll be back
at Barker sooner than you thought.
I'm real proud of you.
You hear what I said?
Yeah.
What?
I don't know, you just...
You look like her sitting there.
We made a great team didn't we?
The four of us.
Hey Wes, get up.
Come on.
What are you doing here?
Hurry up, pack your things let's go.
Why?
We're leaving.
What?
Hurry up, get your shoes.
- Man, what's taking him so long.
- I don't know.
- "In and out".
- Shut up.
- Don't mess with that man.
- Lance knock it off.
- Shh.
Put it back.
I can't go anywhere.
It's not a choice, Wes.
Grab your books.
Hurry up, get your shoes.
Hey where's your jacket,
the really good jacket?
Holy shit.
Lance.
Cut it out, Roger.
Roger, put it back.
What?
The fuck was that?
I'm going up there.
- You stay down here.
- Stay down.
- Quiet.
- Don't fuck up come on.
Where the fuck did you get that?
Your dad's house.
Go, go.
She's asleep.
- Drop the bat.
- Lance.
- Sit the fuck down.
- What the hell are you doing, Lance?
- Put that gun down.
- Are you okay, man.
- Oh shit Hyder.
- Is he okay, roger?
- Well, I hope he's okay, bitch.
- Just put the gun down, please.
- This bitch hit Hyder.
- No, I didn't know it was him.
Where the hell did you get a gun?
- Stop talking.
- Lance.
- What are you doing?
- She's gonna call the cops,
man, we're all going to Juvie.
- I'm not calling anybody.
- Sit the fuck down.
- Jacob.
- Lance, chill out.
Shut the hell up, sit back.
Lance I got it chill out.
Okay.
- What are you doing.
- I'm sorry.
What are you doing, Jacob stop.
Stop that, stop fighting him.
Quit moving, quit moving.
Quit moving, lay the fuck down.
It's okay, it's okay.
What are you doing?
You think it's okay what you did?
You gonna wake the fuckin neighbors.
Lance!
You're a fucking bitch,
breaking a perfectly good family.
- Cut it out, man.
- ...outa here, I don't feel good.
- Just chill out.
- Get the fuck over there.
- Let it go.
- You're breaking up a family.
You have a clue how fucked up that is?
Do you?
Why don't I shoot you now, huh?
- Lance stop! We're fucking leaving.
- You think you're so tough?
- Lance, stop.
- Please.
- You fucking bitch.
- Lance, hey.
Calm down.
Get off me.
- Lance.
- Get off me.
Get off of him...
Shit!
Get up, cops are coming.
Let's go.
What's going on?
Wow, hey, say that again?
Pam!
- What the hell happened?
- It wasn't Jacob's fault.
He was trying to protect
everybody, and Lance was just...
I got the boy off to the town
hospital, he's gonna be fine.
You have any idea where
these boys might have gone?
I don't know.
The detectives out there want you
both to come at the station.
Are you kidding me Walter?
My kids are out there, scared and alone.
I'm not going to any of your dam station.
- When they find them,
they're bringing them in.
- They're fucking kids.
- What's he doing?
- He's just staring at me.
Let's go.
Hyder!  Hey, stop!
Stop.
Hey, Hyder.
Stop, where are Wes and Jacob?
Uh? Where are they?
The beach.
Hey, how long?
Has to be about at least another 30
minutes before it gets back over here.
Okay, we'll be back.
Let's go.
You remember when mom used
to take us here to wait?
We start over in Galveston.
Just like she wanted.
It will be like .
The Swiss family Wilson or something.
I'll take care of you, okay?
Come here.
Walk in on the left boys.
Are you OK?
Yeah.
- Hey, you see 2 boys get on
- Get on, you need to get on.
- 2 boys 10 and 13?
- You need to get on.
- 2 boys 10 and 13, did they go on.
- Yes, they're on there somewhere.
Wes.
Jacob.
You alright?
Uh? Are you OK?
I got you.
Are you OK?
Come here.
It's okay, shhh.
- I'm sorry.
I screwed up, me.
I never should have left you boys.
Look at me.
I love you more than anything.
You understand me?
Everything is going to be okay.
Wes, let me out I feel sick.
You're okay?
Stay with dad, okay?
Stay with him, understand?
Promise me you'll take care of him.
Alright boys, come on.