Subtitle created by - Aorion -
"Tomorrowland 2015" ^ (Run time : 02:01:24)
- Are we on?
- Yup. Introduce yourself.
Okay. Hey, I'm Frank.
How're you doing?
Don't answer that.
That's rhetorical.
Okay, let's get
you up to speed.
This is a story
about the future.
And the future
can be scary.
What?
Are you sure you
want to go with scary?
- Yes, I want to go with scary.
- Okay.
Okay.
The future can be scary.
Unstable governments.
Overpopulation.
Wars on every continent.
Famine.
Water shortages.
Environmental collapse.
And scientific breakthroughs,
wonder and beauty..
Could you please just
stop interrupting?
I will. Just try to be
a little more upbeat.
- Upbeat?
- Yeah, tell them what you like.
I can't tell them anything
if you keep interrupting me.
You're right.
Sorry.
As I was saying
With every second
that ticks by
- we get closer and closer...
-  Oh, I know. Tell them about...
I can't tell them anything
until I tell them about this.
Can we please just
start somewhere else?
Fine. Where would you
like me to start?
Well, you keep saying the future
wasn't always this way, right?
It wasn't. When I was
a kid, the future was...
- Different. Right?
- Yeah.
Okay, cool.
Let's start there.
Alright. Well,
when I was a kid
The future was different.
Flushing Meadows,
Corona Park World Fair!
Don't forget your valuables
and enjoy the future.
Hello, sir.
- May I help you?
- My name is John Francis Walker.
- I'm here to win $50.
- Is that so.
I took it apart because of
the nitrogen compartment.
Seeing as how the bus ride was
kinda bumpy, and, you know nitro.
I could have used a hydrogen
peroxide-powered engine,
while lapses of that
with their rocket belt,
and I guess there
were some issues
with maneuverability and
flight duration and stuff.
It's a jet pack.
Obviously.
You made
this yourself?
Athena, what
are you doing here?
Did you?
Or didn't you?
Uh.
I...
What?
Did you make this yourself?
Yeah.
Why?
I guess I got tired of waiting around
for someone else to do it for me.
Does it work?
Um... Sure.
Yeah.
Mostly.
It just doesn't really,
you know, technically...
fly.
But if it did, you
know, technically fly,
what would it's purpose be?
How would your jet pack
make the world a better place?
Can't it just be fun?
Mr. Walker, please tell me
you can do better than 'fun'.
Anything is possible.
I-I don't know
what that means.
If I was walking down the street and I saw
some kid with a jet pack fly over me,
I'd believe
anything's possible.
I'd be inspired.
Doesn't that make the
world a better place?
I suppose
it would.
If, it worked.
Unfortunately,
it does not.
And if it doesn't work,
it has no purpose at all.
Thank you for your
time, Mr. Walker.
But I can
make it work.
That's the spirit.
Until then,
young man...
have fun.
Absolutely not.
I like him.
Athena, no.
What makes you think you're
gonna make this thing fly?
- I'm optimistic.
- You're wasting your time.
- I'm not.
- Damn contraption.
It's not a contraption!
It doesn't work.
- I can make it work.
- No, you can't.
I'm not giving up.
Don't turn around.
Be cool.
What did I
just tell you?
- Sorry.
- Stop talking.
Look over there,
5 o'clock.
You know?
On a clock?
Where the 5 is?
That way.
I'm going with them. You
count to 20 then follow us.
Don't get spotted.
Who are you?
I'm the future,
Frank Walker.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Whoa-whoa-whoa...
Sorry folks,
you're gonna have to
wait for the next boat.
There'll be another
boat in just a minute.
Hello?
Good afternoon. Please step
aboard the transport.
The site is active.
Please put on your
head protection,
in order to prevent
significant injury.
Injury?
Transport will commence
in 10 seconds.
Wait.
- Wait. Wait
- 5.
4.
3.
2.
1.
Hey, that's mine.
Did you just fix it?
Wait.
Hey!
Aww!
Whoa.
Wooo!
Hey.
It works now.
So.
What is this place?
And then,
everything went to hell.
- Oh, boy.
- Well it did.
So you gave them like, one second
of blue skies and jet packs and....
It's important they need
to know the stakes.
I think they can figure out
clocks counting down on them.
- Do you want to tell the story?
- No, you're gonna...
Because if you think
you can tell the story better
I would absolutely
love to hear you try.
- Wow, really?
- Really.
Well, I guess technically
I am more qualified.
Are you?
How so?
Because unlike you,
I'm an optimist.
- Hey. Babe, you filming?
- It's video.
I knew it.
- You video it.
- Okay, go ahead, sweetie.
Do your thing, Casey.
That's Sirius.
That's Canopus.
That's Acturus.
Rigel Centaurus.
Vega, Procyon,
Capella, Betelgeuse.
Why do you love the
stars so much, Casey?
Because,
I wanna go there.
But it's so far away.
It will take a long time.
A real long time.
What if you get all the way
up there and there's nothing?
What if there's
everything.
- Oh, boy.
- What?
We're gonna go through
your entire childhood?
You started when you were a kid.
I'm just giving them context.
Just move it along, okay?
They don't have all day.
Cool.
You got it.
Identify yourself.
Nate, if you wake up dad,
I will crush you.
You shouldn't sneak out.
Well you shouldn't
still need a lovey.
Dad says it's
okay to sleep with.
That's because he doesn't
want you to grow up.
Were you at the
platform again?
What do you
do out there?
Are you trying to stop them?
From taking it down?
No.
That would make me a criminal
and a pretty terrible role model to
impressionable youth such as yourself.
But if someone
else did it
I've to assume,
they believed,
even the teeniest of actions
could change
the future.
How can
you be sure?
Because I know
how things work.
Why are they taking
the platform down?
Guess it's hard to have ideas,
and easy to give up.
But you won't,
right?
Never.
Hey, dad.
Heading to school.
- Made you lunch.
- Hey.
Wrap it up.
- How'd you do...
- You would've gotten it.
Yeah, Eddie Newton.
What?
All three cranes.
Alright, Douglas.
Thanks for the call.
Bye.
Everything okay?
Yeah, the equipment over
at Canaveral's down again.
- Weird.
- Really weird.
Well at least you
get the day off.
Actually, their bringing in
replacement cranes from Orlando
so I will be back
to work by noon.
- That's fantastic.
- Case.
Yeah?
Nothing's gonna stop 'em from
taking down that platform.
Nothing. And when we're done,
I'm out of a job.
There's nothing anyone
can do about it.
- It's inevitable.
- Well then, you'll find something else.
You're a NASA engineer.
With nothing to launch.
- There are two wolves.
- Case.
You've told me this story my
entire life and now I'm telling you.
There are two wolves,
and they're always fighting.
One,
is darkness and despair.
The other is
light and hope.
Which wolf wins?
Come on, Case.
Okay. Fine.
Don't answer.
Whichever one
you feed.
Good.
Eat.
Come on.
Mutually assured destruction.
Today, any nuclear
country or terrorist
is capable of inflicting
damage on a massive scale.
- With weapons of...
- Environmental entropy.
The polar ice caps aren't waiting for
us to decide if climate change is real.
Rising coastal waters,
intensifying weather patterns
they're all punching,
our one way ticket to...
Dystopia, by definition,
not perfect.
Huxley's 'Brave new world'.
Bradbury's 'Fahrenheit 451'.
Orwell's '1984'.
Once considered fiction, these futuristic
novels are actually happening right now.
And they seem to be getting
worse. Yes, Miss Newton?
Can we fix it?
Sorry?
I get things are bad, but
what are we doing to fix it?
Have a good
weekend, everybody.
Newton?
- Yeah.
- You made bail.
Motorcycle's in impound. You can pick
up your personal effects over there.
- Newton?
- Yeah.
Alright.
Okay.
One money clip,
$47.32
One Florida state driver's license,
one baseball cap.
We got... one pin,
one pack of Beemans gum.
And I don't know
what this is.
Sign here.
- That's not mine.
- What's not yours?
The pin.
I've never...
Aw!
What! What!
Huh!
No way.
Have I been here
the whole time?
I know.
No!
I got it.
You have no idea of the strings I had to pull to keep
Homeland Security from pressing charges, Casey.
This is not just vandalism, alright?
It's NASA.
It's government property.
Have you ever
seen this before?
You're not getting
it, are you?
I'm very upset with you.
I get it.
You're angry, I understand.
But I just need you to look at it.
Does it look weird?
Don't touch it!
Why are you
yelling at me?
Not while you're driving,
Dad. It's dangerous.
Just pull over.
Pull over.
I swear to God, Case,
if you're on drugs...
I'm not on drugs.
Just, look.
I need you to be
NASA dad now.
New frontier dad, okay?
All will be explained, as
soon as you touch this pin.
What, it's...
It's not working?
You're not seeing this!
Stop it!
Honestly, Casey. I don't
know what's gotten into you.
- Come on, guys.
- Bad move, Dexter.
Totally sweat.
Come on, idiots.
We're gonna be late for R&D.
The hover rail will be
arriving in 1 minute.
Are you coming?
- You can see me?
- We don't have all day.
- Wait for us!
- North bound line. Now departing.
Next stop: Space port.
Dad, you're embarrassing me.
Do you promise you'll
transmit everyday?
- Even when you're out of range.
- Come on, what's the big deal.
We're only going
twenty light years out.
Now arriving: space port.
- Hey guys, over here.
- Oh, hey.
Come on. We saved
a seat, just for you.
Now you run
out of power?
Aww.
- Nate, wake up.
- I didn't do it!
Dad changed the password to
his computer. Do you know it?
You smell like swamp.
Tell me the password and
you can go back to sleep.
Your phone has internet.
My phone got soaked
in a lagoon.
Fine.
What are we
looking for?
Stop!
That's it.
Extremely rare collectible pin
commemorating the 1964 World's Fair.
Experts and purveyors of the most extensive
selection of space-age collectibles in The World.
Whoa. This site
is like ancient.
Okay, give me their number.
They don't have a number.
They don't
have a number?
They have an address.
Okay, look. You are gonna tell Dad,
you woke up, saw me leaving...
I told you I was going camping
with friends and I will call tomorrow.
- Can you do that for me?
- Only if you tell me what's going on.
I...
I think that I saw...
That I went to...
the future.
Can I come, too?
Not...
yet.
- Huh!
- Hello. Is Casey Newton home?
Uh.
No.
She ordered some cookies
and I'm delivering them.
You're a girl scout?
Of course, I am.
Why aren't you
wearing a uniform?
It's at the cleaners.
Those are Oreos.
Could you please tell me
when Casey will be back?
She went camping with some friends.
She's gonna be gone for a couple of days.
Is that what you
told your parents?
Um...
Yeah.
But it's not true.
Yeah, it is.
No, Nathan.
It's not.
Don't ask me how I
knew your name.
I know it the same way
I know that you're lying to me.
Are you from the future?
You clearly understand.
So why aren't you telling
me what I need to know?
That pin thing,
it stopped working.
She went to find another one.
Nathan, where
is she looking?
Hello?
Sale this week.
Front 3 shelves,
70% off.
Oh. No thanks, I'm not
here to buy anything.
I was hoping that you
could tell me about this.
Hugo!
Welcome,
to Blast from the Past...
Thank you for
the help, dear.
Well. If you'd just kept it open
you wouldn't need my help.
If I kept it open it would ruin the
effect which is everything.
Pardon my wife, she has no respect
for showmanship. Hugo Gernsback.
- How may I help you?
- She has a pin.
She has a pin.
I saw that you were
looking for one online...
Where did you get it?
What can you
tell me about it?
I can't tell you anything about it unless
you tell me who gave it to you.
I'm not going first.
Well it seems our
business here is done.
Seems it is.
Saw something,
didn't you.
When you touched it.
Something incredible?
It's real?
Of course it is.
Don't ask me how these people have developed
technologies we haven't even dreamed of yet.
Wait.
What people?
Oh.
Have you ever wondered
what would happen
if all the geniuses, the artists,
the scientists, the...
smartest, most creative
people in the world...
decided to actually change it?
But where?
Where could they even
do such a thing?
They'd need a place free from politics,
bureaucracy, distractions,
greed.
A secret place.
Where they could build whatever
they were crazy enough to imagine.
'Plus Ultra',
they called themselves.
The only way to see it, however,
is through contact with one of these.
Why did they make them?
What are-What are they for?
Rumor has it...
They were about
to go public.
Share what they had
built with the whole world.
Unfortunately...
That never happened.
Why not?
I think we've shared
enough, young lady. I...
As, we've decided
to trust you...
Please, trust us.
And tell me,
where did you get it?
I don't know.
What do you
mean, honey?
I kinda got arrested and
it was in with my stuff.
In with your stuff?
Yeah, I don't know
how it got there.
What was that?
Tell us who gave
it to you, please?
No one gave
it to me!
It's very unlikely,
sweetheart.
Uh. You know what?
I think I'm gonna go now.
Thanks for your help.
A $1000 if you tell me
where you acquired the pin.
I don't know.
- 10,000.
- Was it a girl? A little girl?
I don't know what you
guys are talking about.
Have a nice day,
enjoy your freakout!
Tell us where she is
and you will be spared.
This is a joke, right?
Wah!
Where's the girl?
I-I don't.
I don't know.
You will tell us
about the girl.
I don't know any girl.
I told you, I-I don't...
Where is the girl?
I don't know any girl!
We have to go.
Come on. Now.
This is a time bomb.
Stops time, but not for long.
- What?
- Listen to me.
The sphere's collapsing and
you're in the line of fire.
We need to go,
or you will die.
I'm stuck.
I'm stuck!
But only temporarily.
Take my hand.
The moment you're
free I'll pull you clear.
And stay behind me.
Ready?
The girl!
Look out!
We have to go.
They're about to self-destruct.
We have to go now!
...crazy enough to imagine.
Casey, get up.
They'll be coming.
- What?
- Go!
- I know
- I don't know what I...
- Get in, Casey.
- can't get in the car.
How do you
know my name?
Just get in the car.
What just happened?
2 AA units targeted
you for extermination.
I saved your life,
they self-destructed.
Wait.
AAs?
Audio Animatronics.
They were robots?
No, advanced and more...
Sure.
Okay, Robots.
Who are you?
My name is Athena.
I'm the one who
gave you the pin.
The pin? The...
Whoa, the-the pin!
Yeah.
And I do wish
you hadn't run off
before I had a chance to give you
some rather necessary contexts.
Contexts? What are you
even talking about?
How are you
driving a car!
Who are you?
I'm a recruiter...
re---  I... know--
re re...cruiter...
60 seconds to self-destruct.
My translator is damage.
(Japanese)
So sorry about that.
You're...
one of them.
Obviously.
What are you doing?
Stop, I'm trying to help you!
Oh my god.
Oh my god!
Hey!
This isn't happening.
No, way!
Let me out of this car!
- Stop yelling! I will not.
- No!
- Let me out now!
- I will not!
I gave you my very
last pin, young lady.
And I am not about
to let it go to waste.
What do you mean
your last pin?
The place I saw.
- It exists?
- Of course, it does.
But if you don't
come with me,
it won't for much longer.
Why not?
Because they built something
they shouldn't have.
Wha-Built what?
Do you want to keep asking me questions
until someone arrives to murder us?
No.
Then which way do
you want to go?
Backwards...
Or forwards?
And you could
take me there?
I can.
I'm driving.
You fellas are
released. Thanks.
Alrighty, boys.
Fire chief says we're cleared
to go in and poke around.
Hopefully, they were out for lunch and
nobody was in there once she went boom.
Captain.
Afternoon, sir.
Dave Clark, Secret Service.
Hoo-hoo-hoo.
Looks like you got
yourself a doosy here.
Secret Service?
Hey, where are
they going?
They're securing the premises.
Thanks so much for your help,
but we're going to take it from here.
Hey Dale, found this just
outside the window.
Ever seen
anything like it?
What the hell?
God almighty!
Sale. This week, 70%.
Was it a girl? A little girl?
You wanna tell me
what's going on here, son?
No, sir.
I do not.
Was it a girl?
A little girl?
Contact Governor Nix.
Tell him we
found the girl.
Veer left!
A little more of a
heads-up next time.
Hey, here's an idea. Why don't you
just tell me where we're going.
Pittsfield of New York.
What's in Pittsfield,
New York?
Someone who can
get us back in.
Hold on, you said that
you gave me your last pin.
How many other people
did you give them to?
Not important.
I'm not even
your first choice.
I only found
you a month ago
when you started wantingly
destroying government property.
Which happens to go on my search
parameters for recruitment.
Not to mention you scored a 73
on the Feynman Daubert scale.
73?
Is that good?
Wait. Hold-Hold on.
Recruitment for what?
I'm not allowed
to answer that.
Who's not allowing you?
I'm not allowed to answer
that and I should warn you.
You keep asking me questions and my
countermeasure protocol will initiate.
Okay, and what
does that mean?
I will shut down.
You will not.
Try me.
You said that they built
something they shouldn't have.
Did something happen over there?
Something bad?
Son of a b...!
Please don't answer.
Hey. You've reached
Eddie Newton's cellphone.
Leave me a message
and I will call you back.
Hey Dad, it's Casey.
Um.
I told Nate to tell you that I was
camping, but I'm not camping.
I just don't like
lying to you.
But I didn't know how to
tell you the truth because...
But something highly
unusual is happening, and...
Okay, my point is,
I'm fine.
I will continue to be fine.
I'm not on drugs.
I haven't joined a cult.
I won't be gone long.
And I will call again soon.
I love you, Dad.
OH!
Oh my god!
Are you okay?
Yes.
Fine, thank you.
I thought I
broke you or something.
I should drive.
Casey.
I know you have no
reason to trust me.
But I've been looking for someone
like you for a very long time.
Now please.
Pull over.
Of all the people you could
give one of those pins to...
Why me?
Because you're special.
Oh yeah.
- I'm special.
- You are!
So this guy we're
gonna go see.
What's his name?
His name is Frank.
Frank Walker.
He's special, too.
Frank
Walker.
Hey! Wait!
Where are you going!
Great.
Where are your paw prints?
That is cool.
I can hear you,
you know.
Go away.
Didn't you
see the dog?
Yeah!
It's a hologram. How did
you do that in daylight?
- Pretty impressive.
- Who are you?
What do you want?
You're Frank Walker, right?
My name's Casey. And I want
you to take me there.
Take you...
where?
To the place I saw
when I touched this.
Where did
you get this?
A little girl.
Athena.
Where is she?
She ditched me here...
Of course, she did.
Look.
Wherever you came
from, kid, go back.
No, I want you to
take me there.
- What I saw...
- What you saw, is gone.
This, what you're looking for,
it doesn't exist anymore.
No, I feel-I feel like,
like I have to go.
Like, I'm supposed to go.
Why?
Because they're saving a seat
on a rocket ship just for you?
What you saw was a commercial
that was recorded decades ago.
It was an invitation that never went out,
because the damn party got canceled.
You are not supposed
to do anything.
You've been manipulated to feel like
you're part of something incredible.
Like you were special.
But you weren't.
You're not.
So that's a no?
Son of a b...
Oh, you little...
You know. I could
call the cops anytime!
Anytime!
You have...
I'm giving you 5 seconds!
I'm not leaving!
Either tell me how to
get there, or kill me!
If you touch anything in there,
that's exactly what I'll do!
What are you doing?
I'm touching things!
Open this door, now!
I'm serious.
I'll knock you out.
Hey what's this doohickey
with a trombone slidey thing?
Don't touch those!
I'm serious!
Will you take me there?
- No!
- Then you're not serious!
Oh come on. You didn't
think that was funny?
You're recording this?
If I get you to laugh, I wanna,
you know,
have
it for posterity.
I laughed.
You smiled.
A smile's not a laugh.
Everyone laughs.
It's a biological need.
Actually it isn't.
Sleep is a biological need.
And I've never seen
you sleep, either.
Well, sooner or later I'm
gonna make you laugh.
Until you do, I'm not
gonna stop trying.
Maybe you should.
What?
Stop trying.
Why?
Must you record this?
- Get out!
- Wait a second.
What is-What is that?
Is that a countdown?
I am not leaving. I deserve to
know what's going on around here.
- You deserve?
- Yeah, I deserve some answers.
- Answers to what?
- I know that you were there.
You don't know anything.
How can you ever
leave a place like that?
Because they
threw me out!
They threw me out and they
locked every door back in.
Was it because you built that
something that you shouldn't have?
Who told you that?
Is that it?
The something?
If I could tell
you the date...
The exact date that
you're gonna die...
- Would you wanna know?
- How would you know?
- Let's just say I did.
- What, are you psychic?
- No, that's not the point.
- Then what is your basis for knowing this.
Hypothetical. Alright, just-just
use your imagination. Alright?
- Alright.
- Okay.
Just accept that there's a world
where I know with absolute certainty,
the exact time of your death.
Now.
You want me to
tell you or not?
Of course, I would.
Who wouldn't?
But.
What if...
Accepting my death
is what causes it,
so the answer is "Yes".
I would want you to tell me,
- But I wouldn't believe you.
- You have to believe me.
Why? Don't we like, make
our own destiny and stuff?
What?
Who are you, kid?
Is that bad?
Oh, hell.
Oh, hell!
- They followed you here?
- What? Who?
Robots.
I've never seen
them before.
John Francis Walker.
You have been permitted to live based
upon your agreed non-intervention.
You are now harboring
a fugitive element.
Release her to our custody
or be extinguished.
You have 1 minute to comply.
- Thanks.
- Don't thank me yet.
Huh!
Wait.
Come on!
Look out!
Go.
John Francis Walker.
By authority of Governor Nix.
This unit has been authorized...
to extinguish your life...
Okay.
Alright, that's enough.
That's enough.
Come on.
Close the door.
Who the hell
is Governor Nix?
Let's go.
Come on.
How is this
a good idea?
Whoa!
Move or sink, kid!
You were actually
prepared for that?
- My hat.
- Leave it.
No no no.
I can't go without it.
It's my dad's.
You're too smart
for your own good.
Your father never understood you,
never supported you.
Now you wear his hat,
as a badge or rebellion.
Right?
No.
My Dad is amazing.
Oh. Wait a second.
We're not...
We're not talking about me,
are we?
Well, we just get you
to your amazing dad...
Pretend this never happened.
Hop on.
- Battery's dead.
- No, it's not.
- Well maybe it's the point.
- When's the last time you tried...
- You know you're not helping?
Get down.
Now.
Wait.
Hello, Frank.
Are you going
to shoot me?
- I'm deciding...
- Could you decide in the truck?
Because we really
should get going.
Wait.
Why, so more
robots can show up?
She's one of 'em.
Yeah, I know.
Are you coming or not?
Move over.
- Frank?
- Not yet.
What were you thinking, why
would you drag her into this?
I didn't drag her into anything.
I gave her a pin.
She did the rest.
Just like you.
Oh, don't even...And where
did you even find the pin?
I was there.
They destroyed them.
Not all of them. I made it
out with nearly a dozen.
So you give one
to a teenager?
Hey, I got a 73 on the Feinberg-
Dusseldorf scale or whatever.
- You got a 73? That's not possible.
- Mm-Hm.
He's jealous because
he scored 41.
Wha... You know what?
I was 11.
Don't touch that!
This is a 1 kiloton detonation,
it is not a toy.
Do not mess with my stuff.
You got it?
- Sorry.
- I didn't begin with her, you know.
I wasted years holding
out for potential candidates.
Potential candidates?
For what?
Oh-ho-ho...
That's beautiful. You still think
you're recruiting, don't you?
Do not ask her any
more questions.
She's gonna do her
countermeasure shutdown thing.
What countermeasure shutdown?
Did you tell her you had a
countermeasure shutdown thing?
- She was annoying me.
- What...? You-You lied?
Get used to that, kid.
One minute, she's promising
you a beautiful future.
Next thing you know, she's
leading it to your house to kill you.
I'm sorry. But time is running
out and you needed motivation.
Motivation for what?
We need to go
back over, Frank.
Back over there?
Yes! Yes! Frank, we
need to go back over.
Good! Great.
That's just great.
You know, "Hey, I got stung by
a bee, let's jump on the hive."
That's a terrible analogy.
That's a fantastic analogy! What
do you know about analogy?
You know you're impossible
to talk to when you're like this.
I am like this, because
you derailed my life! Again!
Frank, it's not personal.
It's just programming.
We're here!
Where are you going?
This is where your wire
station's located, isn't it?
We need to get to
the Spectacle.
- Spectacle?
- Hey. Are you insane?
They know that you sent her to me,
they're gonna be waiting for us.
Fine. Give me the Edison tube
and we'll go without you.
I don't have the
Edison tube.
It's in your bag.
I have X-ray vision.
- When did you get X-ray vision?
- Oh. She's full of surprises.
I know all about her surprises.
Chief among them is this,
she doesn't care about you.
All that charm and the sense of
purpose and the cute little smile.
It's all just software.
It's 1s and 0s.
That's it.
Trust me, when you get
there, you're on your own.
What happened to you two?
He thinks
I hurt him.
No. You hurt a dumb kid that
was stupid enough to fall...
You were many things,
Frank Walker.
But you were
never dumb.
Why don't you just
give me the Edison tube?
- I'm not giving you anything.
- And...
I'm...!
Alright.
You want in? I'll
bring you in. Why not.
What's better than waiting around here and
getting hunted and killed, etc, etc.
- That's the spirit!
- Et cetera?
What's the et cetera?
What kind of cables are these?
The kind that transmit people.
People, like us?
What, like a miniature teleport...
Do I have to
explain everything?
Can't you just be
amazed and move on?
This is all wired to
the dish up there.
Are you-
Are you using satellite?
I know how things work.
Well, zip-a-Dee-doo for you.
Wrap this around your eyes, tight.
- Why?
- Because justice is blind.
Just.
Do it, kid.
You want me to put
this over my head?
- If this sticks on my eyebrows...
- Shut up.
Open your mouth,
tilt your head back.
Awk.
What is that?
Powder.
Will ya back off?
Good to go!
Good. Did you set it
for the tower?
There is still a
receiver there.
Last I checked.
How long ago was that?
25 years ago.
Roughly.
They threw you out too?
Okay guys, killer robots.
Alright. It's gonna be bright,
cold, and really loud.
You're gonna lose 90% of your
blood sugar in 1/100 of a per second
and you're gonna wish
you were dead.
By then, it'll be over.
Don't pee on us.
This sounds spectacular.
Why now?
Why her?
Because she
hasn't given up.
You think she can fix it.
What makes
you say that?
Can she, Athena?
I have no idea.
Let's go find out.
Hold on.
Is this-
Is this normal?
What... is... happen... ing...?
I'm thirsty.
I'm dying.
I think I'm dying.
- I'm dying. I'm dying.
- You're not dying.
There's coke
in the fridge.
Help yourself.
We have no idea
how many are here.
But we're damn sure
they know we're coming. So.
We move quickly, you follow me.
No questions, got it?
- Got it.
- Alright.
Excuse me.
We're in Paris?
Would you stop
being so amazed?
- I thought you wanted me to be amazed.
- I want you to stop yapping.
(French speaker over PA)
Tower's closing.
Oh, hell.
Come here.
Now. You and I are gonna
be on their watch list.
They may not have your facial
recognition profile uploaded yet.
- May not?
- May not, so...
You walk over there, you take
this, you tap him on the neck.
If he's human,
it knocks him right out.
And if it's a robot?
- Hey.
- Then you'll just pissed it off.
Fantastic.
She got guts.
You gotta give her that.
Human!
The French hated this thing
when Eiffel first unveiled it
at the Paris World's Fair.
They thought it was an eyesore.
Eiffel didn't care though. It wasn't
meant to be a monument.
It was meant to find
another world.
Le cat premiere.
Plus Ultra's first four.
They were a
part of all this?
Eiffel, Jules Verne,
Tesla, and Mr. Edison.
They designed this
antenna that we're inside...
Wait, what?
The Eiffel Tower's an antenna?
Now I finally answer your question.
Are you gonna interrupt me?
Yes, Tesla designed the antenna to
observe every kind of frequency out there.
Subspace, trans-dimensional,
you name it.
And, they found exactly what
they were looking for.
And then, Edison tried to
take credit for it,
- because these two hate each other they....
- Frank.
Stay on topic.
Yeah.
There were all these rumors,
of a secret entrance...
the four kept just for themselves,
a one way ticket...
in case of emergencies.
The Spectacle.
You ain't seen nothing yet, kid.
Oh no.
The tour is over.
It's a rocket.
They're coming.
Alright.
Buckle up.
- What'd he say?
- Pretty much what you'd expect.
Tell them to hang on.
WOO...  HOO...!
- Why are we going back?
- We're not.
We're going through.
To another dimension.
So we blasted into outer space
just to get a running start?
This part may
get a little weird.
Casey.
Wake up.
Casey?
Casey.
Wake up.
We're here.
Now what?
You tell me.
I tell you?
This was your idea.
I don't have ideas. I just
find the people who do.
- So there's no plan.
- There's a plan.
You just haven't
come up with it yet.
But, you should
do that soon.
That's just terrific.
Here. Hide this.
Absolutely.
Wait, is that the 1 kiloton detonation
thingy you told me not to play with?
Right now,
it's our insurance policy.
There's a good chance they're gonna
try and kill us right at the gate.
So we're just
gonna stand here?
Well, you wanted to see Tomorrowland.
Here it comes.
Take the bag.
- Frank.
- David.
You look well.
Age becomes you.
Thanks.
You should try it.
I don't know. I think I'll just keep
drinking my shake every morning.
Comes in chocolate now.
Yum.
Hello, Athena.
Started to think you
were never coming home.
Where oh where
have you been?
Doing my job.
Your job?
I'm sorry, were we not clear when we
suspended your recruitment protocols?
I got that since when you
called me bloody obsolete
and tried to disassemble me.
Well, you certainly caused
quite a commotion
by launching an antique
rocket ship out of the Eiffel tower!
Under normal circumstances,
we'd be working overtime to convince
everyone it was just an elaborate hoax...
Unfortunately, for all of us, it
doesn't really matter now, does it?
Why doesn't it matter?
And who might you be?
I'm- I'm Casey
Newton.
And who-
who might you be?
David Nix.
Pleasure.
Well, Frank, it's been
wonderful catching up.
But as we were fairly clear
about the terms of your exile,
and the consequences of violating it,
I have to ask.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I think she
can fix it.
I'm sorry, I...
Her. I think she
can fix it, David.
Wait, what?
I've been pirating your signal.
Every time you turn it on here,
I can see it there.
And it flickered.
The percentage dropped, David.
Impossible.
You don't believe me,
let's go find out, right now.
I'm sorry,
what can I fix?
The world, Ms. Newton. He
thinks you can fix the world.
Is that like a
portal to Earth?
No.
It is a bridge way to Earth.
Welcome back to
The Monitor, Frank.
It's something, isn't it?
Yeah, it's something.
Don't worry about
the light show.
It's perfectly safe.
- Am I supposed to do something?
- No.
Okay, can you be a bit more specific
because fixing the world sounds a little...
Just be yourself.
Gotcha.
What are those?
Flashes of future.
That's a few seconds from now.
This whole tower
funnels energy by tachyon.
A particle that moves
significantly faster than light.
We discovered them
almost forty years ago.
Your physicists are still
arguing over whether they exist.
Oh, dear.
Too late.
So.
On with the show.
We've enhanced the
interface significantly.
There's still functions on
your original algorithm.
You have something
to show me, Frank?
Show me.
Pick a place.
- What?
- A location. Anywhere in the world.
Pick one.
Canaveral,
Cape Canaveral.
Easy.
The Interface is oriented from
your hands to the center of the Earth.
Okay, I got it.
You've trained her, obviously.
I just met her yesterday.
She knows how things work.
How is this possible?
We are millions of
exponential deviances
away from the dimension
you call home.
Frank had the noble idea of building
this machine so that we could
keep in touch.
This is 3 days ago.
Relatively.
That's
space-time humor.
Because tachyons
travel faster than light,
once we harness them...
You can see
backwards in time.
Not just backwards.
You're kidding.
No.
What happened?
Keep going.
Just a little further.
That's enough.
That's enough, kid.
That's my house.
Would have been nice, if Frank
had prepared you for this.
I'm afraid the world is ending.
It is certain, it is
unavoidable, and it is coming.
When?
This is 58 days from now.
58 days?
Whatever caused this, could happen
anytime after the static starts.
It could be a month,
could be sooner.
Still looking for your flicker, Frank?
I know what I saw.
So why aren't you
telling anyone?
The whole planet is gonna die,
and you're just, sitting here?
We're not gonna die.
This is your world, not ours.
We'll be perfectly
fine here.
Then why don't
you let people in?
- Tell her, David.
- Oh, Frank.
All those years in exile and
you still don't understand.
These people are...
They're driven by savagery.
If we told them
about this place,
then that, would
happen here, to us.
Then nothing would survive.
But it hasn't happened yet.
Actually it has happened.
You just haven't accepted it.
Well I don't accept it.
You see that?
Did you see that?
David, I know that you saw that.
That means that there is a chance.
There's at
least a chance.
That went quite well,
don't you think?
What happened?
You're being deported...
again.
Well,
that's Nix for you.
No new ideas.
Apparently your 1/10.000
furball in the inevitability
wasn’t convincing enough
to change his mind.
Be gentle.
You okay?
I know you think somewhere in the
zillions of questions that I was asking you,
you could've said, "Oh, Casey.
Well that's stuff not really the issue
because our future predicting machine
says we're all gonna die."
He did sort of
hinted at it.
This place has nothing
to do with hope.
- It's the opposite of hope.
- Come on, don't say that.
Why not?
You said it.
No wonder you gave up.
That's before I knew about you.
You really...
You really are special.
Why do you people
keep saying that to me?
I'm not.
Why'd you even give me this?
Hm.
You showed me a place, that was
amazing and incredible, and it was a lie.
If you're gonna zap an
idea into people's heads,
you should really make
sure that it's the truth.
Because you can't do that.
You can't just zap...
What?
You zap an idea
into people's heads.
You were pirating the signal.
How?
- What?
- At your house,
all your TVs,
your doomsday room.
You were boosting the feed
from that Monitor thing.
- How did you do that?
- No big deal.
They're running so much power through
it now, a ham radio can pick it up.
It's just a matter of
finding the right frequency.
You grabbed a signal from
another dimension.
From a machine here. That
means it's transmitting there.
What if it's not just
predicting the future.
He's broadcasting it.
When I touched this thing,
for a few minutes,
it felt like anything
was possible.
So then why can't the
opposite happen?
What if The Monitor
is just a giant pin,
but instead of making you think positive,
it makes you think negative. And it...
And it's...
convincing the whole world
to feed the wrong wolf.
We need to turn
that thing off.
It's time
to go home.
David.
- Ah! It's uninhabited and uncharted.
- Listen to me.
But it looks like a lovely
place to spend your last days.
David, The Monitor is
acting as an antenna.
It isn't just receiving tachyons,
it is taking a possible
future and making it like...
Amplifying it, transmitting
it, like a feedback loop.
It's a self-fulfilling prophecy
that is coming from right there.
But it's not just showing people
the end of the world.
It's giving them the idea
over and over
- and over again until they just accept it.
- It's a ticking time bomb.
And we're the ones
that lit the fuse.
We still have 58 days
to try and change things,
but nothing will work as long
as that thing is still on.
Young lady, I'm gonna assume that your
knowledge of tachyonic fusion is a little sketchy.
Shutting it down is impossible.
There is no 'Off'.
I'm telling you what it's doing.
Why don't you care?
Because he's the one
that's doing it.
Right?
Let's imagine
If you glimpse the future,
and were frightened by what you saw,
what would you do with that information?
Would you go to
politicians?
Captains of industry?
And how would you convince them?
With data, facts?
Good luck.
The only facts they won't challenge,
are the ones that keep
the wheels greased,
and the dollars rolling in.
But what if there was a way
of skipping the middle man,
and putting the critical news
directly into everyone's head.
The probability of widespread
annihilation kept going up.
The only way to
stop it, was to show it.
To scare people straight.
What reasonable human
being wouldn't be galvanized
by the potential destruction of
everything we've ever known or loved.
To save civilization,
I would show it's collapse.
But how do you think this
vision was received?
How do you think
people responded
to the prospect
of imminent doom?
They gobbled it up,
like a chocolate eclair.
They didn't fear their demise,
they repackaged it.
It can be enjoyed as video games,
as TV shows, books, movies.
The entire world wholeheartedly
embraced the apocalypse,
and sprinted towards it
with gleeful abandon.
Meanwhile, your earth was
crumbling all around you.
You got simultaneous epidemics
of obesity and starvation.
Explain that one.
Bees and butterflies
start to disappear.
The glaciers melt.
Algae blooms.
All around you. The coal mine
canaries are dropping dead,
and you won't take the hint!
In every moment, there is the
possibility of a better future.
But you people won't believe it.
And because you won't believe it,
you wouldn't do what is
necessary to make it a reality.
So you dwell on
this so terrible future.
You resign yourselves to it.
For one reason.
Because that future doesn't
ask anything of you today.
So. Yes, you saw the iceberg,
you warn the Titanic.
but you all just steered for
it anyway. Full steam ahead.
Why?
Because you want to sink.
You gave up.
That's not The Monitor's fault.
That's yours.
Put them through.
Thanks for visiting, Frank.
It's genuinely nice
to see you again.
- What are you doing?
- Not giving up.
Look out!
- Get the thing!
- What thing!
The thing I gave you
when we first got here.
Arm it!
Casey, the bomb!
- NOW WHAT !?
- Arm it!
HOW !?
Casey!
The bomb?
Where's the bomb?
1 minute to detonation.
- 45 seconds.
- Athena!
Bomb. What do I do?
How do I turn it off?
30 seconds.
You can't.
Ha-ha-ha...
This is not
funny.
Frank, get out of there!
It's gonna blow!
GET OUT...!
Get out of there!
- Close the portal!
- 1.
- Are you alright?
- I'm fine.
- Can you stand?
- Yeah.
Frank!
No.
- What happened? Is she okay?
- I need to get her to a repair module.
Frank!
No one's going
to repair me.
I'm out of time.
I need to tell you
something now.
I'm done.
I'm shutting down.
I'm...
...shutting down.
I'm going to lose sync.
Don't look at me like that.
I finally think it's not...
failure.
I know.
There are things I need to
tell you before the final
Before the automative
program kicks in.
I'm a machine.
I never thought
that was bad
until I see your face
when you found out I was.
I always knew.
No, you didn't.
Systems failing.
Activating last thoughts,
saved for
Frank Walker.
Log 15.
September 1965.
Frank Walker is looking at me in a
manner that is difficult to recognize.
It seems imperative to explain to
him that I'm an Audio Animatronic.
Athena.
But I'm concerned that he
may be adversely affected,
when he finds out
that I'm not human.
He has potential.
I don't want to damage it.
He needs someone
to believe in him.
And I'm fulfilling that need.
He's my top recruit.
Log 24.
October 1965.
I'm having unusual thoughts
towards Frank Walker.
I suspect a flaw in
my empathy interface.
I'm thinking I
should report it.
But I haven't.
I cannot explain why.
Log 78.
April 1984.
Frank Walker has been
banished by Governor Nix.
He says he's lost hope.
And he holds me responsible for
having given it to him in the first place.
I do not understand this.
He says I never will.
Because I do not feel
anger, or disappointment
...or love.
End recording.
I was designed to find dreamers.
I found you.
I lost you.
Until I found her.
Casey.
Dreamers need to
stick together.
It's not programming.
It's personal.
The Monitor.
The bomb is gone.
But I'm not....
yet.
There isn't much time.
My self-destruct.
Use it.
You know what to do, Frank.
How to get this right, this time.
I thought you can't have ideas?
W-Well.
W-What do you know.
What do you know.
Systems failing.
- Frank.
- Yeah.
Do-Do you want to know why you
couldn't have make me laugh?
Why?
Because you're not funny.
You can let me go now.
Goodbye, Frank.
Goodbye, Athena.
Oh, bollocks.
Now, what?
You're asking me?
This was your idea, kid.
Yeah.
You think it'll work?
I guess we have
to make it work.
So, we're making it work.
First order of business.
Get the door back open.
Couldn't hurt to get a few
experienced engineers over here.
- Next?
- Put the party back on.
And print out some
new invitations.
Which brings us to
why we're here today.
A year ago it was all
supposed to be over.
We shouldn't even be here.
But we are.
It isn't hard to knock
down a big, evil building
that's telling everybody
that the world's gonna end.
What is hard...
Is figuring out what
to build in it's place.
If we're gonna do that,
we can't do it alone.
We need all of you.
Frank Walker.
May I ask a question?
- Sure.
- The search parameters you've given us,
while mathematically sound,
are a bit...
undefined.
Could you be more specific, please?
Well, Miss Newton?
You wanna tell our new recruiters
what they're looking for?
Dreamers.
We are looking,
for dreamers.
Anyone who will
feed the right wolf.
So.
I once told your predecessor
that she was nothing but a
combination of 1s and 0s.
I was wrong.
She was much
more than that.
You are much
more than that, too.
So.
Go out there and do
what she would have done.
Find the ones who
haven't given up.
They're the future.
Subtitle created by - Aorion -