A "TEAM AWESOME" presentation
Breaking News!
Incident in Shigure Valley.
Where's Shigure Valley?
National park,
Nagano Prefecture!
Patrol cars,
fire and media trucks are there!
Live nearby,
crazy since dawn...
Roadblocks,
late for work!
Crime rate 32x average.
Murder maybe?
Deserted all day.
My kids go there. What's up?
The Show White Murder Case
In Shigure Valley National Park,
a burnt corpse...
was found by a local resident.
Police state the body was stabbed
over 10 times and burned,
badly charred when found,
trying to identify the victim...
in this abandoned corpse case.
Set up quickly!
Hey, which is what?!
How about cues?
You check on it.
Put 'B' roll in first.
... tourists and locals are shocked,
and the criminal
is still on the loose,
so local residents are afraid.
Had 'ramen' noodles at
Manpukuken.
RED_STAR:
Ordered thin noodles.
Nothing special.
Rating: 2 stars.
What's going on?!
Get to work!
Sorry.
Why are you here?
No reason for you to come.
Sorry, you're right.
Sorry.
- Go away!
- OK.
Get out of here!
RED_STAR: Had ramen at
Aniki Noodles on the way home.
Noodles and soup both awful.
Doesn't know what ramen is.
Rating: 1 star.
Nothing...
Why is the camera moving?
Her husband searched for
her hidden savings.
You know,
I did it hand-held.
To express his feeling
on the screen.
Not needed for
re-enactment drama.
Maybe not...
Risako Kano
RED_STAR: Oh, a call!
What?! Just you.
Pretend I'm asleep?
Yeah?
Hello. You awake?
Yeah.
Sleeping?
Better wake up now.
This news is
too important for texting.
What?
Today,
for the first time in my life,
RED_STAR: Drives me crazy.
Today,
for the first time in my life,
police questioned me.
Speeding...?
RED_STAR: Police questions?
Interesting.
Speeding...?
RED_STAR: Police questions?
Interesting.
Wasn't so trivial!
I did nothing wrong.
Didn't you hear?
Shigure Valley incident.
Huh?!
You must know!
You work in TV news.
RED_STAR: What's the
Shigure Valley incident?
You must know!
You work in TV news.
RED_STAR: What's the
Shigure Valley incident?
Not in charge of it.
RED_STAR: What's the
Shigure Valley incident?
You're not in charge!
Just do as told.
Director doesn't do as told.
You're a director now?! Wow!
1 new TWEET
You've come a long way
since university!
Stabbed body
found in the park.
You've come a long way
since university!
Stabbed body
found in the park.
Stabbed body murder?
Yeah, that's it.
I know the case.
You live in Shigure Valley?
It's a national park,
no one lives there.
That's not why I called.
I know the victim.
Really?!
RED_STAR:
Knows the victim?!
We can't deal with this by texting.
Well...?
Police came to my office today.
They look at you differently.
Like being trapped in their gaze.
Then what?
They told us the name of the victim.
Noriko Miki.
I told you about a
beautiful superior at work, it's her.
RED_STAR: Victim's name is...
Can't make it public!
I told you about a
beautiful superior at work, it's her.
RED_STAR: Victim's name is...
Can't make it public!
Oh, that woman...
RED_STAR: 1st feature.
24 years old...?
Oh, that woman...
RED_STAR: 1st feature.
24 years old...?
Somebody resented her beauty?
RED_STAR: 1st feature.
24 years old...?
Don't be stupid!
Noriko wasn't a sleazy beauty.
When I say she's pretty,
people assume resentment.
RED_STAR: 2nd feature.
Very pretty.
people assume resentment.
RED_STAR: 2nd feature.
Very pretty.
Fairy tale beauties
like Snow White and Cinderella...
RED_STAR:
Ignore her idea of beauty.
Fairy tale beauties
like Snow White and Cinderella...
also have pure hearts.
But real world people
think they're bad.
RED_STAR: Don't care about
your beauty theory.
But real world people
think they're bad.
RED_STAR: Don't care about
your beauty theory.
Isn't that strange?
That's true. So...?
Actually, Noriko and I...
were partners.
What?! What?!
Huh?
No, not partners like that!
Training partners.
For the first year,
new employees...
RED_STAR: Shocked me!
Just a work partner.
For the first year,
new employees...
RED_STAR: Shocked me!
Just a work partner.
are paired with experienced
staff for training.
RED_STAR: Shocked me!
Just a work partner.
We call that a partner system.
I felt insecure,
lacked confidence.
Challenging to be
Noriko's partner...
Let's do our best.
I'll work hard.
Every day was like
a princess and a slave.
Like Marie Antoinette
and her servant.
My future seemed bleak.
Our featured product.
Snow white Soap
I see.
You'll have Snow White skin.
But within one week,
I was glad to be Noriko's partner.
What's wrong with you?!
Worthless new employee!
I'm sorry.
Boss, get mad at me, not her!
She did nothing wrong.
Noriko wasn't just gorgeous,
she was also kind.
She treated me to meals
at gourmet restaurants.
And often gave me presents.
The CD I'm playing is from Noriko.
Serizawa Brothers.
RED_STAR: Victim worked at
"have Snow White skin" soap company.
Hear it?
RED_STAR: Victim worked at
"have Snow White skin" soap company.
It's a nice song.
RED_STAR: Victim worked at
"have Snow White skin" soap company.
Yeah.
Trio of violins and piano...
What did the police say?
Well...
That Noriko's death occurred
last Friday night. That evening...
our section
held a farewell party.
It was for Mayama.
Noriko had a fever,
so went home early.
RED_STAR:
Death occurred Friday night.
RED_STAR: Victim attended party,
left early.
About that murder?
Wow!
Not about ramen today!
But it seems she
didn't return home.
The next morning...
RED_STAR: Want to declare
I've quit gourmet reviews!
The next morning...
RED_STAR: Want to declare
I've quit gourmet reviews!
her burnt body was found.
RED_STAR: Want to declare
I've quit gourmet reviews!
Hey, don't share this
on Twitter or your blog.
Why not?!
Be responsible
about this incident!
RED_STAR: Shared already,
too late!
Be responsible
about this incident!
RED_STAR: Shared already,
too late!
I know that.
So...
Do you know the suspect?
Well, actually...
Huh?
RED_STAR: Is this my big break?!
Shigure Valley
Charred Remains Identified
She is gorgeous!
Victim's name and
photo released.
Beautiful!
Snow White soap staff...
found charred black,
but is really Snow White?
I use Snow White soap!
It's shocking.
Wasn't Snow White
going to a castle ball?
That's Cinderella.
RED_STAR: So this is the...
"Snow White Murder Case".
Recording it?!
Don't worry, not your face,
it's from the neck down.
You can approve it before use.
Alright.
Risako Kano
Colleague #1
So,
the killer?
Well,
Mi-chan...
suspected that
Shirono is the killer.
Look, this is her.
Miki Shirono.
You could say...
she's rather plain looking.
Yeah, she is plain.
Right.
Shirono joined the company
when Noriko did...
Hold on!
Who's Mi-chan?!
Everybody is named 'Mi...'!
That's true...
Mi-chan joined when I did,
real name is Emi Mitsushima.
It's like this,
Noriko's family name is 'Miki',
meaning '3 trees',
Noriko Miki.
'Miki' Shirono...
means 'beautiful'...
'princess in the castle'.
But actually,
Noriko Miki was really the
'beautiful princess in the castle'.
Yeah.
Hired together,
they were compared.
Probably that upset Shirono.
When visitors came,
their boss would...
Shirono, prepare tea.
Noriko, please serve it.
He should have told
Noriko to prepare and serve!
What's more,
Mi-chan says Shirono dated
Section Head Shinoyama.
But they stopped dating
just after spring.
It was because of Noriko.
So, to Shirono,
her boyfriend was stolen by Noriko.
Shirono was seen
glaring at Noriko,
by Mi-chan.
So the motive was jealousy?
But...
Shirono didn't seem to feel that,
treating Noriko the same afterwards.
I also had trouble with Shirono,
I dropped the mug
that she treasured.
Mug?
It had a big 'S' on it,
maybe that stood for Shinoyama.
Satoshi Shinoyama.
You should have seen her face!
Repressed feelings...
might make someone
snap from stress...
on the murder night.
That evening,
Shirono attended
a farewell party.
Are you alright?
I may have a fever.
You don't have to stay.
No, I owe a lot to you, Mayama.
You're that kind of person.
Only you'd say such kind words.
I feel the same way.
That was a great party!
Now let's go to karaoke!
Excuse me,
I'm going home.
Mayama, thanks for everything.
It was great knowing you.
Same for me.
Bye, I'll be leaving now.
Good night.
And I'll...
also leave now.
Really?
Good night.
She should have been more grateful.
Shirono was your partner,
so owes you the most.
She's just that kind of person.
Let's go!
I'll give you a lift.
Thanks.
A frequent visitor
saw Noriko get into Shirono's car.
Really?!
Hold on!
Now it's just fantasy.
Besides,
why would Noriko fall asleep?
Sleeping pills or something?
Something?
When did she take them?
Then our colleague
saw Shirono...
run into the train station,
and take a Tokyo express.
Really?
Shirono's car was found
in pay parking by the station.
She hasn't come to work since then.
No way...
Called to say that...
her mother was dying,
but that was a lie.
There's been no contact since then,
she simply disappeared.
Must have done it.
Well, we just don't know.
Actually,
to be honest,
it might be best if she did it.
If it was a stalker or some
unknown man that killed her,
I'd be afraid to go out,
and wouldn't sleep.
That's not everything,
Mi-chan...
Mi-chan is incredible!
There were thefts at work,
and Mi-chan thinks
Shirono may be the thief.
Risako's former boyfriend...?
'Mi-chan'
Emi Mitsushima
Colleague #2
What?!
You're not?
When Risako...
talks about guys,
it's always you, Akahoshi.
Maybe she still likes you?
How about you?
Mi-chan,
too many questions!
What's that mean?
Risako said something?
That I like to gossip?
Whenever rumors spread at work,
everyone blames me for it.
It's really tough.
It's obvious I don't gossip.
I want to ask about Miki Shirono.
She's your partner, right?
She's the killer.
Definitely.
I'll do my best.
A s for Shirono,
nothing unique about her...
Not being unique
is what makes her unique.
She dated the Section Head?
Yeah, I noticed something.
The box lunch Shirono made...
was exactly the same
as Shinoyama's.
Who confessed their love first?
How did it all begin?
There's someone I like,
please tell me how to begin an affair.
How about preparing him lunch?
Try it for 3 days.
Didn't I sound just like her?!
Yeah, I suppose...
From what I've seen,
I think Noriko didn't date Shinoyama.
Maybe Shinoyama liked her,
or just had a delusion.
But Shirono did begin to
break down from that time.
I can't compete with Noriko.
If someone stole your lover,
would you stab and burn them?
Well, normal people wouldn't.
Shirono is not normal.
Last summer,
our section held a social charity
BBQ in Shigure Valley.
A s organizers,
Shirono and I went ahead to set up.
Cops will catch you!
Don't worry.
I know where the speed traps are.
She chuckled,
with a weird grin.
Her face really
did not look normal then.
Did anybody see Noriko's pen?
I heard about that theft.
I just saw it here...
Noriko's pen was stolen.
It's worth about 5, 000yen!
It was produced for a minor
violinist that she liked.
Serizawa Family?
Serizawa Brothers.
Amazing!
TV people know everything!
That group seldom has concerts.
That's right...
You didn't put it somewhere else?
No...
Shirono had a weirdgrin
at that time also.
It was the day before the murder.
Are you alright?
I may have a fever.
You don't have to stay.
No, I owe a lot to you, Mayama.
You're that kind of person.
Only you'd say such kind words.
Not at all.
I'll give you a lift.
It's OK, I'll walk home.
Your pen...
I have to return it.
Huh?
She stole the pen so
she could get Noriko into her car.
And to steal the pen,
she had previously
stolen other things.
It was all part of a
carefully planned murder plot.
Don't record it.
Satoshi Shinoyama
I'll leave now if you do.
Colleague #3
Satoshi Shinoyama
Of course. Sorry.
It seems female staff
told you some things,
but don't believe them.
Gossip and fantasy
have ended up sounding true.
It seems that you were dating Shirono?
That's not true,
we weren't dating.
Last fall,
"Snow White Soap" became a big hit.
It used to be called "Heavenly White",
only the name changed.
Even so,
suddenly we were really busy.
I often had to work all night.
Ouch!
Are you alright?
Sorry.
I felt dizzy.
Lack of nutrition...
Can I bring you
a box lunch tomorrow?
No, please don't bother.
My parents sent so many vegetables,
I can't eat them all.
You'd be doing me a favor.
As if we're lovers...
Because you need nutrients...
Well, at least let me
pay for the ingredients.
No thanks,
then I would be under pressure
to make a proper lunch.
I'll bring one tomorrow.
I have to say no,
I really have to.
How is your health?
You need nutrition on the weekend, too.
This is scary...
I just dropped it off while shopping.
Sorry to bother you.
Not at all.
Actually,
I have a girlfriend now.
So no more box lunches...
I see.
I understand.
I'm relieved that I don't have to
worry about your health now.
Oh...!
Is your girlfriend...
Noriko?
Yeah.
I thought so.
Now I understand.
You lied so that...
I didn't lie!
I was dating Noriko.
She came after me.
But it ended after about 3 months.
She said that she met someone else...
It happens a lot.
You can't imagine...
how it is to date
a lovely woman like Noriko.
Fumiaki Ozawa
You can begin.
Colleague #4
Fumiaki Ozawa
I saw Shirono on Friday night,
over there.
The party ended at 08:00 PM?
Right.
I saw Shirono here
about 09:00 PM.
I drank a lot at the party,
so waited here for a taxi home.
But there weren't any.
... the next train departing
for Tokyo is at 09: 10 PM.
Please board now.
She was really running!
She held onto her big bag
like a rugby ball.
Serizawa Brothers
RED_STAR: Info update!
Victim is Serizawa Brothers fan.
Who are they?
Huh?!
Related to Masaya being shoved down?
Masaya?
Who's that?
Masaya Serizawa.
Someone shoved him,
injured his hand.
Not just his hand,
injured all over.
RED_STAR: Now in Shigure Valley!
On the spot report?
Nothing at that place now.
Masaya's injured hand...
may end his musical career,
it's a critical situation.
Let's pray for his quick recovery.
RED_STAR: 30minutes
by car from town to park.
Faster if familiar with road?
Different time.
Crime was at night.
I'd drive it in 20minutes.
On a mountain road?
RED_STAR: Suspect 'S' emerges!
Suspect is opposite type to victim.
Motive is stolen boyfriend.
Definitely the killer.
HARUGOBAN: Don't report here,
maybe tell the police?
RED_STAR: Kingfisher?
RED_STAR: Nearby tree charred.
This is so pitiful.
Why?
If not for you...
I could have been happy.
Mirror, a mirror.
Princess Snow White...
gone forever.
RED_STAR: Right now,
I am the only person...
in the world who's closing in on
the heart of this crime.
HARUGOBAN: Don't go any further.
Or it will include you.
Curse will kill you.
TWEET
Regarding the Shigure Valley murder
on the 12th of this month,
the woman was stabbed dozens
of times, and the body burned.
The victim was Noriko Miki, 24,
cosmetics company employee.
Like the symbol of their
popular "Snow White" brand,
she was lovely by anyone's standards.
Already one week since
the incident occurred,
but investigators
have made no progress.
But our enquiries...
Victim Worked at
Cosmetics Company
show that from 3 months earlier,
unusual thefts had occurred
at the company.
The first theft was cake
from the office fridge.
Colleague of Noriko
The first theft was cake
from the office fridge.
Colleague of Noriko
A piece of cake with a chestnut...
was kept for someone
who'd missed a party,
but only the chestnut remained.
It started with dessert
from the fridge,
but feminine pads in lockers,
items on desks,
even the company's pride,
"Snow White" soap, were stolen.
A s part of this,
Noriko suffered a personal loss.
Colleague of Noriko
Noriko's pen was stolen.
It was worth about 5, 000yen!
Rumors in the company said
someone with a grudge against Noriko...
had committed the thefts.
Colleague of Noriko
Might make someone
snap from stress.
Colleague of Noriko
Suspected that
'Ms S' is the killer.
'Ms S'
A certain woman
was mentioned at this time.
'Ms S'
A colleague of Noriko, 'Ms S. '
She's rather plain looking.
Nothing unique about her...
Noriko was very attractive,
while 'Ms S' was uniquely plain,
so superiors
treated them differently.
Probably that upset Shirono.
'Ms S' had to make tea,
but Noriko served it to visitors.
Although there hadn't been
conflict between them,
the situation totally changed
this past spring.
'Ms S' had dated a male
employee some months earlier...
Her boyfriend was stolen by Noriko.
"Noriko Stole Her Boyfriend"
They said 'Ms S' was a good cook who made
a box lunch for him every day, however...
when we interviewed him,
he told a different story.
Male acquaintance of "Ms S'
when we interviewed him,
he told a different story.
Male acquaintance of "Ms S'
It's true she made lunches for me,
but I don't recall dating her.
Male acquaintance of "Ms S'
I wanted her to stop,
it was a real nuisance.
Perhaps only 'Ms S'
thought they were dating.
After that, he became
involved with Noriko.
A colleague said this about
with 'Ms S' said at the time.
She said,
"I can't compete with Noriko".
A frequent visitor saw Noriko
getting into the car of 'Ms S'...
on that night Noriko was killed.
And just after
the time of her death,
a male colleague saw...
'Ms S' run into a train station.
Male Colleague of 'Ms S'
She was really running!
She held onto her big bag
like a rugby ball.
But where was 'Ms S'going?!
She took the next day off,
lying that her mother was dying.
Since then,
her whereabouts is unknown.
That's what happened...
Do you use this soap?
Snow White
No, I don't use it.
It's very popular,
lots of TV commercials.
Yes, and after that company
office worker was murdered,
the Internet refers to
"The Snow White Murder Case".
There's even a fan site
for the victim.
Noriko Dates Mr D,
Thefts Begin!
Thefts began...
Noriko Dates Mr D,
Thefts Begin!
just after 'Ms S' was dumped?
Yes, they did.
But we don't know if that
is related to the murder.
Only the victim
had an expensive item stolen?
That's correct.
The pen was rare,
produced for a violinist she liked.
So there was hostility between them?
No, not particularly.
Just asking, but...
could she pick up the victim by 08:00 PM,
drive to the scene of the crime,
stab her and set fire to her,
and then arrive in time for
the express train at 09:10 PM?
Is that schedule possible?
Mr. Akiyama, can it be done?
Well, let me see,
Mr Akiyama
Former chief Investigator
Well, let me see,
I'm not familiar with that area...
Possible.
It is possible.
But we still don't know...
- that 'Ms S' is the criminal...
- It's just a theory.
Perhaps 'Ms S' can provide information,
so police are trying to locate her.
I hope she is found soon.
She probably knows something.
Commercial break out, 90 seconds.
RED_STAR: My news
segment was a big hit.
Do more than food reviews!
HARUGOBAN: So,
you work for TV news?
Great re-enactment.
Shaky camera showed emotions.
Saw it!
Lots of info not on other news.
Waiting for update!
Damn! Missed it!
Want to see today's update!
Great job!
Probably you know where
Show White killer is?
What's up?!
You said you'd ask before using it.
Seemed like everyone
in my company...
thought Shirono was the killer!
RED_STAR: OK to Tweet her name?
Everybody knows already.
Be responsible.
Company was crazy today!
Should have asked!
RED_STAR: Shut up.
SA CO, don't name her.
Better stop?
Don't know she's killer.
She did it.
If she didn't do it,
she'd say so.
Suspect name 'Shirono'?
Snow White soap >
Shirono > found real name!
Vulgar...
Got name too!
First initial 'M'!
Ms M Shirono?
Insensitive.
Basically, she did it.
Unfair.
In the end,
motive was jealousy.
OK being dumped
for beauty.
Man also to blame?
It's really taking off.
NORI-MI: Name 'Shirono' used.
Is that 'Ms S'?
RED_STAR: Use imagination.
TWEET
NORI-MI: I know Ms Shirono well.
1 new TWEET
Is accusation acceptable?
HARUGOBAN: You are cursed.
I won't hold back, destroy you.
REPLY
RED_STAR: Who are you?
Indiscrete.
Sue him!
Find his name.
Fool to reveal
TV things here,
must be just a part-timer.
You're trash.
Doing a lousy job.
RED_STAR: I won't reveal more.
NORI-MI: Bad attitude,
I'll sue for damage to reputation.
Minori Maetani
Classmate #1
I'll begin by stating that
this is a letter of protest.
Since college,
I have been a close friend of...
Miki Shirono, identified as
suspect 'Ms S' in last week's TV news.
We lived in the same
dormitory in college.
What do you mean, 'do it'?
'Do it' means 'do it'!
Did you 'do it'?
I don't understand...
I mean...
Had sex?
Is it OK to do that before marriage?
We nicknamed Shirono "En-chan",
for 'endangered species'.
She loved "Anne of Green Gables".
She's a good cook,
so if we had to work late,
she'd prepare little meals
to leave in our lockers.
Such a kind person couldn't kill.
Sweetie Food Service!
I support my good friend,
En-chan.
That news report is all wrong.
I don't trust the source.
... but only the chestnut remained.
En-chan loves chestnuts.
... but I don't recall dating her.
This guy is the biggest liar.
I met him before.
He is Shinoyama, right?
A real nuisance.
I met with En-chan last winter.
Welcome!
Oh!
See you.
Bye.
Excuse me.
You like him.
Why not tell him?
I think he wouldn't
be interested in me.
You're a good cook,
so why not prepare him lunch?
Try it for 3 days.
That's what I advised.
Dating him?!
Yeah.
The result of your advice.
She had a great smile when happy,
we called it the 'En-chan Smile'.
I'm sure she had that smile
when she told me,
so I felt really good.
She said Shinoyama
was grateful for the lunches.
He likes beef and eggplant,
but dislikes smelt and tomatoes.
Would you mind?
She said that...
they did it...
And he liked to be licked
between the 3rd and 4th toes.
She told me such things by phone.
Would I make up these stories?
Since then,
her whereabouts is unknown.
That is what worries me most.
A ware of my sensitive skin,
En-chan often kindly sent me
hard to get Snow White soap.
If somehow she did
get involved in a murder,
she might commit suicide from guilt.
Even as the criminal,
please locate her quickly.
Bring her back to me.
She is my dear friend.
You tweeted on the Internet,
you idiot!
No, I didn't do that.
Of course not.
Don't get carried away.
You'll be fired!
I know. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
NORI-MI: My friend Miki Shirono
was suspected of the murder.
Sent a protest letter to TVprogram.
Miki Shirono,
graduate of 'T' Women's College?
NORI-MI: That's her!
Are you also a graduate?
Miki Shirono,
'N' prefecture, 'F' Senior High School?
NORI-MI: Probably.
Are you a local acquaintance?
Stupid director's face.
Miki Shirono,
'K' City 'A ' Junior High School?
'K' City 'N' Primary School?
NORI-MI: I don't think so...
Aya Shimada Machiko Ozaki
Use this for TV?
Classmate #2 & #3
Aya Shimada Machiko Ozaki
With blurred faces,
and distorted voices?
That's great!
You asked about Miki Shirono?
What she's like?
Here's our yearbook.
Brought that?!
- Future stuff...
- Brings back memories.
"Person Most Likely to Commit Crime".
She's 2nd.
No way!
Miki Shirono.
Look here.
"Will good things..."
"happen in college?"
Miki Shirono.
Seems that good things
didn't happen in college.
She was in my group
in cooking class.
She'd chop off fish heads...
That's scary!
She was amazing.
And meat fiber...
She really knew
how to carve meat.
- She knew?
- Yeah!
In Junior High School,
she was known as...
'Curse Shirono'.
The soccer team captain
was really good,
he could become
a top local soccer player.
He was fooling around one day,
like school kids do,
and he kicked a rag as...
the classroom was being cleaned,
and just by accident...
the rag landed on Shirono's head.
About one week later,
that skilled soccer player,
broke his leg
in a car accident.
Car came from the side,
I slammed on the brakes,
but they failed and I got hit.
My leg was hit hard.
It was strangely twisted.
Shingo Eto
My femur was broken.
Classmate #4
Shingo Eto
It took 3 months to heal.
They told you it was a curse?
Such people are disgusting.
There was no curse,
brakes were disconnected.
But I think Shirono...
disconnected them.
The entire body...
had been stabbed dozens of times,
and then burned?
Trigger may have been...
because of me.
The rag I kicked
landed on her head,
her face went totally red,
must have felt insulted.
To be honest,
I really regret it.
It must be about 14 years ago.
At the Myojin Shrine over there...
See it?
Kinuko Yatsuka
Maybe you can see it...
Local Resident #1
Kinuko Yatsuka
In that group of big trees over there.
Can you see it?
Inside there is...
the shrine to the Myojin deity.
That place caught fire.
Maybe just a rumor,
but probably true,
that little Miki started the fire.
It wasn't arson or playing with fire,
anyway...
I heard it was the Curse Ritual.
In Primary school,
Yuko and Miki would go together,
and my daughter said that
they'd have a Curse Ritual ceremony.
Probably Yuko is in her house now.
Actually...
Yuko never leaves her house,
she's always there,
she's a recluse.
Yuko Tanimura
Local Resident #2
We did it.
Talk about the Curse Ritual is true.
We made a human-shaped cutout,
shoved a pin through it,
and set fire to it.
I won't talk if you don't play,
Yuji Akahoshi.
Around that time,
me and Anne...
Anne?
That's Miki Shirono.
Anne asked me to call her that.
Anne used to call me Diana.
Anne of Green Gables
Just kid's playing...
It's hard to talk about it.
The same on Twitter,
people use a
creepy handle name.
Like KEROPPA...
Anne thought of making
paper figures to burn.
The Curse Ritual...
was for me.
A s a child, I was said to be
the prettiest girl in town.
Akahoshi, don't leave!
I'm just beginning.
But a girl named Akane...
changed everything.
The 'yu' in 'Yuko'
looks like the character 'ta'!
Yuko Tanimura
The 'yu' in 'Yuko'
looks like the character 'ta'!
Yuko Tanimura
It's true!
'Yu' and 'ta' look alike!
Mix up 'Yuko' and 'tako',
she'll be 'Tako'! 'Octopus'!
Her name is 'Octopus'!
Octopus Tanimura!
I blushed in shame,
and everybody
called me Octopus.
Octopus!
Octopus! Octopus! Octopus.
Isn't that awful?
Even the home room teacher
called me Octopus.
Except...
Anne,
who didn't.
Yuko, let's go to school.
From this window,
Anne's house can be seen.
There was a scene in
"Anne of Green Gables".
At night, we'd put a
candle on the window sill,
and pass a cardboard sheet
up and down in front of it.
When I was bullied,
Anne would often do that for me.
To say I'm your best friend,
I am...
always here for you.
Magical Fairy
"Pin up a human-shaped figure
at a sacred place".
"Make sure no one sees you".
"This will cause your
mean classmates..."
"to have pure and
generous hearts",
"and they'll become kind to you".
Akane Yatsuka
No! No!
I said not to use fire!
That shrine
burned to the ground!
Don't use fire!
Never use fire!
And don't use a flashlight!
Miki said she won't meet.
What?
After that,
I never met with Anne again.
I didn't hear until later,
but our parents argued about
who'd set the fire,
both sides decided their kids
would never meet again.
I loved Anne so much,
I reread the "Anne" book.
I cried.
In the book, Diana was
Anne's only friend.
Not Diana,
I was Gilbert...
About the Curse Ritual ceremony,
was the human figure this size...?
Enough!
It's game over.
Sorry to intrude.
Hey!
Yes?
You think everything...
I told you is true?
Huh? You mean some was untrue?
Listen carefully.
People have false memories.
They only tell things
that benefit them.
Don't miss the main thing.
You got it?!
RED STAR.
SHIRONO
Kozaburo & Satsuki Shirono
Parents
Miki was...
Kozaburo & Satsuki Shirono
Parents
a very kind...
and good daughter.
She never rebelled,
to the point where...
we wanted her to be
more self-assertive.
Asking about the Myojin fire?
Yes...
If even...
a fire links someone to murder,
everyone could be a killer!
I know.
It wasn't true that I'm dying.
But everyone...
has told a lie like that.
We are so sorry!
Please try to...
forgive our daughter!
See our shame!
Try to forgive us.
She was a kind, good girl.
That girl...
would never commit
such a crime.
... has told a lie like that.
We are so sorry!
Please try to...
forgive our daughter!
See our shame!
Try to forgive us.
Akahoshi...?
Is everyone telling the truth?
Huh?
It's OK.
Just forget it.
Yeah.
Mystery #6:
Where is 'Ms S' now?
To get info about where 'Ms S' went,
we visited the village of her family.
She may have the power to curse,
Former High School
Classmate
She may have the power to curse,
Former High School
Classmate
her Junior High classmates
believed that.
The words "power to curse"...
don't fit our era,
but are crucial when discussing 'Ms S'.
And he kicked a rag as...
Former High School
Classmate
And he kicked a rag as...
Former High School
Classmate
the classroom was being cleaned,
Former High School
Classmate
the rag landed on the head of 'Ms S'.
That boy had been selected
for his soccer skills,
but one week later
was hurt in a car crash.
When 'Ms S' heard that...
Former High School
Classmate
When 'Ms S' heard that...
Former High School
Classmate
She laughed.
Former Classmate of
'Ms S'
Awful.
Former Junior High
Classmate of 'Ms S'
He had potential for pro soccer,
Former Junior High
Classmate of 'Ms S'
but works in local real estate
and coaches junior soccer.
Former Junior High
Classmate of 'Ms S'
To be honest,
I feel responsible.
Her heart of darkness
is the result of...
what I did.
Heart of Darkness
Further enquiry
revealed a startling story...
of when 'Ms S'
was in Primary school.
The Myojin Shrine caught fire.
Neighbor of 'Ms S'
She played with fire
at their revered shrine,
it was terrible
when it burned to the ground.
Neighbor of 'Ms S'
I heard it was the Curse Ritual.
"Curse Ritual"
Primary School Classmate
of 'Ms S'
We talked to the classmate of 'Ms S'
who did the Curse Ritual with her.
Primary School Classmate
of 'Ms S'
We made a human-shaped cutout,
Primary School Classmate
of 'Ms S'
shoved a pin through it,
Primary School Classmate
of 'Ms S'
and set fire to it.
Primary School Classmate
of 'Ms S'
It seems rather strange to put a pin...
through a human
figure and set fire to it.
Neighbor of 'Ms S'
Wasn't that recent murder
similar to the Curse Ritual?
Neighbor of 'Ms S'
Our reporter interviewed...
Family Home of 'Ms S'
the parents of 'Ms S'.
We are so sorry!
Parents of 'Ms S'
Please try to...
forgive our daughter!
Parents of 'Ms S'
The missing 'Ms S'
is the only one who knows.
We can only pray that
the case will be solved quickly.
Well, now it involves the occult.
Perhaps childhood memories
had a significant role...
at the time of the murder.
Killed during a flashback
of the Curse Ritual?
Such cases have occurred.
But 'Ms S' may not
actually be the murderer...
Her age during the Curse Ritual?
She was 11 years old,
Primary school Grade 6.
I don't know...
myself anymore.
She always felt victimized
and heldgrudges.
Shirono lives at 221-12...
She always felt victimized
and heldgrudges.
Kill Snow White.
Miki Shirono colleagues.
Is this...
Miki Shirono.
Miki Shirono?
If I could,
I'd return to that night,
and change it.
I will...
try to write about myself.
Not too late,
to leave here after that.
Miki Shirono
To Whom It May Concern
Nagasawa is a typical rural town,
surrounded by mountains.
That's my home town.
In Primary school,
my best friend was Yuko Tanimura.
Yuko, let's go to school.
The prettiest girl in town.
But she was bullied,
and always looked sullen.
Akane Yatsuka was to blame.
Akane, you're so pretty.
You're lucky.
I'm just average.
Yuko is more pretty.
Yeah, Yuko is also pretty.
Those few words by someone
changed everything.
Akane had such a cute face.
If Akane hadn't put others down,
she would have
received lots of compliments.
In that respect,
she was just like Noriko Miki.
Ms Higashiyama was our
Grade 6 teacher.
Taichi Suzuki.
Here!
Oh dear,
a strong name,
but a weakling.
Until Taichi graduated
Senior High and left town,
he was called 'Weakling'.
Next,
Miki Shirono.
Let's see the
'beautiful princess in the castle'.
Here.
Too bad,
wrong name for you.
Yuko Tanimura.
Here.
Next...
Teacher...
Call her 'Octopus'.
Octopus, nice to meet you.
Octopus!
Oh my, you turned purple,
like an octopus!
Octopus!
I hate my name.
Not just you,
I'm 'beautiful princess...'
Akane didn't have to
tell the teacher.
Don't cry, Yuko.
When you feel bad...
When you feel bad,
go into a fantasy world.
Like "Anne of Green Gables" did.
We made up names
for our fantasy world.
Best Friend Alley.
Sleeping Fairy Mountain.
Knock-knock Road.
Stardust Lake.
See, bad things disappear
in a fantasy world, Diana.
Anne...
But shy to be 'Diana'.
No,
from now on we'll say
'Anne' and 'Diana'.
I'm here.
I'm here for you, Diana.
Akane Yatsuka
Even after we grow up,
will she be like that?
In the end,
will girls like Akane always win?
There will...
be some.
Huh?
After we grow up,
good things...
My first love was in Junior High.
Give it a try?
Wow! Great shot!
I'm sorry.
I hate you!
I won't forgive you!
It was like them.
Anne and Gilbert.
Anne wouldn't easily forgive him.
But that led to them
being interested in each other.
Sorry about that.
I'll never forgive you.
I'm sorry.
Not forgiven!
I didn't let him off the hook,
so he'd come to me daily,
saying he was sorry.
I guess there's no choice,
it's OK.
I forgive you.
One week later,
on the day I was
going to say it was OK...
He had an accident.
A car hit his bike,
his broken leg needs 3 months to heal.
On his way home from
practice yesterday,
perhaps speed was a factor...
Why'd you come?
I have the right to be here.
Because...
I haven't told you yet,
that I forgive you.
Thank you.
Even if everyone
is against you,
I'll be on your side.
During that happy daydream,
I'm sure I was smiling.
Even so,
Will good things happen in college?
Miki Shirono
I kept believing...
Will good things happen in college?
Miki Shirono
good things would happen.
Minori Maetani was my best friend.
I see...
You're dating him.
So,
did you do it?
Do 'it'?
I mean...
Had sex?
I don't want to...
talk about such things.
Amazing...
you did it first.
Unbelievable!
Huh?
En-chan, tell me about it.
Tell me, I'm your best friend.
She was...
my best friend.
But then,
I met Noriko Miki.
I'll work hard
to learn my job quickly.
I'll do my best.
I'm Noriko Miki.
I can't beat Shirono's name,
'beautiful princess of the castle',
but I'll work hard to be
as good at my job.
Shirono, prepare tea!
Noriko, please serve it
to the visitors.
Yes.
You're so fashionable, Mayama.
Not at all.
I just buy at a few shops I like.
Good morning.
Morning.
You like it?
I just bought it.
Morning.
I'm sure she intentionally
bought the same outfit.
Mayama didn't...
wear hers to work again.
This looks good.
Don't start it like that,
Shinoyama!
I'm sure it was from that time that...
Noriko started checking up on me.
She's gorgeous.
Most beautiful woman I've ever seen.
Same here.
Number one.
How about you, Shirono?
Well...
The most beautiful one is...
my childhood friend, Yuko.
Who?! What's she like?
Primary school classmate.
Beautiful black hair,
fair complexion.
Like the "Snow White" princess.
Ouch!
Are you alright?
Sorry. I felt dizzy.
Lack of nutrition...
Can I bring you
a box lunch tomorrow?
Really?!
That would be great, thanks!
Thank you.
Perhaps...
Actually...
No problem,
you don't like the taste...
No, that's not it!
The food was great.
It was really good!
If possible...
I would be very grateful
if you'd bring lunch tomorrow.
Of course.
I'll bring lunch tomorrow.
I just dropped it off while shopping.
Sorry to bother you.
Not at all.
Why don't you...
come inside for a while?
Right there!
That's it, right there.
Between the 3rd and 4th toes.
Did you play sports?
Yeah.
Soccer.
Even if everyone is against you,
I'll be on your side.
Let's go camping,
just the two of us.
In Shigure Valley.
Alright.
Huh...?
I can't accept any more
box lunches.
Why not?
My girlfriend...
doesn't like it.
Girlfriend?
In spite of that,
I still had one important thing.
The Serizawa Brothers.
The sound of their violins
was heavenly.
I chanced upon them
on a music site.
They seldom had live concerts,
most people hadn't heard of them.
The brothers were violinists.
The younger one, Masaya,
who played viola,
had eyes that reminded me of Diana,
prettiest girl in Nagasawa.
Good things happen.
I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry.
I think that Noriko Miki
probably realized it at that time.
Serizawa Brothers?!
Yeah.
Who are they?
Sounds like a comedy duo.
You fool, Mi-chan.
They're great musicians.
You know them?
No...
Is that a Serizawa pen?
They're popular,
even fan club members can't get these.
Although dumped by Shinoyama,
I acted as if nothing happened,
but she was upset.
Serizawa Brothers FAN SI TE
Masaya and a woman?!
No! A fan?
I won't forgive her.
I'm shocked!
I hope it's not true.
She recently joined fan club,
Noriko Miki.
It's true, we're dating.
Record company friend of Dad
let me watch them recording.
Masaya came over
and talked to me.
And Shinoyama...?
Shinoyama?
I never intended to date him.
She took everything I had,
still not enough?
If I'd stopped liking
the Serizawa Brothers then,
this may not have happened.
Did anybody see Noriko's pen?
I just saw it here a minute ago.
That was the day before the murder.
Shirono,
I want to talk to you.
Huh?
It wasn't me.
I would never steal
anything from anybody.
No, it's not about the pen.
I already know who took that.
Also took "Snow White" soap,
I'll take action at some point.
Eh?!
Who took it?
Our talk isn't about that.
There's a concert in Tokyo
tomorrow with the Serizawa Brothers.
Yeah.
Others groups will also play,
tickets are sold out.
But they rarely perform live,
I really wanted a ticket.
I have one ticket.
Masaya gave it to me.
But I have a cold,
so can't go to Tokyo.
Can you go instead of me?
Front row seat.
You sure?
I'll bring it tomorrow.
Thank you!
But tomorrow...
What time do the
Serizawa Brothers appear?
At 11:30 PM.
Found one!
You'll have to take
the 09:10 express train.
But Mayama, your...
Never give up, from now on.
In every way.
Good morning.
Nice outfit.
Thanks.
I feel better now,
so I'm going.
Masaya intended
for me to use that ticket,
and would notice if I didn't go.
But I already...
bought an express ticket.
I'll buy it from you.
I'll bring you a souvenir.
Is a mug OK?
Risako broke the
Serizawa Brothers cup you had.
Excuse me...
Perhaps it's because of Noriko?
Yeah...
I thought so.
To be honest,
I've had problems with her also.
Feel free to confide in me
if you want.
Shirono,
let's go to that concert!
Huh...?
Her plan was quite simple.
I have cold medicine.
It really works.
Not poisoned?
Forget it...
No, just joking.
I'll take it.
I won't get drowsy?
Not at all.
Thanks.
It makes you really drowsy.
I'm usually OK, but get drowsy with it.
I may have a fever, after all.
The best medicine is beer.
Drink up!
I'll also pour her lots of beer.
Noriko can't drink much,
so would sleep in a car.
When she does,
take the ticket from her bag and run.
Chopstick?
Excuse me!
Chopstick, please.
Sorry, I have a cold,
will leave early.
I guess I won't see you again.
Goodbye.
I can't do it...
You were supposed to
go to the concert.
Why just put up with things?
You always do.
Hey...
I'll give you a lift.
To the station.
It's OK, I can walk.
Also...
I didn't give you the express ticket.
Somehow,
drinking beer...
Yeah?
Really woke me up.
I'd been feeling sleepy.
Really?
Thanks.
Also, the ticket.
No...!
I forgot it!
How could you?!
Ridiculous.
Sorry!
There's enough time to get it.
I'll just buy a ticket.
Let me get out!
Be right back.
Hurry!
Express Ticket to Tokyo
What'll I do with Noriko?
Just leave her in the car.
There's pay parking by the station.
She'll be mad when she wakes up,
but it serves her right.
... the next train departing
for Tokyo is at 09: 10 PM.
Please board now.
Masaya!
Please stay back! Stay back!
Masaya, over here!
Stay back, don't push!
Careful,
please don't push!
Don't push!
Get back! Get back!
Masaya!
Are you OK?!
Serizawa Brothers
FAN SI TE
Masaya's left hand injured?!
I was there, but didn't see that.
He was shoved and fell.
So many fans!
I saw the woman do it.
Report it to the police.
It's a crime.
She ran away quickly.
Her eyes looked scary.
Regarding the recent incident
of the stabbed and burned body,
the victim worked at a
cosmetics company,
and has been identified as
Noriko Miki, 24.
Miki was at a company event
on the previous night of the 12th,
but she left alone and went missing.
Police determined that
on that night a car was seen...
in which the victim, Miki,
was riding.
Police are looking for the car,
and into the victim's company...
Loner type went crazy.
Shirono did it.
Evil witch.
She won't escape.
Track her down.
Death penalty.
Terrible to burn the body.
Must be a weird psycho.
Want her dead.
Die!
Goodbye. Thank you.
Regarding the Shigure Valley
murder on the 12th,
in which company employee
Noriko Miki was stabbed and burned,
we have breaking news.
This afternoon a suspect
was charged with murder,
she is Risako Kano, aged 23.
Kano was initially arrested
for possible theft of company goods,
during questioning she
admitted murdering Noriko Miki.
Police suspected
Risako Kano of murder...
You'll have Snow White skin.
Really?
You should use it.
Especially you.
Why did you take this soap?
Actually...
Worthless new employee!
I'm sorry.
Boss, get mad at me, not her!
She did nothing wrong.
- It was good.
- Thank you.
Thank you for always treating me.
Treat me sometimes...
Today...
I received my bonus,
so please let me treat you.
You don't need to treat me.
When you're a
new employee's partner,
treat her the same way.
Inaba,
I saved you some cake!
Who's the one that
ate Inaba's cake?!
It must be you!
It wasn't me.
Someone eat it by mistake?
I don't know.
Nasty! Who did it?!
Sure it wasn't you?
I didn't eat it!
Who ate it?!
The suspect of the thefts,
Risako Kano,
said seeing others overreact to...
the ongoing thefts
relieved daily stress at work.
Did anybody see Noriko's pen?
I just saw it a minute ago.
Anyone seen a brown pen?
Haven't seen a brown pen?
I know who stole it.
What are you saying?
Well,
I wonder what I'm saying?
The threat of being exposed
made Kano feel uneasy,
and she focused her attention
on none other than 'Ms S'.
Excuse me...
Perhaps it's because of Noriko?
But 'Ms S' thought only of
going to the violinist's concert.
Wait...
Kano saw an opportunity
to skillfully exploit 'Ms S'.
But how extensive was her plan?
Why?!
Kano wasn't satisfied with stabbing.
She knew lighter fluid from the BBQ
was still in the car of 'Ms S'.
Lovely...
Hello...
Hello? Hello...
Furthermore,
to mislead the enquiry,
she contacted a university friend who
was a TV news temp worker,
leading him to believe
'Ms S' was the criminal.
It might be best if she did it.
Have criminals really become
so terribly selfish these days?
Regarding the motive for her crimes,
Kano said...
I didn't want to lose my job.
Just for that?
Yes.
That was her response.
Stress built up over time.
She testified that she was
afraid of losing her place.
Losing her place...
It seems possible the suspect
suffered from a complex.
No, Kano graduated from a
prestigious university.
The company superior said Noriko
may have had a junior college complex.
Some years later,
Kano could've become
Noriko's boss?
That is possible.
Regardless, to put it simply,
she was very shallow.
Total lack of ethical values.
It leaves us astounded.
It does.
We have a statement...
Yes...
Due to our failure to do research
during production,
an innocent person became a suspect,
we apologize.
We offer our humblest apologies.
Moving on, our next topic...
That's all?!
All over?
Apologize to Shirono!
I'll totally object to this report.
Shouldn't watch such stuff.
You watched too!
Why are you sitting around?!
Don't need to be here.
Akahoshi went to apologize...
Of course he did!
You're also in trouble.
Poor Miki Shirono.
We're on her side.
NORI-MI: Now you support her.
But I'm the one that believed Shirono.
You also suspected her.
You weren't her close friend.
You revealed her full name.
Masaya is not injured.
'Love Affair'
of Masaya and victim...
also seems to be untrue!
Masaya wrote to fan club,
"I never met Noriko Miki."
Internet exposes the truth.
Internet accuses falsely.
Shirono Family Funeral
Tough she wasn't here
at the time of death.
Did her best.
Right.
Please cooperate...
Miki...
Miki. Miki...
Miki!
We're sorry, Miki.
I'm here.
I'm here for you, Anne.
Even if everyone is against you,
I'll still be on your side.
Anne...
Your memories,
your tough times,
the fantasies you've imagined,
no one can take them away.
Not enough!
That's not an apology!
Get down on your knees!
Well...
For what I have done...
I am...
I am very sorry!
I humbly apologize!
Report by
'RED_STAR' Akahoshi: 1 star.
Works at TA G Pictures.
Contract ending.
Fired soon!
Low wage job!
Lives at #205 Libura,
8-9-4 Higashi-machi...
His stupid face.
College indie film.
Why not find real killer?!
Why no personal apology?
Akahoshi is low-class.
Weird he posted to Internet.
I always doubted them.
Yuji Akahoshi
No Connection
Ouch!
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
I didn't hit you?
I wasn't hit.
Excuse me.
It's just that...
Huh?
A bad thing happened,
and now...
somehow...
it's like I'm not myself anymore.
Oh, excuse me.
Why am I telling this
to a stranger...?
Excuse me...
There will be some.
Huh?
Good things.
They'll happen.
Akahoshi, that was...!
She is...
Huh?
It's OK.
It's nothing.
Mao INOUE
Go AYANO
Misako RENBUTSU
NANAO
Nobuaki KANEKO
Shihori KANJIYA
Erena ONO
Mitsuki TANIMURA
Shota SOMETANI
Katsuhisa NAMASE
Original Novel by
Kanae MINATO
Screenplay by
Tamio HAYASHI
Music by
Goro YASUKAWA
English translation by
Paul BRYDEN
Subtitle timing, editing and
additions for this version by
famitsu1
Special thanks to
ikeda69
Directed by Yoshihiro NAKAMURA