The world has been divided into eastern and western side
Empire ruled the west side of Queen
He opposed the eastern empire
Queen of the west side of the world in order to achieve a unified
Intelligence activities to the countries of the aristocracy having to give
The presence of the 'Queen's beongyeon' had to be called
Other news
Last night, a new dawn in the industrial district fourth angry mummies have been found in the fluid
Three weeks before the mummies found in the earth's forests to fire together this fluid is the fifth of seven
Make the case for gender specific announcement is still not secure
Ipsilateral home country (某 国)
"Her Majesty's command-fire succession necrosis investigate the case your mummy"
Considering trafficking 'goods' I'm too rough handling
Where do these women?
What are you doing sleeping?
Why have these pictures, right?
You're usually not a bitch!
The majority of those who mummified
Fancy shape you into contact with during his lifetime!
What is stamped on the envelope flux that picture?
I do not know!
Rather, what's that eye!
Excuse me!
Who are you?
Oh ... I'm so sorry!
Now that I have the gene, but Poe
Master the ...
Go pick up
Come!
Master?
What's that?
Kill them!
One bag!
Stop.
What are you from?!
Me?
I'm just a butler!
Butler is such a mundane murder possible?
What are you talking about?
Poe, who is a deacon in Copenhagen
It can not even yijeongdo What can I do?
So
Yireomyeon What are you going to do?
Sebastian.
Sebastian?
One name that used to be grown attached!
There's a pretty room! Lady!
Hooh! Ohdeuahyi (Iris exotic disease) is?!
Farley expensive rare elsewhere because the main course!
Speak!
Where do I put him in the hands of directors?
What are you sleeping?!
Hey! How long will you play?
There do not look so good place to sleep?!
Hit me so much?
Uh-oh!
Recent performance of the gun's good too!
Group is much wrong with the old!
Lie!
Master has given valuable clothing
Dirty!
When playing you? Fool!
As I say, Master
And was excellent!
And watching it for a while as he looks
I think not bad!
Really ugly and wonderful!
If you are really good with a small soft!
Who are you talking to me?!
Hold it!
I do not know this guy ... die!
What do you want me to do?!
Do it! Arm hurts!
But Master! I might go near to die?!
Stop. 're Gonna break the contract?
Ridiculous!
I am the son of a faithful servant from the day!
If you want to
I'll do anything!
What a strange saying? This monster guys!
This does not achieve my goal
It's impossible to eat my soul!
Of course!
And son killed someone deserved
It can not be me!
So fast ...
Muppet!
Told you please tell how?
That's an order!
Ask me!
One bag!
Shut the fuck up!
I will take away my lord!
The game did this so funny!
You!
This guy's 10 times!
Not got it 10 times! So my ...
I have a man-made money etc.
Not interested!
Did you not say?!
I ...
Demons and
Butler said
I'm gonna ask again!
What's in that envelope deceived?!
Last chance!
Say what you know!
There's no such thing to say!
You guys! Will see in hell!
Yeah! Then it's game over!
If you are already viewing the hell!
That's no way to pray!
There's no such thing as god!
Does not save anyone!
So Kiyoharu son!
Evening meal was prepared by a French cook
This morning hoping've prepared desserts
Either way I do tonight?
Dessert!
One bag!
Kuroshitsuji
Continued from the 19th century nobleman prestigious Gen Poe
The son of the family head in the morning Kiyoharu
Early morning starts with tea!
This is a house maid Lynn
For the life of me can not understand that the behavior is repeated
Snow is not bad
We have noticed that their hair geolkkayo not?
Sorry!
The rest I
Creep-year-old (杀 意) I feel
This is a house of Tanaka Steward!
The genus mug
Lemonade!
Good morning!
This is my master! Count Kiyoharu Gen Poe!
This fragrance is a ... silronti today?!
Yes! The Blue Lady for Higgins ...
Only 17 years old and the best way ipsilateral face as toy makers also have a phantom president
'The Queen's beongyeon' of
Surge back if not dignified society
Seem to have a pretty depressed scissors!
It's always dreams!
It's done!
We hope all my dreams, but also ...
Yes!
Rather cool because you do not see your face!
Little unlucky!
Huh?
No!
If you still dream of ...
I was in a place hard to die!
I know!
Just for you!
If suicide at will!
If you commit suicide, so I can take the soul!
Peace!
Never letting go until the purpose!
To do that you dont look like this to the!
That's no way think of any more!
Game the decision to go! Sato!
Sato immediate Secretary Charles Queen B
The brain and its management abilities at a young age!
I really scared! Count Kiyoharu Gen Poe!
Praise enough! He'll tell me!
'Devil's Curse' and another new victim is out!
Anthony Campbell, our country's embassy
State as before yo mummy found in localized
Remained in the field, the card is!
Picture is also 'evil' is
This is the fifth of eight?!
As victims of foreign embassy
Now it has become a hot topic around the world
Some of the media in the 'Devil's Curse' it might be said against the wrist!
'is also a victim of the fifth consecutive embassy killing 08'
Therefore, in the near future of the factors are gathered around the east and west
Ordinance of the devil fight seems to have decided to conduct my!
Dullness.
Either
Damage to the embassy of the country more than crazy
It is not right you can bonchae!
Her Majesty is rushing to solve it!
Tell him to know he would sire!
The beginning of this one
Three weeks before the mummies found in one ward
Since then, the phenomenon of human living while mummy is still going on Tuesday?
World, 'the devil's curse "seems to be the case because the called!
You give people the power to dry up first?
I do not know ...
Juice in the weaving skills but
Most of the dead man is alive, and that human trafficking
Contact thing is definitely not!
What the hell had it?!
And to acquire the police investigation?
One bag!
Foreign Affairs Bureau of Security Police
Excuse me!
've Been waiting for! Talkie and group parties!
Give you relief. Participated!
Wait a minute!
Now I'm trying to write an important letter
Love Letter ... is not routinely!
Found in warehouse pier mob found in the fluid, such as those who report ...
Wait a minute!
To entrust such a redneck cop back in the fight, right?! 0:21:37.320,1193:02:47.295  Nekoma security commanders bear Arts
This is the devil's curse "is no longer the case ...
Dressed in a black tailcoat with witness information man
Alone killed 12 people on stage!
Alone?
This site features!
Please look at the data here!
No way ...
'' Queen's beongyeon 'doubts about the' West side of the Queen can spend 0:22:18.200,1193:02:47.295 'beongyeon' is
Received the Queen's commands to run the affairs assassination or 'nobility of darkness'
This means uneven and dry well into the general public does not care agent.
Exist in this country!
But that's ... thats just a rumor?!
'The Queen's beongyeon "If this country as a real dangerous!
Must be removed!
Eopne permit can only guess!
Yes!
Nothing that you have not listened to me throughout!
Excuse me!
I certainly have not heard anything!
However, party and military-talkie!
To remove beongyeon
The owner should not go unnoticed!
Phantom four
So this quarter, the 'doll business' as such a big hit
Toys jeoyeonryeongcheung towards increasing the sales forecast by 5%
Thank you!
So concludes the executive board!
Abandoning busy day immersed in playing house, hit me?
I'm so sorry!
Did you know something?
Tell us if you have any questions at any time cooperate! Mr. Kiyoharu!
Thank you! Aunt!
In the past
Phantom of the prestigious west side hive nobility Count Ernest
'Gen Poe' settled place names have been building our country!
Gen Poe goes by many generations, manufacture and sale of toys became wealthy!
Walking business, but the work of the ever-widening
Heat third generation family head of Gen Ali and his wife Erica Poe
Events being killed suddenly occurred to anyone!
Kill?
Yes!
Doknyeo of munam inchae siohri missing since the day!
Just six months after the event
There I said Hi Kiyoharu discussion is illegitimate
Man dressed in a tailcoat with fairy suddenly appeared
The family business is now followed by Kiyoharu is received!
Such 'outsiders' I bet this is good for him heir?!
Poe originally going to Copenhagen
Followed by a man outside the family head of the clan that rules are not receiving!
This is the voice Kiyoharu susanghi Initially there was only a
DNA confirmed the feelings!
Erika's sister, the only relative of the Wakatsuki hanae
Kiyoharu guardian to hold up
The co-management of Kiyoharu and hanae Gen to further expand the business of Poe
Disgruntled human being is gone
'Count' is a random Kiyo inherits a day now!
"Aristocracy of darkness' is ...
The defeat my Battle.net?!
Anthony died on the streets of the ghetto
According to the testimony of witnesses
Mummies have been angry at the moment
Just before his death, and what you have done, where the
Not yet known
This country is a result of the police investigation
But how these things always get to do?
Queen's beongyeon also
Useful 'dog' because there raising
Continue to
Thank you Anthony Campbell's research!
We look forward to!
Fourth generation
Why is the cat so good?
And talk only know!
I'll go out!
Prepare any car you want today?
Small car!
Anthony will be repatriated today's fluid!
From now on we will head to the place where only the promise
5 minutes is probably buying time
Enough!
Hello, my count!
I waited!
Why do I have to move the body, but did she know?
This is not to know, paying!
Carrying data in order to fix it I did to you!
You will be asked to purchase the only remaining thing!
Out of the way!
I got it! You got five minutes!
It leaves the market!
Cuban mountains, too! It 's amazing in times like these!
Yijeongdo is evidence?!
Time!
Muppet! Forgot singe this ...?
Why is the hidden part of the chief
I know that I'm not the wine country, right?!
Fluid between the teeth of the blade market that remains is
Without a cigar cutter
'd Cut the teeth of the evidence!
However, after seeing a well tailored suit and polished shoes
This man is a gentleman significant
That such behavior in
I can see quite a drunken state!
So full of mouth alcohol at least once or twice a
I can predict the chief is polished!
Devil quite eager to play detective theme works!
Poe is the butler of self-Gen
How should I also did not yijeongdo?!
But of course you think your son noticed?!
Butler damn!
Is a trademark of wine, you would know anyway?!
Said the 75 year old Chateau Bo Nuerburg
Find cigars and wine distribution channels!
Valuable trademarks of either!
One bag!
Exclusive club?
It is the only club in the surface everywhere
Some members do not go out in the basement containing the President
Maybe there seems to be a secret meeting!
Canvassed all distribution channels
The cigar and wine
Gathered in both places where there were only two
Anthony then there just before the mummy?
Maybe!
Yeah!
The invitation to the party is the envelope deceived?!
Get me a list of the participants of the party!
Here!
Someone will need to infiltrate the introduction!
The members are aunt would be the one to know!
It'll ask you somehow!
Let's talk tomorrow!
So contact us now to take hanae's it!
Meet outside the meeting room in the heart gets heavy!
I also pathological natgarim days!
As the family head proudly Gen Poe simply touch!
How come, first give me that blunt face throughout!
Lady is disrespectful!
Boy looks happy, even throughout the lies!
Now! Laugh!
Get off me!
I originally ...
Since that day,
I forgot how fun and smiling!
Sorry!
Really great food, too! Sebastian.
I got it! If you get an invitation, but a gun?!
Sorry to ask this, but!
Trying to find what's happening?!
'm Always reticent important part!
Your mother is my sister!
I just like the heart of revenge!
So am going to cooperate with you! I will not suck to be useless!
Aunt!
Akashi please!
Matgyeoman us!
The enemy must!
Yeoreomyeong'll be fine, so even acquaintances!
But as far as
Relative to enter the venue, you need a coat es
A good man who could?
Sorry!
Committed employees are examples of my house it!
That's awesome!
Anything is possible, but you always think yours!
Clearly this versatile limbs!
But King is me!
This is my command, it does not move unless you severely tamed!
One bag!
Yes! Not bad!
So please do not look at that!
Rinssi! Please! Please!
Do not mistake!
Yes yes!
It's an invitation!
Watch out!
What's going on?!
The Stamping ...
Father and mother were killed when the
Mr. Kiyoharu?!
Aunt! The organizer of the party?!
President of Epsilon Pharmaceuticals
Responsible for the development of new drugs in the Ku Ya Zhou Shinpei!
Let's go! Rin!
Yes!
Investigation of the pharmaceutical drug factories you Epsilon!
One bag!
What is it? This is?!
Politicians around the world famous business executives embassy ...
This club is hell?!
Shinozaki!
Arms dealer known as the path of darkness!
The deal is rumored to be a terrorist organization, and!
You! Given the well with today!
The role of the curator in charge of the party called the Ku Shinpei jaws!
Please enjoy slowly come tonight!
Here!
Muppet!
Rin! Told you to stay still?!
I'm so sorry!
Leave alone, but never told my lord, because
Seeing as how back!
How can I help you?!
Am I glad to see you too!
Maybe I wanted to say
You have to chase!
Mr. Cruz Shinpei jaws that?!
Yea, but yes?
Nice to meet you! I ...
You already know!
Phantom's young charismatic president mean?
No, that ...
And
Queen's fold!
What are you doing?!
Stop.
Jabber is an empty!
Epsilon pharmaceutical chemicals plant
Jeoran He's ...
I see it ...
I've found!
A look here!
Now research shows the performance was lonesome!
Shinozaki jaws and coo ...?
They are against the law, I developed a drug addict!
To test a new drug gajindago tempted to do a private meeting
Had fun together!
So, as long as they experiment
Let us show to watch the best security!
So now waiting for a new drug that you share it!
Completed at the end of this long study of the ultimate drug!
Necropolis The name is Moses!
Do not hurry!
This is the way the system Necropolis enjoy!
Evaporation of the liquid has flowed out of the capsule
The components of the drug release in the air!
Just to absorb the air you will go to heaven!
To climb the stairs to heaven How are you feeling?
Irritating than any medication?!
Yes!
You know you are
Rumor Reclast's famous words 'Devil's Curse' is the identity?
Bleeding from the nose is going first
Then, in the ears
Finally, bleeding from the eyes!
After rising to a maximum heart rate
At once angry mummies!
Evaporation of the liquid has flowed out of the capsule
Until it loses its effectiveness is the approximate time of 15 minutes!
Is only one way you live!
It is the antidote of the Sith Necropolis!
Just for you!
Life is available, but only one grain
The brain is very likely interfere with others!
In order to survive in a healthy state
It is to eat at least two pills!
Oh!
Starts bleeding from the eyes evidence that the kingdom of heaven is near!
Please hurry up!
Anyway, it is impossible to divide human beings are hurt!
Dropping others their own way to survive, but do not choose one person!
Check it a look!
It's like a microcosm of the world!
I could get a good test results!
If the system and antidote Necropolis
We can dominate the world of horror!
This is the formula for making it!
What You've got to be kidding!
Muppet!
- Do you muppet warrior! - Somebody!
Muppet! Muppet!
Muppet!
Rin! Come on!
Are you okay?!
The glass is broken, my God!
Stop breathing!
As soon as possible!
That son of a bitch!
Do not be ridiculous!
Let's go! Sato to call!
One bag!
'The Devil's Curse Is the identity of a drug called Necropolis system!
Medication?
Perhaps this is a target-ku jaws before leaving the store
The market system and handed over to the device Necropolis!
Then put the evil hidden in secret cards
The target market for the device in the suction system and the Necropolis.
No! No!
And despair is lost breath!
This set of cards was the devil!
Mummies will have finished!
So heukmak the Ku jaws?
No! He was murdered!
Will be using her arms dealers!
Ku system to order the Necropolis jaws Shinozaki is just what must be killed!
That the arms merchants in the back
Drumsticks are filled with a sense of urgency technology and money are extremely low!
This will be suffered by a nation stupid!
Peace!
Shinozaki will go immediately to see!
Get ready!
One bag!
Muppet!
What is it?!
Sebastian's son met with police minutes from me!
Ordinance today I can gather around a factor of!
I would like to avoid trouble!
Who can blame them?!
Have a safe trip.
It boasts!
One bag!
Security special irradiation
An exception is the presence in any of you!
The exception to this is recognized among police organizations Place your own!
Shinozaki boss
Strange! No one!
I can go to the now empty!
Meanwhile ... these three people will take care of you!
Knock yourself out!
Slowly ...
The margin is only now!
I miss right now unbearably doegetjiman
Might be hard to come back!
Coming your way!
Yes!
Into the interrogation attention?
Questioned?
Ah! Sorry!
Looks like time is absolutely no condensation do it!
Deliberately killing on the sheet!
Killing power to remove without leaving traces, Ethan?
It has! Master!
Muppet!
Rin! What are you doing?!
Son told to leave alone
I learned!
Also you ...
Rin!
Sheet murdered right at the moment!
Muppet!
Shinozaki?! What's going on? Heukmak this guy ...
Yeah!
It was questionable from the beginning!
Leave a criminal purpose of the devil card
Events were gorgeous!
If the only purpose of the drug development
You do not have to do that!
It's to raise the attention of the world!
Then why did not I kill!
To me, to Her Majesty beongyeon
I have to convey Shinozaki heukmak events!
Will not deliberately kill me!
That means using the system heukmak Necropolis hurry to carry out large-scale terrorist semin it!
The threat gathering place for the world's attention is ...
Ordinance today I gathered around the factors that can!
The timing of
In addition to the threat of the Sith Necropolis Ordinance No.
Will not appeal to the world stage!
Traces of the building concealed the person is gone, as kkumimyeon
Shinozaki doubt anyone's gonna crime!
The firm
Suspected of complicity with the terrorist organization because of
Necropolis system went beyond the hands of a terrorist organization, people are aware of
World tremble in fear!
It's really the perfect sacrifice!
Muppet!
Stop it!
Come on!
Give me the gun!
Rin!
I'll create a gap between them!
Since childhood to keep your gekkeum of Gen Poe was raised!
My family has lived for generations so!
So
Please do not hesitate that!
Siohri girl!
Rin!
You ...
The Master and his wife not to keep that
Stolen from Miss
I was going to die!
But ...
Came back!
To take over the work of beongyeon
One from the appearance of a man!
Me not cleaning dishes
Keeping a lady had hired!
The grace
Only now can reward!
Lin ...
Was much taken care of!
Come on!
Enshrining the noble destiny's dark!
Is to be prepared!
Sebastian's!
Why here?
Muppet!
Aunt!
Kiyoharu!
First president of the Ordinance as soon as possible!
Ordinance No.?!
Be sure to save our valuable employees!
Immediately after it was made chairman of the Ordinance?
Offers me!
'We must get valuable employee!' Said
The word grateful!
So ...
Has been prepared, right?!
Kings wedges since last night I was in the cathedral began Ordinance
Citizens of countries with representatives of international organizations and wake up and pray
The expense of the solemn atmosphere around
God! Are you seeking my soul from death,
During the life of God in the light of the walk in front of it
God! Please have mercy on me!
Mercy on us!
Where you have to rely on my soul!
Length wrong!
No! That's right!
I have been called to God's heavenly!
God had done everything for me to
God left me in the sky to obtain your
Please cut trees below me trample
God of mercy and good faith has left
Detonator?!
Already seen, right?!
This is ...
Yes! Necropolis system!
I've been wearing a mask, you would not see!
What are you doing?!
The next 30 minutes.
Within one kilometer radius of the mummified humans!
Shake the world is going to be a large-scale terrorist clear!
're Then spread this photo!
Hyeojun to disturb you, thanks to this site
Shinozaki a criminal plan to mess doeeoteuni
Her Majesty's done everything did change was the plan!
You!
Oh, yes!
I think that is because of the snow shone
Sebastian is now
Ordinance in accordance with the instructions to obtain lean toward zero, right?!
Not move unless your command
Looking like strict way there!
The 'devil' is
I know!
You are in charge of the curse Gen Poe signed pledge!
Soul for the devil, right?!
But
It is scary to kill you lost!
Relevant that the father and mother were killed
I am deprived of all
So then I sold it!
The soul!
For revenge!
Jukeulsu is not!
'm Resigned to not clean!
Pangeot soul to the devil far so good!
But ...
Should not think of it as me!
Will be looking ... mean?!
We will return!
Sebastian.
You! Why here?!
Be sure to save our valuable employees!
Immediately after it was made chairman of the Ordinance?
Offers me!
'Offers me' What is the true meaning
Free to act to protect the owner would be asked!
So the president has not go Ordinance No.
Information network of its own particular place is here!
I see indeed!
That you won ...
Thought!
Gravity constraints placed on the literature, we have seen the lab up ...
No matter how other western India erikseo
Locate the person about to take sihwangje Xu Fu
That the body of mermaid legends Immortal eat
It was all about immortality!
This means that the fire bulsayak Cruz studied jaws!
I ate in their white lab medicine
If you ate the same drug was!
Sorry!
Although it is not about immortality
You can stay young itgie
Can expect the effects of netting makes it clear!
Then the Necropolis system?!
's A by-product of this medicine?
Cruz originally commissioned by the jaws by the hanae
The fire was started to develop bulsayak!
Son's parents have been killed long before!
The study is a critical raw material reached
Only to extract the girl in the living enzymes and hormones can!
The optimal combination was sought during
The growth rate of the cells significantly faster creating substance is accidentally completed?
It ... 'Devil's Curse' is the identity?
Then the women were in the warehouse
About the ingredients?!
Customs of the clan is cursed too!
I was your father's wife!
Did you know?!
Poe's family head to be a Gen beongyeon the
Our wives and sisters to meet either be fixed off
It is ... I was selected
I was happy!
But anyway, bloody clan!
One day is aimed at Gen Poe incident was attacked!
Sacrifice, paying me and my stomach was a baby!
I can not bear children twice became the body!
Can not give birth to a successor immediately discarded human Manda!
Instead ... you were my wife's mom!
Lie!
No way to select and practice than I!
You look like the guy on purpose ...
Father was not someone who could do such a thing!
I think my sister's face looks happy until the seizure lasts happen!
So I thought!
I'd rather not have children can have
Having his body is not never die!
And
Insisted on such a silly human customs, dies
I have family head me!
He knew all this, a liar, right?!
My goal is eternal life!
Strangely when taking this medicine seizures stop!
The irony did he?
You the same thing!
I should not have been born!
What is really in the human
Toward pleasing me a lot!
You killed my father and mother, you?
Yes! Been disturbed there!
Kill them!
One bag!
Sebastian.
He is the body's ability to maximize the drug raised the art to it!
God created a miracle could naelsu art devil?!
Silver wedges to kill Dracula side effects that have never been!
What do you think? The taste of the sword made of?!
A species with such a humble
Please do not treat together!
Is he all right?!
The soul is killed danghamyeon not get it?
Death devil junk?
Fool your own! Antidote ...
It!
That can not be!
Here!
We will return!
This reversal of the tide!
Akashi!
In looking for what was going on?!
Sonbeoreut resemble the owner is bad anyway!
Uh uh hate!
The only thing that can defeat me now!
Help!
The antidote to our vault!
Drugs have been imported from the factory!
I do not need it! Anyway, since this
I'll say to you eaten soul
Help!
I did not kill your family!
The total of
I killed my father and mother
I saw the eyes!
I just gave help!
Beongyeon was your father!
'll Think I'm by myself up here?
Mr. Wakatsuki hanae this is!
Necropolis during the planning system?
The assassination of the organization's stakeholders beongyeon I got asked to cooperate!
Ipsilateral to the darkness that huge criminal organization controlling it!
All day he's the boss of the organization's heukmak!
I had no choice!
If you do not obey me ...
Teach the identity of the boss!
I really do not know!
And Ali beats or something?!
What do you think is it?!
Purpose of achieving more than likely not be
This woman is an exercise to make use of!
Not only about the two pills!
I know!
But ... you can do this, you know!
Catch!
Thank you!
Survived it! Survived it!
What a fool you are!
Altogether
Were you lying?!
Now is not the story of the lies!
Murder of parents to teach heukmak sipeodo
I really do not know!
I'm sorry!
You! What?!
It is a little experiment!
Experiments that?!
Ahead there is only two pills capsule
Humans are greedy and want some action
Just
Unfortunately, that is not the antidote genus
Necropolis was stained red with the blood of my system!
Only one
Symptoms not continue, so soon
Act like it!
Master!
You can not even delay the tip!
Immediately hanae's mansion
God! Please listen to my cry!
Call you at the end of the world!
When frustrated ...
So what do you do is count?!
Mothaetjyo goal is not achieved yet?
I know!
Indeed in this situation
I did not help others, right?
The deacon then the password ...
One of his birthday?
Perhaps his father's birthday?
You can not achieve revenge?!
Really all right?!
Father! Mother!
I'm sorry!
I can count where you are
Please become a strong wall!
Sebastian.
Maybe I
Nash fluff, paying the owner to do!
Moment of self-chosen death
Not bound by
Father's date ...
Everything started the day!
Is the game over?!
Whilst for other people to choose death
But labor is reduced!
This can take the soul of the son!
Who can blame them?!
This is also way out of his or her choice!
False to pretend that their going to say?
Does not achieve the purpose of the dead!
O lovely owners!
Why do not you're fooling yourself!
The fact is I'm not wanted?!
To save someone
Throwing his life to the human form!
I'm expecting somewhere in the human heart!
So you
'm Sitting in the press in the world!
No!
Tinged with self-interest
Is it for money or their lives without hesitation to kill.
I know it
Human beings!
The devil is in the past
I've never heard of was an angel!
Too high above
In hell.
Been the devil ...
No matter what story do!
Nothing What?!
Antidote!
Why?
There would be no obligation to help
Take the soul of the son is now
Not funny!
More slowly locked in dark black soul must be nourished
The heart is made to eat!
Risk?!
This drug is
'Devil's Curse' identity?!
'The Queen's beongyeon is alive and well - from Nekoma'
Muppet! One kind!
Are you sure you want to ask him a question?!
What is it?
If you did not feed me antidote to the then
What do you think was your son is?
Why do it?!
Come to think of it at the moment
It felt like you save me?
Than human
It means that the devil is the duality is more!
Conventional and
Cruel and ugly
To seem more demonic than a demon!
I just like!
I filled it in ugly!
It's a human!
It's human Sebastian.
So, I say!
Is your very own!
Do not betray me, your very own!
Never!
One bag!
Sebastian.
Here! Until I fall asleep!
Always
Master's by!
Flowerbed!
Do you have a life
Until then,