Xem Phim Online HD Nhanh Nhất Tại VIPHD.VN
[NEW PRESENTS]
[A M TREE PICTURES PRODUCTION]
[SIDUS HQ]
[EXECUTIVE PRODUCER KIM WOO TAEK]
We're your average high school friends
who swore to a lifetime of friendship.
Even though it wasn't under any special
circumstances where our friendship began
it was still special to us
in our own way.
Ahem... ahem.
Ahem...
[MEET ME IN THE SCHOOL BACKYARD.]
- Did you fondle So Min's chest?
- No.
I didn't fondle her chest,
but I just stood there and touched it.
- You must be mental.
- Is that a question?
You think that was a question, you asshole?
Hey, it's not like we're kids anymore.
What are you guys thinking
to fight over a girl like that?
You guys need to be reasonable about this.
- Play rock-paper-scissors for it.
- That's a good idea. Let's do it!
Okay, we'll only play
one round like real men.
Rock-paper-scissors!
A real man throws out a rock.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Let's do it again. Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- I'll date her first.
Since I won at rock-paper-scissors,
and I've even touched her chest.
Come on, it's not like our relationship
is going to last forever or anything.
Just stick close by me
and you guys can play for her again
whenever I break up with her.
Sound good?
It didn't feel entirely right
the three of us spent most of our time
together ever since that moment.
During all of our years together
there were trivial worries
over our grades...
- I think I flunked the exam.
- I'm just happy that it's over with.
And much bigger worries like
Dong Woo's father going bankrupt.
My family is the one in the dumps,
so why are you two looking so glum?
We were just playing the part, you idiot.
- Ouch, that's hot.
- Hot!
I heard you touched Soo Jung's chest?
Yeah.
Sorry I didn't tell you about it first.
Even though we're breaking up now
as your friend, and fellow classmate,
I will always wish you the best.
Fighting.
There was even a time when we didn't
realize what a problem it could pose
when a girl would give us an ear
splitting slap across the face.
I can't hear anything that you're saying.
You're such a moron.
I never knew that a girl
could turn into such a bitch.
But I guess a person of any gender
can turn into a bitch.
I'm getting too old for this.
His use of the phrase,
"Getting too old for this"
definitely felt weird as I was hearing it
but the phrase also carried some weight
as we stood, in the face of our twenties.
Okay, we're standing
in the middle of a crossroad.
Between dream and reality.
Up to this point, all the mistakes
that we've made in our past
has been excused because we were young,
and lacked real-life experience.
However, as we stand here,
older and more experienced...
I believe we need to be more responsible
in the choices that we make.
No matter which path we choose to take
let's respect and support
each other's decisions.
- I'm going to take this path.
- I'm going to take this one.
There's something
that you guys aren't getting.
This isn't just a dual path
but there are three paths
to choose from.
- I'm going to go this way.
- Hey, Chi Ho.
- You like women's breasts, don't you?
- It's what I live for.
Going down that path will lead you back
to your mom's breast, not to other women's.
- Oh, shit.
- Yuck.
Okay, a man must go forward.
Show me some respect.
- But must we make this decision now?
- No kidding. We're still young.
Hey, split the years of your life in half.
Where do you think that middle is?
- I'll probably live to be 80 years old.
- How can you be sure you'll live to be 80?
My father passed away at age 40,
and Mozart died when he was 35.
- Kurt Cobain died when he was 27. 27!
- Kurt Cobain committed suicide.
How can you be sure
that you won't commit suicide?
So what's your point?
You want us to buy life insurance?
If we were to divide our lives into halves
then half will be spent as minors,
and other half as adults.
Meaning, the mid point of our lives...
is at 20 years old.
We've already lived half our lives?
- Wow, we've aged fast.
- Now that we're at our midpoint...
- We can't just sit around like this.
- My point exactly.
Sex.
- Let's have sex.
- The three of us?
Ugh, you're such a moron.
- Let's not lose our focus here.
- This is a very serious problem.
Don't you guys ever
read any foreign news?
On average, most teens in Germany
lose their virginity by the age of 15.
They worry about contracting STDs
while we worry about doing our homework.
Condoms are given out like candy,
and what's the result of all that?
- Mercedes, Audi.. the best in the world.
- Wow.
How old are you guys?
You guys are 20 years old.
But let's not turn into monsters.
Then the monster that you see
in the movie, "The Host"...
- Is it because it didn't have sex?
- Yeah.
- That sounds like a sad movie.
- That movie made me cry.
- Let's have sex.
- Let's do it.
Fine, let's just do it.
My body is just going to rot
once I'm dead anyway.
- Let's just do it.
- She's so much better when she's sober.
Her problem is not knowing when to stop.
I think I take offense to that.
Hey, Cha Chi Ho.
You said your goal in life is to sleep
with 3,000 women before you die.
So why is it that you haven't
laid a finger on me yet?
- Are you saving me for last?
- Did she actually bring a pillow?
Here, now is your chance.
- Come here, you asshole.
- Are you kidding me?
She'll catch a cold if she
sleeps on that cold floor.
- Leave her. Let her catch a cold.
- Pour me a drink.
Honey?
- Oh my goodness...
- Kids these days are so spoiled.
- She is spoiled.
- You're a mess, Kid.
Look, it's Cha Chi Ho.
Better be careful
before she hurts herself.
Thanks for your concern,
but you just worry about yourself.
So, where did I leave off in my story?
I... don't want to
become a monster.
Sir, I'm against the idea
of prostitution
so I have no idea how, when,
or where I'm going to get laid.
Do not be afraid.
Do not think that it's impossible.
You're already ready for it.
Just... just...
How do I put this...
Just think of it as
a simple negotiation.
First...
I will walk you through
the negotiation steps for you.
- I'll take you out to the scene.
- You're a real true friend.
I'm so nervous.
But where?
I like this music.
- What is it?
- I don't know.
No more drinks for me.
I can feel myself turning red.
Okay, stop drinking.
I'll drink the rest myself.
- But don't you want her to drink?
- Don't push it, or it'll seem obvious.
This girl's desire for food
is much stronger than her sexual urges.
She'll think that you're not
trying to put the moves on her
and she'll start drinking again so that
she doesn't lose her drinks to you.
- Never stop analyzing your subject.
- You should tackle your studies like that.
Stop being so absurd.
You got it?
I'm glad my parents are never home.
The drinks are flowing,
and you've got the house to yourself.
Just don't act like a moron,
and you've got her in your bed.
- Act like a moron, how?
- Like calling the girl's father.
Yes, sir.
We're about to turn off the lights,
and get it on.
Yes, your daughter has
already agreed to it
and we're just waiting for you
to give us the all-clear.
- But you're not going to do that.
- Of course not.
Then it's a guaranteed score. Unless...
That's what all women are like.
They go around doing
whatever they want, but
they never let their
friends do anything.
I don't know what kind of bullshit
that is, but it's a threat.
A real live threat.
If you don't stay alert,
then you'll lose your chance.
Don't show that you're panicking.
Rather, get the girl flustered.
Then... it's time to go in for the kill.
I want to rub my dick all over your ass.
- She's shocked to hear that, right?
- That's an understatement.
Because you just don't say that.
She's now wondering what your deal is.
It's called, “cognitive dissonance.”
She doesn't know what to make of it.
That's when you go in for the kill.
Your male reproductive organs
have long finished maturing by this point.
But our nation's education system
disregarded that reality
and worked to keep that bit of truth
strictly hidden away from us.
They only emphasized the need
for academic achievement
and completely stomped out
our natural burning desire for the flesh
by enforcing us to live our lives
like celibate monks.
The Korean education system
can go fuck itself.
This is your true education.
Behold, my friends.
The divine Buddha has heard our prayers
and is giving us his blessing for us
to join our flesh together as one.
Shall we all join our bodies together?
Here's my own definition of
what sex means to me so far.
Something so near, yet so far...
A dream made into reality
by the shake of your own hand.
There's no shame in it.
There are only two types of men
who does not masturbate.
He's either missing his hands,
or missing his dick.
Kyung Jae. Kyung Jae.
In despair over his low test scores,
a high school student commits suicide.
It's a tragic story that
we hear about every year
but the student of this specific story
was well known for his good grades.
- Mom!
- Hey!
Mom, there's something wrong
with Kyung Jae.
He's keeps beating himself on his thighs
while watching some lunatic scream
on his computer screen.
Let Mom sleep, and I'll explain.
- Kyung Jae, are you okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
I'll explain.
It's almost like a rite of passage
before a man starts college.
It's not a religion,
but religious people do it, too.
- Something that most men do...
- Were you beating off?
Our twenties started off
on a rather insignificant note.
What's the first thing that a man does
when he enters a brand new environment?
Finding a pretty girl.
It's not like he'll do anything about it,
but it's pathetically true.
It's not like I wasn't hoping for
a campus romance like you see in dramas.
- Are you all right?
- Yes, I'm fine.
I'm worried you may have
dislocated your shoulder.
- No, I'm fine. Really.
- No.
- But I feel really bad.
- I'm fine.
- Let me buy you a steak buffet dinner...
- No, I said I was fine.
A drop in the nation's bonds...
This is a good environment for me.
I will devote myself
to my academic pursuits.
I'll make sure to work tirelessly
to build up my credentials
and will ready myself
for the job hunt.
You heard about
freshmen orientation tonight, right?›.
Ah, that's right. Of course.
Hey In Gook, what was your surname again?
Me? Hwang.
- What was your name?
- Oh...
Kyung Jae.
- Lee Kyung Jae.
- Kim Kyung Jae.
The Kimhae clan, right?
No, the Andong clan.
- Mom!
All right! Bubble wrap!
Mom, there's no playground around here.
Buy us one, huh?
Dong Woo has a clear goal in mind.
He chose to repeat his final year
because of the college tuition
but he's working hard to save up money
from his part-time jobs
and he'll later become
Korea's best comics artist one day.
Enjoy.
- Excuse us.
- Yes?
We ordered half and half.
Then why did you order
a plain fried chicken?
I'm sorry. My apologies.
What are you doing?
I'm sitting still.
What are you doing while sitting still?
Nothing.
Chi Ho's goal was...
to keep breathing.
He's already accomplished that goal.
- Business Management!
- Cheers!
- Business! Management!
Now the other way!
Don't you dare spill a drop!
I would accept it if this was
also part of the process
but I was a bit disappointed.
In the idea that a welcoming party for
intellectuals wasn't at all intellectual.
Um...
I looked at you because
I thought we've met before
but my intention wasn't
to hit on you or come on to you.
- I'm sorry.
- Hi.
Yes, hello.
Do you know me?
I'm sure a lot of people do.
I'll give you a ride
if you're headed to school.
I totally fell on my back, didn't I?
The party culture is the problem.
Nothing to feel embarrassed about.
Am I driving too fast?
Are you scared?
What?
Wow.
I enjoy the thrill.
I'm actually very comfortable right now.
Senior, thank you.
You're that way, right?
See you next time.
What's going on here?
How is it that you're
getting out of her car?
You heard her right?
She said, "See you next time."
What does that mean?
What are you saying, you moron?
Don't go over-analyzing her words now.
She must be really rich, though.
I don't know about that, but I did hear
she made some money in stocks.
- Stocks?
- She's the ace of the stock club.
She's the top dog
in the university.
How could you be getting out of her car?
I ran into her at the bus stop,
and she recognized me.
- Huh?
- Hm?
I didn't recognize her,
but she recognized me and...
Oh, I guess that makes sense.
You haven't seen this yet, have you?
You should see this.
You're on Facebook.
- I am?
- Yeah.
No more! I can't drink anymore!
How is this a welcome party?
This is a suicide mission!
He swallowed his own vomit!
The party culture is the problem.
Nothing to feel embarrassed about.
You're a Facebook star, man.
In Gook... This isn't right.
Hey, repeat student.
I'm repeating my year
under very sad circumstances.
- I'm not cool with that.
- But I'm cool.
- Do you beat off, too?
- What!
- What the heck?
- I caught my brother beating off.
I even asked him how often he does it.
It was totally hilarious.
That moron.
He should've been more cautious.
He was being cautious,
but I unlocked his door.
Why did you unlock his door?
Ugh, seriously.
I read somewhere that a use of lubrication
is crucial when masturbating.
Keep it down!
Beating it dry may be too much stimulation,
which could leave you desensitized.
But the grip of a woman's body isn't
as strong as the grip of your own hand.
Which can cause an issue for you when
you actually start sleeping with a woman.
- So make sure to always use a lube...
- Go sit somewhere else!
- I want pasta. Buy me some.
- Me? When I'm broke and penniless?
Ugh, this is so stressful.
I wish I could just find a rich man,
but I don't have any time to meet anyone.
And I'm a man to you?
Of course you're a man.
You even masturbate.
- Ugh, that Kim Kyung Jae!
- At least buy me some ddukbokki.
- Come on, buy me some!
- How about I buy you some instead?
Hey!
Dong Woo is so penniless!
Hi, Dong Woo.
Have you been well?
I know your school isn't close,
so what brings you by here?
It's not that far.
- Because I wanted to see you.
- See me?
Yeah, I have missed you.
How about you and I ditch So Hee,
and go grab a beer somewhere?
Wow, that's so low.
Are all college students like this?
I'm sorry, but I can't.
I have to work early in the morning.
- Is it because you're broke?
- I have money.
- You said you had to buy rice.
- It'll be my treat.
Sorry, but I don't think I can tonight.
- That's too bad.
- You and I can go instead.
Forget it.
- How much do we owe you?
- I've got money, so I'll pay.
- Look at you trying to act all cool.
- Keep your mouth shut.
Hey, did you know that
Dong Woo beats off?
Seriously!
Knock it off!
You've been saying that all day!
Oh my... you're actually getting upset.
I guess I'll be saying it tomorrow, too.
Your card has been declined.
Mom.
Did you take money out of
my bank account?
Something came up,
and I needed the money.
Why would you take money out of someone
else's account without even telling them?
It's not like we're strangers.
You even have your weekend job.
That's so I can pay for my tuition.
How am I supposed to eat now?
- Am I to just starve?
- Then you never should've moved out.
How am I to study in that tiny rural town?
There are art academies
around here, too...
Ugh, forget it.
Home sweet home.
I'm very happy right now.
There are some nasty rumors
going around about you.
I was giving my friends a field lesson.
She's acting like a child.
Where are you going
so early in the morning?
I just got home and am going to bed.
You know that I'm nocturnal.
Hey, come over here and have a seat.
I seriously have no idea...
where we went wrong with you.
Isn't that something a scientist would say
when he fails one of his experiments?
Let's just stop all this nonsense,
and come learn business from me.
We can take it slow
while you go to culinary school.
Isn't having one chef
in the house enough?
I'm too good-looking
to be cooped up in the kitchen.
I'm not doing it.
Honey, cut off his allowance as of today.
What? What a harsh thing to say!
Are you giving me up as your child?
Then what about you?
Are you giving up on your life?
- Just eat, sleep, and shit all day?
- It's not just eat, sleep, and shit.
I eat, sleep, and shit like a champ.
Do you know how difficult that is?
I was even out clubbing all night.
I was very busy in my own right.
- Honey, don't even feed him.
- I'm still a growing boy.
How can you say such a thing
as my own dad?
Okay, fine. Fine, I hear you.
By the end of the year...
I'm not even talking next year,
because I'm not that type of a person.
I will give some major thought to what it
is that I want to do by the end of the year
so let's just keep my allowance flowing.
Let's both agree on that, okay?
- No.
- Come on, why not!
No, I don't want to waste any more money.
Then give me tuition money
so that I can go to school.
Okay, let me see your acceptance letter.
- Give me the money first.
- Get lost.
Come on, just give me my allowance!
Did I ask to be born?
I was brought into this world
because you two were horny one night!
- You disrespectful bastard!
- Give me my allowance!
- How am I supposed to live without money!
- Get your act together!
- Give me my money! I want money!
- The bastard!
Give me my allowance!
Father, please give me my allowance!
My baby is such a good eater.
- Let's break up.
- What now? Stop being so annoying.
I don't even have an income anymore,
and I can't date a poor girl like you.
Even though all I have to give you
right now is this pickled radish
but I still have a bright future ahead
of me when I finish college.
But the present is more important to me.
I'm going to find myself a sugar mama
at one of those bars.
You're not going to
screw yourself like that.
What makes you think that?
Because your parents are good people,
so you're not going to screw up.
But you don't have parents,
so how are you so good?
- Because I'm in love with you.
- That's a serious problem.
Thinking isn't your strong suit,
so just keep eating your food.
I have to get to class.
- Want a kiss?
- No.
Hey.
What do you think I should do?
Are you being serious
about this right now?
I'm going to go to a PC room.
I can't decide between playing
League of Legends or World of Warcraft.
A life or death decision then.
Try selling off your game items.
Wouldn't that keep you afloat
for a couple of months?
The increase in actual income
affects the demand.
If you look at the graph below...
Ah, they say that love
is an unwelcome visitor.
Can't even drive it away.
Hi Kyung Jae.
Hello!
She called me by my name.
Pardon me, Senior.
I'm interested in joining
the investment club.
Our club is seriously boring.
You have to invest more time
into it than you might think.
Investments should be made rationally.
Don't invest unless you understand it.
Oh, exactly.
Rational judgment...
Hey, are you okay...
Hi.
- Hello.
Do you know that professor?
What?
I recognized him because
I saw him on TV once.
But how do you...
I take his class.
Ah, I really wanted to
take his class!
Don't bother. He's full of shit.
He's smarmy too.
You know how to talk badly about people.
Kyung Jae.
I'm going to go for a drive right now.
I don't want to go alone.
Want to invest in some time with me?
If you can understand, that is.
Yes.
I think I'm beginning to understand.
Truthfully, I wasn't planning on
joining a club.
Why not?
I was afraid I'd dream about
becoming something else.
Something that might
burden my family.
Like becoming an artist.
So you try to prevent things
before they ever happen?
- You're scary.
- What?
No, I like neckties, too.
I'll buy you a tie when you get a job.
Whoa, that's a promise!
Let's toast to that promise...
Well, we should.
But then who will drive?
You drive.
I did get my license,
but I've haven't driven since then.
We'll just sleep over then.
I'll give it a go!
One should sleep at home.
You must have a good reason
to go home.
My boyfriend tends
to go home early too.
Is your boyfriend...
a gamer too?
You have to suck that like a man.
Anyway, it's nice that he's not here.
- You have to suck it.
- But...
Can't they keep it down?
They're a bit loud, aren't they?
Do what you did in the welcoming party.
Opposing the corrupt system
like a rebel.
Senior.
That wasn't me then.
Even if you were But
still, this a bit...
Then I'll do it.
The duty of the youth is
to challenge corruption.
Oh? You like Kurt Cobain?
Shut your fucking mouths!
I feel a bit weird, boss.
[CHA CHI HO]
[LEE SO MIN]
- Wow, thank you for the meal!
- Eat up.
- Hey So Hee.
- Yo.
You're not studying hard,
by any chance, right?
Would I? Who do you take me for?
That's right.
You've already done everything
you need to do. You're pretty.
I'll marry your daughter as soon as
she graduates, Mother-in-law.
- Okay.
- What the? You're that easy, Mom?
Chi Ho's sexy.
You have to be really careful.
Don't go too far.
Do the dishes.
- I don't want to.
- I'm leaving!
- Okay, bye.
- Goodbye, Mother-in-law!
I love you!
It's the same with compact cars.
Move over. I'll be late to work.
What? You went to the seashore
with a girl and nothing happened?
And you just drove her home?
Are you human?
I'm so disappointed.
You loser. You nutjob.
She has a boyfriend.
You know I'm not that kind of guy.
As if that makes a difference.
What does that make me as a guy
who's taken and sleeps around?
You?
A tall son of a bitch.
It's not being a son of a bitch.
It's called being flexible.
Say she goes on social media
and posts what you did to her.
Then the girls will think,
'My word, there are gentlemen out there!'
Don't go and raise the bar
for the rest of us, please!
You were in the wrong, Kyung Jae.
You should have at least
gone to third base with her.
I said not to talk about her like that!
I like this girl!
Are you getting mad at me
over a girl right now?
- That's right.
- I'm sorry then.
He is kind of cute.
Oh, shit.
I want to sleep with her.
Watch how I hit on her.
Flexibility, okay?
Now what are you thinking of doing?
I told you not to do it
while I'm around.
She's really hot.
Oh my god! Shit!
What the fuck? You hit someone!
Are you insane?
The brake slipped!
I was only going to scare her!
Well, you succeeded.
You definitely scared her.
You said you were
going to sleep with her.
Go sleep with her.
She's already lying in bed.
I'm being serious right now.
Hey, you know that money
we've been saving for our trip?
I only saved 100,000 won!
You're useless.
What am I going to do then?
What else? You have to call home.
My parents are ready
to totally disown me.
They'll be so happy about this
that they'll throw me in jail.
Go on then.
It's not like you have
anything to do anyway.
Can you go instead?
I've got allergies.
Screw you. You go.
You're a son of a bitch.
Fuck!
Go and hit on her.
That was your intent anyway.
Wait... really? Hey.
You're really going to hit on her?
Does that work?
We're filming at night as it is.
Then get me a manager.
Do you know how awkward
it is going on set alone?
I'm going. I'll go.
- The flowers are in full bloom...
- Take the wheel.
Good morning, Director!
Assistant director.
- Who is she?
- She plays the girl that gets bullied.
Her name is Heo Eun Hye.
I'm rookie actress Heo Eun Hye.
Please take care of me.
- You have to make it look realistic.
- You can count on me!
I grew up getting smacked around.
Director Jo, I brought
my manager with me.
You had a manager?
Since the company said
I'll be busier from now on.
I see.
Your manager is quite handsome.
Goodness, I hope you
take good care of her.
We really have high hopes for her.
- Good to meet you, too.
- Yes, of course.
See you around.
They give you food
even if you do nothing?
Isn't waiting around
part of the job?
What are you going to do
about the settlement?
Want to go out for drinks
after filming wraps?
Don't mess with me.
- Give me three million won.
- I don't have it.
What is it that you do?
During the day... I'm sitting still.
And at night, I either go out drinking...
- You're unemployed.
- Yes.
- How old are you?
- 20 years old.
I have five days of filming left,
so you can be my manager.
Just follow me around
and I'll forget about the settlement.
You got that?
So I can just wait around
and eat the food?
Yes. And pretend like you're taking care
of me like that guy is over there.
That's easy.
When have we met that
you'd speak so politely?
We're the same age, so drop
the formalities when we're alone.
Eun Hye! We're getting ready to film!
- Hurry up!
- Yes, Director Jo!
I want to smack that face of hers.
- Stop moving around when I smack you!
- Cut!
- Good work, everyone!
- Are you okay?
Good work!
- Yes, I'm fine.
Hey, you can smack me
as hard as you want.
Okay, let's do another take.
Everyone get in position.
Let's get this rolling.
Ready...
Action!
I've brought some refreshments!
Here you go.
Here, this is for you.
- Okay!
- Okay.
Okay, I'll see you tomorrow.
- You really must have nothing else to do.
- Yeah.
- Forget it. Stop coming to the set.
- No, I'll come.
I'm not as sweet and innocent
as you think I am.
Don't develop any feelings for me.
What bullshit are you spewing now?
Who says I think you're sweet?
Whatever. Do what you want.
Okay!
- Dong Woo, your tuition isn't in yet.
- Really?
I don't know how that could've happened.
It'll be in next week.
Okay. Why are you crouched on the floor?
I'm having sympathy for the poor.
[GOOD JOB AT SCHOOL TODAY.
I'M ON MY WAY HOME AFTER CLASS MYSELF.]
[YEAH, I'M ON THE BUS.
I'LL TEXT YOU BEFORE I GO TO BED.]
Just send her the smiley face!
Why are you hesitating about it?
Do you mind?
You're embarrassing me.
- Are you two finally dating?
- No, we're not dating.
If you're texting each other before bed,
then that means you're dating.
Kyung Jae and I text each other
before bed, too.
Why are you dating my brother?
Which one of you is the girl?
Forget it. Let's just forget it.
- Dear brother, you're home.
- Yeah.
- What brings you by here?
- Mom wanted me to bring you some food.
She's afraid that
her precious son might starve.
If she's that worried,
then she shouldn't touch my bank account.
She needed some things for the twins,
and she had no other choice.
Mom bawled her eyes out
after taking your money.
I know that mom's a bit thoughtless,
but knowing her situation
shouldn't you have at least checked
to make sure everything's okay with her?
But I guess...
your comics are more important
to you than Mom is, isn't it?
- Hey, you know that's not true.
- Yes, it is.
It's been years since our family's been
in the dumps after Dad was taken away.
It's not like you need a college degree
to draw your comics.
That's true.
But I fear that if I give up now,
then I'll never get another chance.
It's not like I'm telling you
to give up college.
I'm sorry, I know you need
to go to college, too.
I'm going to go to military school.
Mom wants me to go to law school,
but that's just crap.
If I left, then who will look after her?
[MIN JUNG: ARE YOU ASLEEP?]
Um... I have a question that
I'd like to ask you.
Sure, what is it?
How does one become a movie director?
You have to shoot a movie.
Then you're a movie director.
How does one shoot a movie?
Actors start acting,
and I capture it on film.
If I don't capture it,
then the film director captures it.
Then I just sit here and say, "Okay."
But if something seems off about it,
then I shout out for another take.
Do some bullshit like that,
and you have yourself a movie.
- It sounds like a very stressful job.
- You actually understood that?
Director, we need you over here.
Please come.
Okay.
Why ask?
Do you want to make a movie?
- Well...
- Don't. It's too much work.
You have a nice body.
You should just be a model.
No, don't do that either.
It's too hard.
Just get into business.
No, not that either. It's too hard.
Running a small business is too tough.
If you can, just become a rich tycoon.
The government is nice to rich tycoons.
Just do that. Then you can marry
pretty actresses, too.
And if things don't work out,
get divorced and get remarried.
Get remarried as often as you want.
Doesn't that sound good?
Director!
I asked you to come here!
Can't you see that I'm on my way?
I'm on my way... over to you.
That jerk is such an asshole.
He's always ordering me around.
He thinks he's the director.
- Director, what took you so long?
- I didn't hear you.
Then why did you answer me?
There he goes again.
Please get up.
Get up.
- What do you want me to take a look at?
- Come this way.
He's so awesome.
That was so beautiful.
[CEO KIM: CLUB ROSE IN CHEONGDAM-DONG,
NEXT WEDNESDAY AT 9 P.M.]
Investment is all about analysis.
Jin Joo's boyfriend
rarely calls or texts her.
Outside of her class, she spends
most of her free time in the club room.
Which means, she spends
most of her free time with me.
We have a similar food preferences.
Which means, we eat our meals together.
She likes comedic movies, like me.
Meaning, we go to the movies together.
Hormones created by feelings of
being in love doesn't last very long.
It only lasts for about 30 months.
Jin Joo, how long have you been
with your boyfriend?
We've been dating for about two years.
Why do you ask?
Thanks.
You need to judge rationally.
Never invest in something
which you don't understand.
But this... I understand.
I'm going to invest all my heart
into the love that's budding for her.
- Jin Joo.
- Yeah?
I want to rub my dick all over your ass.
This coffee smells great.
What's so funny?
Oh... I'm so sorry!
I'm so very sorry.
I'm... I'm so sorry.
Crazy bastard!
- I'm so sorry.
- What's wrong with you?
Twins!
- Dong Woo!
- Chicken!
Mom! He's brought us chicken!
Mom, have you been smoking?
It's the best remedy for stress.
- Don't eat like street beggars.
- Don't scold them while they're eating.
Why aren't you eating any?
I'm sick of chicken. You eat.
I like duck better.
Next time, bring me some duck.
Mom, why did you have so many kids?
When you were born, you looked so much
like your father, and I didn't like it.
Then when Dong Won was born
he looked so much like me, and I loved it.
But... I really wanted a pretty daughter.
So, that's why I got pregnant again.
- But I never thought...
- Stop listening, and just eat.
Your father going bankrupt was
what stopped me from having another one.
Maybe it was a blessing in disguise.
I still find a small sliver of joy even
in the midst of that unfortunate story.
- Stop laughing like a street beggar.
- Don't scold them while they're laughing.
What the hell?
Did you snoop through my messages?
Asshole.
What the hell are you doing?
What?
Who the hell do you think you are?
Are there any gigs for me, too?
With rich old ladies?
- Why didn't you stop me?
- Why would I?
It's not like you're going to
be supporting me.
Are you crying?
Stop crying just because
you're struggling.
I've got enough to deal with already.
But she sure looks pretty
when she cries.
That's a real rarity.
Hey, what's with that strange
expression on your face?
I've never seen you look
at a girl like that before.
Like what?
Like you're thinking
with your heart...
rather than with your dick.
Like you want to hold her,
rather than just bang her.
Right?
But...
You're wrong.
Wow... I wonder if all this is
going to disappear, too.
That's just the way of life.
Easy for you to say since you never
take anything in life seriously.
- Is there a new girl in your life?
- Yeah, the one from the other day.
That's going to make things
awkward with So Min.
I've got nothing to hide.
So Min is my girlfriend,
while I'm just dating the other one.
- What does dating mean to you?
- Having sex whenever we're together.
- Then how about a girlfriend?
- Someone I see when I want to have sex.
- That strangely makes sense to me.
- Then... what does it mean to be in love?
- Doing it multiple times a day.
- Ah...
Crap, this sucks.
I actually understand his logic.
So Joong!
- What are you about to do?
- I wasn't going to do anything.
- I should teach you a lesson, asshole.
- Damn asshole.
So Joong, we're here.
Just look at you.
You're so damn pretty.
- Shut up, and bring your lips over here.
- Shall I?
[NEWBIE DRIVER]
I'm quite the thrill-seeker.
One, two, three!
Is it my turn?
Happy birthday to you!
Blow out your candles!
Dong Woo, for you!
- Thanks.
- For you.
Okay, let's do this.
Let's go!
[FOR YOUR VIEWING PLEASURE.]
Ugh... that crazy girl.
- Should I draw a mole on my nose?
- Why?
Because they're pretty.
Just look at Han Ga In and Go So Young.
Then you'll look like
every other actress out there.
You should draw one in
the middle of your forehead.
A really big one.
What the hell is he saying?
"I'm going to marry her,
so sign the divorce papers!"
"But she's my sister!"
- "I'm going to make you pay."
- "How? By seducing my father?"
"Why not? I'm going to destroy you."
"I'm going to destroy you!"
That's how you're going to say it?
Are you asking me for my permission
to have you destroy me?
You have to be more vicious.
You sound way too meek.
Say it like when you go
bat-shit crazy on me.
Is that so?
I thought I was being tough.
What the...
what's with the sudden accent?
I thought you boys liked girls
with cute accents.
I'm trying to look cute
for you right now.
Wow, so cute. So darned cute!
- Shit!
- I am?
No, I'm talking about me.
I'm going crazy from all the cuteness!
How did you think to do that?
Aw, shit!
You're driving me crazy!
What? What is it?
- Let me see it.
- There's nothing to see.
- Forget it.
- Come on, hand it over.
- Give it back!
Give me back my phone!
What are you doing?
Hey!
Seriously!
- Hey!
- Hello?
Listen bastard, she's not a call girl,
so stop texting her like this.
- Cha Chi Ho!
- What?
That's right, asshole, I'm her pimp.
Are you the press or something?
Fine.
Come and get it, you asshole.
Stop overreacting.
Who the hell are you to stir shit up?
Who am I?
You're asking me who I am?
I don't deserve to hear you
talk to me that way.
You have a girlfriend,
you moronic asshole.
I told you that it was no big deal.
Why did you rush over here like that?
She collapsed and that's not a big deal?
You should've called me right away.
- I ran over here like a lunatic.
- What was that going to do?
Were you going to call the hospital,
and take care of matters yourself?
Uncle...
Your mom has always been a frail person
and she's working
for the first time in her life
so her body couldn't handle it.
I hear that you're studying
cartoon animation?
I'm going to open up a spot
for you in my factory.
- I..
- It's not manual labor.
If you can learn the business...
then I plan on passing the factory
down to you once I retire.
All I have is a daughter
who now lives overseas.
Don't you want to send
Dong Won away to college?
He can be a judge or a prosecutor.
Don't you want that for him?
- You can do the cartoon thing as a hobby.
- I've already paid for my tuition.
- Give me some time to think about it.
- There's no time to think about it.
I know that you guys don't like me.
But do you think I wanted
for your father to end up that way?
Had I gone down with him,
then who would've taken care of the family?
And... even your father
doesn't resent me for what happened.
- Where are you off to?
- To the same lecture that you're going to.
I told you not to go to that lecture.
Like the hymen of a virgin,
once torn, it cannot be repaired.
You'll have to live with it
for the rest of your life
but will you still do it?
Even though it's a one-sided crush,
I will continue to love her in silence.
So that whenever she does become mine,
I won't be too flustered by it.
Did you think that I'd send the two
of you off together with a smile?
Did you really think that I'd do that?
Did you...
Did you really think I'd do that?
I'm not sure if it's wrong of me
to think like this right now
but I can't help but think that
I'm better off than she is right now.
Please delete what you just recorded.
Please, I beg of you. Delete...
what you just recorded.
Please, I beg of you.
- Have you guys not eaten yet?
- We have!
Then eat slower.
- Why are you faulting how they're eating?
- Because there's nothing for you to eat.
- You should eat, too.
- I already ate.
But you should still eat.
I'll go out and get more.
It's okay, I like chicken better.
Why do you keep changing your mind?
I used up all the money I had to buy that!
Duck is expensive!
It's more expensive than chicken!
I bought it for you, so have some!
Why are you two crying,
you little bastards? Huh?
What are you two crying about
like little dimwits?
You two even cry the same
like a pair of little shits.
That's enough.
I want you to leave. Leave!
It's okay, go on and eat.
Yeah.
Are you out of bed?
I'm out front. Let's grab lunch.
You there?
Come on up. I'll make you lunch.
My dad is a chef,
and I even went to a culinary school.
- So this is the least I can do.
- You quit your school after only one day.
Let's break up.
What now?
How can it end so quickly like that?
It was over by the time
my instant noodle finished cooking.
How could that have been the end of it?
There are so many awful men
out there in this world.
Ironically enough
countless number of women get
their hearts broken from loving these men.
Then there are those men
who are there to console, and only
to console those heartbroken women.
Those are the good guys,
or shall I say, brainless idiots?
And I'm one of them.
Jin Joo left for the land of the cold
with the man she loved.
But I'm sure she's receiving warmer
treatment there than she would here.
Right here... it aches right here.
Do you know what that feels like?
Take a look, So Joong.
- Isn't my chest all red?
- It's because you've been rubbing it.
- For you. Can I get you anything else?
- Piss off. I'm still upset.
Hey, I saw that video clip,
and that professor's wife is hot.
There, you should just date her instead.
It'll be an even trade.
- Since the wife is hot, too.
- Yeah.
- She's hot? Show me.
- Yeah, want to see?
- Look at how many 'likes' she got.
- Yeah, she's nice.
What are they doing?
Hey, Kim Kyung Jae.
You know what the saddest part is?
It's not about your failed crush,
but it's that those are your friends.
- She really is pretty.
- Put that away!
You really are wise.
It must be the fancy education
that you're getting from college.
- Want a drink?
- I quit drinking.
Just how old do you have to be before
you stop feeling the agonies of love?
- Does it get better at your age?
- No.
An older friend of mine came by last night,
and he ended up crying into his drink.
- How old is he?
- 49.
Women and our dating lives
are what we're all worried about?
What an insignificant thing to worry about
at the turning point of our lives.
Let's be adults about this, okay?
- You should commit suicide tonight.
- What?
I've been watching a lot of movies lately,
and teens are always committing suicide.
You should commit suicide.
Then it'll give us something
more serious to worry about.
- But I get paid tomorrow.
- Oh, then that won't work.
Then how about an abortion?
But someone needs to be pregnant first.
Hey, go out and get yourself pregnant.
- By whose sperm?
- Who cares? Be impulsive about it.
- I'm on my period.
- Shit.
How about drugs? Let's do drugs.
That costs money.
We don't have money to do that.
So this must be why
soju manufacturers are so profitable.
Then...
- Let's have sex.
- It's about time those words came out.
I say this with the honor
of my name on the line...
If you guys don't have
sex again this year
then forget about being monsters, you'll
turn into one of those dirty politicians.
Then let's be adults about it,
and go to one of those seedy bars.
Fine, go.
Go, you pathetic losers.
- Just go.
- This is going against our principles.
- Are you sure about this?
- I'm sure!
- Let's go! Come on!
- Are you sure about this?
- We're sure!
- Yeah!
[IS IT OKAY TO TOUCH THIS GIRL'S TITS?]
[I'VE BEEN PONDERING ABOUT THAT MYSELF.]
[IT'S NOT LIKE YOU TO HESITATE.]
[I'VE NEVER HAD TO PAY FOR TITS BEFORE.
I'LL GO FOR IT FIRST.]
The first pair of tits I've ever touched
were the fake padded bra
of some nameless girl I barely knew.
My first pair of tits were...
a cheap padded bra that was made up of
polyester, polyurethane, and cotton.
And that's where I blacked out.
- Kyung Jae!
You moron!
Why are you freaking out at the bar?
You're a moronic asshole!
- You're such an idiotic asshole!
- Stop hitting Kyung Jae!
Hey, what's college got to do
with becoming a movie director?
- Well... But still.
- Shut up.
Our country is so screwed up these days.
You have to be good at math in order to
get into a good college, right?
Isn't that how the system works?
But what bullshit is that?
It's so screwed up.
- You're bad at math, aren't you?
- I'm horrible at it.
Shit.
It's a screwed up system where kids
like you are forced to become losers.
It's like you're worthless
just because you suck at math
and you're made to believe you're unworthy
before you even attempt anything.
This is all because of those
shitheads that runs our government.
They pay for their own kids to receive
expensive tutoring lessons.
They're all assholes and shitheads.
All they care about is
finding ways for them to get richer.
Screw math!
It's not like we have to do
factoring problems before we eat.
That's why I've been thinking about
writing a screenplay of my own.
- Like practice of some sorts.
- Good, and be confident about it.
It's an idea that I gave to an
aspiring comic artist friend of mine.
- Would you like to hear what it is?
- Yeah, sounds good. Go for it.
The title is...
Invasion of the Planet Penis.
Penis... as in...
Ah... penis?
Okay, go on.
It takes place in two million B.C.
Towards the end of Caenozoic era.
The story begins with a theory that
the males didn't have dicks back then.
- They don't have dicks?
- Meanwhile...
The aliens of Planet Penis
foresaw the fate of their own extinction
in the far distant future
and infiltrated the Earth to plant
themselves as the dicks on the males.
Interesting.
The bigger aliens
ended up going to Africa.
- Damn! They should've came here instead.
- No shit.
Anyway, those aliens end up going back.
But since, the males viewed their
newly given dicks as a symbol of pride
and went around boasting their dicks
until... they started evolving
to what we are today.
Our dicks are aliens.
Mine is suddenly
starting to feel strange.
You're sucked into the story, aren't you?
Since then, men became obsessed with sex,
and they kept on doing it.
They couldn't stop!
After centuries of peace
living that way.
The aliens of Planet Penis
are in danger of extinction
just like their ancestors foretold.
Their birthrate plummeted.
So they end up invading Earth
to retrieve their comrades?
Bingo!
It's not really retrieving.
Technically, they came to reclaim
what was already theirs.
But would you hand over your dick
if they asked for it back?
- I'd rather die.
- Right?
Intergalactic war.
Humanity's battle against
Planet Penis to protect their dicks.
And then women are more aggressive.
That's right!
- Bravo!
Bravo. You're a fucking genius!
Totally crazy.
Don't do math and don't go to college.
Bravo!
But the production cost
would be incredibly high...
I need to take a leak.
Don't do movies.
You'll get depression.
Hold onto me.
- Dong Woo.
- Yeah?
When will life cease to be exhausting?
Do I look like someone
who can answer that for you?
Point taken.
It's a present. Cheer up.
[FREE CHICKEN COUPON]
- Oh, coupons.
- 10 coupons.
You have to mention it
before you order.
How precious.
What?
- Go on.
- Hmm?
Keep walking.
- Why?
- Just keep walking, huh?
Stop!
Don't turn around!
I'm not doing this
because I'm tired
and I'm not doing this
because of the coupons.
You've noticed that I like you.
Why pretend like you don't know
when you already do?
So rude.
How come you smell this nice?
You said you're broke
but you use fabric softener?
Well... I have sensitive skin.
Don't lose another good girl.
Jeez.
You think I'm out of shape
because I'm a senior, right?
No, I've been sticking to a strict diet
and kept up an exercise regimen.
I'm as busty as can be.
They're totally firm.
I've discovered a commonality
between bad guys and soju.
You have way too much
free time on your hands.
Soju might taste bitter...
but then there's a slightly sweet
aftertaste once you swallow it.
- Is that right?
- That sweetness is addictive.
It's the same with bad guys.
If they treat you nicely on occasion
after treating you horribly
then the girl become an addict
to that hint of a sweet side.
You make it sound like
I only date bad guys.
Bad and worthless guys.
I get that you're passionate
about social welfare.
I totally get it...
but you shouldn't approach men
with that kind of attitude.
I guess I do tend to do that.
Despite my words of advice,
I'm going to be an asshole from now on.
A bad guy can usually deceive others
into thinking that he's a nice guy.
But when a nice guy
tries to be an asshole...
It's a bit lacking.
He could end up looking like an idiot.
Am I considered a nice guy type then?
To put it nicely, yes.
To be more blunt, a pushover.
An idiot who lets the girl he loves
slip away without saying a word.
An idiot.
- I just got her off my mind.
- Nobody forgets their first love.
What are you talking about?
She's not my first love.
That's you.
Say that again.
So that I can apologize
for not hearing you correctly.
I got a sugar daddy.
Should I tell you who he is?
I'll be modeling for his company, too.
Fuck, she's so blunt about it.
I'm breaking up with you right now.
Although there isn't the slightest chance
that I'll ever take you back
but know this if you aren't dumb.
I fucking loved you.
You'll probably never meet someone
who loves you as much as I did.
I'm letting you know so you can
regret it sometime in the future.
How much could you have
possibly loved me?
How many days has he been
sitting there like that?
He's less of a worry
when he isn't off doing something.
- Wrong!
- Oh my goodness!
He's gone nuts.
That's enough.
[I'VE GOT SOMETHING TO TELL YOU.
MEET ME AT SOH SOH AT 3 P.M.]
I think... I'm nervous.
I'll do the talking.
It's not like we've done
anything wrong.
You startled me.
What a moron.
Hey, Kim Kyung Jae!
Are you lonely lately?
Why are you two holding hands?
We're dating.
It's been some time.
So what?
Have you slept together?
This is hilarious.
Fucking hilarious.
Hey, where are you going?
Isn't this what you were
going to tell me?
I've heard you loud and clear,
so I'm leaving.
You don't look okay...
Lash out at me if you want.
I've got some personal issues
going on.
Hey, I think it'll be awkward
if you leave now.
What's with you guys?
What am I supposed to do?
They're the ones dating each other.
What the fuck? Want my blessing?
Why are you cursing, you punk?
Why are you talking as if
you're never going to see him again?
I said I've got my own
personal issues.
And it's really strange.
That's not weird to you?
Let go of me.
It's fine with me.
You have my blessing.
Just keep holding hands.
You already are...
Give him some time.
All right, let's laugh it off.
Goodness.
A week on the couch.
Another in bed.
Can't you at least change
positions from time to time?
You'll get bed sores.
- Dad!
- What the heck.
- What's with girls?
- What, you punk?
- They're messed up.
- Your room is more messed up.
Clean your room, you punk!
Jeez, my head hurts!
My goodness.
Get up, get up, you rascals!
Time to go to school!
Come here.
- No!
- One, two... We can sleep in today!
- Why?
- It's college entrance exam day!
Get up since you're up.
Have breakfast.
[GOOD LUCK ON YOUR EXAM. YOU BETTER
GIVE ME AN ANSWER ONCE IT'S OVER, ]
[IF IT'S A NO, I'LL KILL YOU.]
- Leaving?
- I should.
- Mom.
- Yeah?
Should I move back in with you guys?
There's no room for you.
Seriously. How can you be so fickle?
You told me to move back in last time.
Beautiful women are like that.
You've seen what I looked like
when I was younger, right?
I wasn't going to say this
but I was much prettier than
in those pictures.
Good for you.
I've decided to work for
Uncle's company.
I'm sorry.
I should have made that decision
for the sake of the family...
But I decided to because of a girl.
Ah, there's someone I like, Mom.
She's incredibly pretty.
Almost as pretty as you are.
- Why would someone like that...
- Come on.
You married Dad.
- Because he had a lot of money.
- Hey, seriously.
I'm leaving.
Eat before you go.
Your cooking is terrible.
Why else would the twins
be hungry all the time?
It's because pretty women can't cook.
I guess she must've smelled the food.
Hey So Hee! How did your exam go?
Kyung Jae! Where's Dong Woo right now?
Huh? I don't know, after his exam...
He didn't take the exam!
I heard he quit his part-time job
and the art academy too!
He isn't picking up either.
You don't know where he's gone?
Where is he?
What are you talking about?
How would you like your hair cut?
Like an office employee, please.
Pardon?
Like a real office employee.
What the hell?
What's wrong with you?
- Did your exam go well?
- What are you doing?
And what's with your hair?
Hey, you crazy bastard.
You're broke? Is that it?
You need money?
Here.
Hey, here's some money,
you crazy bastard!
What's with your hair?
Stop making a fuss and take a seat.
Who's making a fuss around here?
Why put up with everything for a year
if you were going to quit like that?
Stop it!
Why are you making
such a big deal?
Why should I be criticized
for giving up?
What's the big deal about the world?
You think it's full of winners like
Kim Yuna and Park Tae Hwan?
So do all the quitters have
to be criticized for doing so?
What? What?
Do you even know
how hard it is to give up?
Who said I wasn't going to college?
I'll take the job route first.
I'll learn the business
and earn some money...
You think this opportunity
comes up every day?
Comics...
Comics can...
The tears won't come.
It's not really something
you can cry about.
I can always find a way
to draw on my own...
It's true. It's not like my parents
died or something.
It's not like we lost our country either.
I guess it's not really
something to cry over.
Anyway, you're back, Cha Chi Ho.
Hey, you two.
Don't have sex in front of me.
What kind of nonsense is that, man?
- Don't get pregnant either.
- Come on.
Don't even look happy together.
I got dumped.
- She dumped you?
- Big fucking time.
And... fuck.
What's really pathetic...
is that I'm heartbroken.
Seeing you three together
reminds me of something.
That it's much scarier
when you three idiots are together.
Pour me a shot, too.
- No!
You guys started drinking during
your first year of high school!
I've lived a decent life for 19 years
and I can't have a shot?
- No.
- No way.
Absolutely not.
Why does it feel so... empty?
People keep saying that
we're living the best years of our lives
are they just talking about our skin?
Life is definitely hard and frustrating
but I can't go and bitch about it
or I get criticized for it.
It just feels so empty.
What's so empty for you?
At least you're screwing
your best friend's ex.
Hey, you son of a bitch.
You want to say that?
What? I can say whatever I want.
So annoying.
I'm only letting you off today
because of Dong Woo?
What's so special about today?
Don't go out of your way for me.
I don't want your pity.
You guys are so annoying.
This celebration turned into
a pity party for you.
What's with the big talk?
Come to think of it,
you're the biggest idiot.
You think you can take me?
- Idiots.
- Fuck you.
At least I'm not screwing
my best friend's ex.
Are you trying to make
a catchphrase out of that?
Shut up. You're screwing
your ex's best friend.
You crazy son of a bitch.
You've gone too far, moron.
They're the ones screwing around.
Why yell at me?
Will you stop using that word?
See? They're so superficial.
- What did you say?
- Great! This is just great.
Great? You're no better
because you're screwing his ex.
Stop saying that word, you ass!
Stop it! At least my brother
isn't masturbating anymore.
- Hey!
Boss, we're back!
Get back. Get back!
Don't do that!
I'm usually not such a bad person.
It's just a part of my job.
I have to threaten people every day...
I have to destroy things too.
But what can I do?
I've got growing kids at home
and it's tough to get a job
in this economy.
Get out before I call the cops.
Get the hell out, you thugs!
Oh, how sexy.
Stay inside.
Let's take this outside.
I came here to do my job,
and she keeps telling me to leave.
Let's do this then.
I've got a crush on your wife.
She's hot!
I'd like to go out with her sometime.
I'm not saying you should
just give her to me.
I'm asking for a fair shot
at competing against you.
I'll write off your interest
and leave your business alone.
I can't give you
a better offer than that.
Honey.
Let's get out of here.
Let's just go, okay?
Stay inside.
- Honey...
- I said stay inside!
A fourth-degree black belt in Taekwondo
and martial arts master
and a former Navy Seal.
A man with an iron fist
from kneading dough.
This man who's been keeping
his wild instincts in check for his family.
He's... about to explode.
But I've been so timely
with paying off the interest.
Please stop with your destruction.
My father invested his whole life
into this restaurant.
I can't just leave like this. Please.
This jackass. You scared me.
- You startled me!
- The duty of the youth...
is to challenge corruption.
Wreck the place.
Destroy it!
Shut your fucking mouth, you fuck!
Leave him alone!
Leave them alone
and let them stay here!
I regretted it as soon as I took off.
I was going to stop him.
Ditto.
Power and greed were greater than our will.
But our feats won't be forgotten.
We barely completed the first half.
One, two, three!
The durability of this product
is entirely different
that has never been seen
in the previous models.
Dong Woo successfully adjusted
into his new work life.
Any other ideas?
I'd like to propose an idea
for a new product.
It's a cup with a built-in blender.
I named it, "Tornado in my hand."
He didn't give up on comics.
He continued drawing after work
and posted them on his blog.
"Invasion From Planet Penis"
now has a substantial fanbase
and it's enjoying
great popularity online.
Chi Ho finally found a purpose in life.
Something no one expected.
Dad, I've decided to make movies.
I'm going to be a movie director!
Honey.
Get me some aspirin.
Ready.
Action!
Okay!
- Get me my pills now!
- Ready!
Action!
Look at this bastard...
Director!
Director! Hold on!
Director! Director!
Director!
Chi Ho's ill-tempered boss
was his biggest obstacle.
He came up with seven
different plans to murder him
but then fought off the temptation.
- Are you okay?
- The knife!
He proved everyone wrong
by sticking it out for three days.
Hey, get over here!
Yes, sir!
Hey, what's with your grades?
I'm a college student. Whatever.
You're still a student.
You sound like my mom.
I lost my entire savings
on stock trading.
Even though it was cyber money.
I joined a new club shortly afterward.
- All right!
- Let's go.
Do you want to go for a spin,
Kim Kyung Jae?
Yes!
I'm sure there will be countless times
of trial and error ahead of us
but we've got plenty of times to
turn back around if we take a wrong turn.
I guess that's why people
call it "the good times."
Our roaring...
Kyung Jae. You got a military
conscription notice.
What's with the face?
Won't you see Sam Hammington there?
The Australian man? How great!
You all applied to go together, right?
With Chi Ho and Dong Woo.
What? Are you serious?
What?
Fuck.
I'm leaving... Damn.
We decided to go on a cross-country hike
a week before entering the army.
It felt like a cool thing to do
to walk to the training base.
Hey you morons.
I told you this was a stupid idea.
Is this cool to you? Is it?
Does it feel cool to pass out
even before we get there?
What kind of bullshit is this?
I was going to get a bonus next month.
I think this country does nothing for me.
Blame your nationality.
Despite everything... I won't be bitter.
No, I won't be!
What a moron.
Okay, let's go! How bad could it be!
Yeah! Let's do it!
Screw you!
Whatever comes next and after that...
we'll be fearless and ready for it.
Because we're in our roaring twenties!
- This feels great!
- This is so nice!
I have a confession to make to you guys!
I'm dating So Hee!
You all right?
Did you sleep with her?
- Well...
- Don't answer that.
Answer him.
Tell him that it's not true.
I feel like...
Would lying about it change anything?
Among the two friends I've got...
one screws his friend's ex...
and the other guy
screws his friend's sister.
Isn't it a weird turn of events
that I'm the most normal one here?
Listen, man. We've had our share of
differences, but we've overcome them.
Kyung Jae, that rock's lodged in there.
It's stuck, man.
You're not that kind of guy.
He dislodged it.
Kyung Jae.
Let's think this through.
You're a sensible guy.
Kyung Jae, Kyung Jae...
I love So Hee!
- Come here!
- I'm in love with So Hee!
I'll kill you!
Get over here! I'll kill you
I love So Hee!