Hi.
Mom!
Please don't fucking do this.
Please don't fucking
do this. Mom. Mom.
I love you.
- I've got to go.
- No. No.
What are you doing?
No!
Let's go. Let's go.
Come on. Get up. Get up.
Move it. Move it.
Welcome to paradise boys.
This is Coldwater. I am
Colonel Frank Reichert.
United States Marine
Corps, retired.
You can call me Colonel.
You can call me sir.
It's up to you. The choice is yours.
Life here, gentlemen,
is very simple.
Let's not bullshit each other.
You're here because you fucked up.
We're here to fix that.
So, you show me that
you have a willingness
and desire to change.
Simple as that.
You continue to work hard,
keep your nose clean.
You show a commitment to the
process, leadership capabilities.
When you've shown us
that you can handle
responsibilities beyond
your petty little selves.
Congratulations on that day.
You are now a useful citizen.
You can then write
your ticket out of this place.
Or you can stay, come work for me,
pass on what you've learned.
We take care of our own.
Let me see that watch son.
This watch is a lot
older than you are.
I'll hang on to this. You'll
get it back when you're ready.
Gentlemen, whatever shit
you came in here with...
let it go.
If it was working for you
you wouldn't be here.
Make no mistake, we
will readjust you
because we are goddamn
good at what we do.
I put my heart and my
soul into this process.
I highly recommend you do that too.
All right. Company
dismissed. Powell.
Yes sir.
Ladies, you heard
the man. Dismissed.
Please stop!
Please no! Stop!
Please! Please, stop! No!
Turn around.
Strip.
Turn around and put your
hands against the wall.
Only a couple more
miles guys. Let's go!
Pick it up!
Get in line. Get some water.
When the mail's finished,
water break is finished.
Man, I've got to get some
fucking water. I know that shit.
Come on, hurry up.
Time's up.
Can I have some water?
Let's go boys.
Move! Move!
What in the hell we
digging for anyway?
- Irrigation ditches.
- Irri what?
Irrigation ditches.
So they can water them
fields down there.
Yeah. Okay. Man, I'm
tired as a motherfucker.
Shit. Ain't never hurt
nobody shoplifting.
I'm going to whip some ass after
this shit. What the hell you do?
I just caught real
high with the homies.
This nigger.
What about you?
Did you go cowboy on
some fools or what?
Lucky bastard.
Yo, Trevor. Come on man.
Pop up.
Hey, Trevor.
What you don't want lunch?
What the fuck? No, no, no.
Wait, wait. No, no. Powell! Powell!
Trevor what you... Powell!
Open your eyes! Open your
eyes! Up, up, up, up, up, up.
Trevor come on, come on, come on,
come on. Trevor open your eyes!
Powell! Get his arm.
Get his arm. Get his arms.
Come on! Come on!
Come on man! Come on!
Stop thinking about it.
What?
It's impossible. We're in
the middle of nowhere, man.
- Boots or no boots.
- What am I thinking about?
That fool Trevor made it
out a few months back.
Up and over the fence.
His fucking family
brought him back.
They fucked him up good for that.
Yeah. We didn't see
him for a while.
That's when they put a
second double down.
Now even trustee can't get out.
I don't know. I think he's got a
key hidden somewhere though.
How long have you been here?
A long fucking time.
What? For getting high?
Come on, man.
Just go to bed.
Jesus.
He's sleeping like a baby. He
must have blown his load already.
His parents will
get a bill if he did.
Hey, you know you
can't jerk off, right?
Come on.
You better get off me like that.
- What the fuck you doing?
- What'd I do? What'd I do?
- Go.
- What'd I do?
Shut the fuck up.
100 degrees most days.
You pass out in the dirt and
they'll just let you cook.
They broke you down.
If you couldn't take it
they took your privileges.
They took your sleep.
Still some guys like to talk tough.
Some guys were just fucking crazy.
You're not taking my boots.
Casey, put it down.
Drop the weapon.
You want these boots,
come and get these boots.
- Step back.
- Come and get them.
- Come on! Come on!
- Drop the weapon.
I don't fucking need this.
Let's do this. Come on, let's go.
After a few weeks mostly
everyone starts to lose it.
Everyday was the same. Until
you weren't you anymore.
It was all routine.
Come on. Watch it,
watch it, watch it.
- Shut up.
- Ow, man.
You'll be back in the
barracks tonight.
I'll be coming in to check on you. You'll
be off your feet for at least a week.
Fine with me, man. It's a
week away from them assholes.
- Yo, is Manny out to lunch?
- What's up man?
- Yeah.
- Oh, thank God.
I'm telling you man if you
want that shit sold I got you.
- Just throw me a little something man.
- Put that shit away man.
Okay.
- Carburetor's flooded.
- Yeah?
- I need a... Phillips head.
- Cool. Yeah.
Oh, my God man.
So, you coming to
Holly's party tomorrow?
Oh, yeah.
- I heard she wants to rape you, dude.
- Yeah? Oh, shit man.
I need to get up on that.
- Yeah dude.
- Where's it at?
It's end of Highland Trail.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah, you've been there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I know.
Yo, B! What's up?
Hey, man, can I holler
at you real quick?
Fuck. Yo, I'll be right back.
Come on, dude. We got places to be.
Don't just show up to where I work.
I told you if you want to deal with
me call me like everybody else.
Yeah, yeah. It won't happen again.
Give me my money.
You want it give me the
money or fuck off.
What the fuck are
you looking at, yo?
Yo, you need to get to stepping.
What? No?
What is this, huh? You come in to
my work and you fucking short me?
Chill. All right. What?
Give it back to him.
- You want it back? Here.
- No, no, no. I don't want it back,
but the last time I fronted you two
assholes you took your sweet ass time.
I want the rest tomorrow
or I'm done with you.
I'm sick of this you
fucking speed freaks.
Oh, all right. Yeah maybe we'll bring
it by that party tomorrow night, huh?
Where'd you say it
was? Highland Trail?
Look at this face, yo.
Shit man.
Shit what? Next time
stand up for yourself.
Jonas didn't kick at the
ATV. Powell hit him.
So, you're telling me that Powell and
my trustee are both lying to me?
Your trustee was nowhere
near us. He didn't see anything.
Counselor step out.
Close the door behind you.
All right, look.
If you make enemies in here your road is
going to be very long and a painful one.
Jonas is not a victim. Neither are
you. I want to keep it that way.
Last couple of weeks you've
shown good progress.
Keep that momentum.
That's how trust is built.
So, tell me. Can I trust you?
That a boy.
You're dismissed Lunders.
So, the stories you
write every night,
I mean do you just make
them up as you go...
or is it based on actual
outside experiences?
No, Brad. It's a barracks report.
So what happens outside the barracks
isn't important. So shut the fuck up.
Since we're in the barracks now you
should probably write this down.
You're a chicken shit
fucking weakling.
You could have protected him, but you
just go along with their bullshit lies.
I wish...
I wish I could get the chance
to fucking come at you...
and not have anything happen to me
because I would tear you the fuck apart.
You fucking pussy.
I'm really not surprised you're
a trustee of a place like this.
You're messing with me.
- Okay. Maybe a little.
- You can tell her it was amazing.
- Yeah, you are. Better.
- Okay.
Hey. Hey. Behave yourself.
You're the only one
I can count on, Erin.
I'll see you tomorrow, okay?
Mm-hm.
- If you start doing business there...
- No, no. I won't.
- Promise?
- Yeah.
- Okay. Okay.
- Trust me.
- Yeah. Okay.
- Okay. I'll see you tomorrow.
Bye.
Listen, we've given
this a lot of thought,
and I think it's time that
John came to live with us.
You guys are selling the house?
No. We're not selling the
house. He's moving in.
I love your mother very much, Brad.
I just want to make her happy.
- Oh, shit. Here we go.
- What? Look...
- I know we've had trouble communicating...
- Wait a minute. You know what?
You've never even
given John a chance.
Yeah, well he's not
moving into this house.
Yes. He's here almost every
night already anyway.
Fine. Come and go then.
Mow his lawn.
Take his couch. Sleep
with his fucking wife.
- Whoa. That's not what this is about.
- You know what? Watch your mouth, young man.
Yeah, what kind of fucking
friend were you anyway? Huh?
Thanks for dinner.
Come on wake up time!
- Let's go!
- Let's go! Get up! Get up!
Let's go! Today.
Let's go.
- How's the foot?
- How you think?
Let's go.
Yeah, the fuck okay.
I can't do shit.
Sure you can. It's been
a week. Nothing's broke.
No, he can't. Jenson was here
yesterday. He doesn't run.
Trustee, has this inmate walked to
and from the shower by himself?
Yes, sir.
Trustee, has this inmate walked to
and from the mess hall by himself?
Yes, sir. Twice now.
In the trustee's opinion, can this
inmate take part in this morning's run?
Yes, sir. I'd recommend boots.
Everyone, fall in.
Let's go!
Whew, man.
Brad Lunders.
Dude be swiping maps
and first aid and shit.
I'm taking you to the doctor's
tomorrow so he can fix this up.
Then you can steal something.
Yeah, right. I don't care.
I learned my lesson.
Shit.
I don't know how much my dad paid, but I
fucking hate him for sending me here.
What about your mom?
Well, she don't know where I am.
Mom fucking split, I was like 10.
I don't think my dad would be
that proud of me right now.
I wouldn't be here
I know that much.
I'd rather be in juvie.
At least I know when
I'm getting out.
At least I could call someone.
At least I'd know when I'd
be hitting it again, baby.
Man, you got a girl
waiting on you back home?
I had a girlfriend.
- Pretty?
- Yeah, man.
She was... beautiful.
What? She break up with you?
How about some more of your stash?
Got bills to pay too motherfucker.
- This is from today?
- Today.
Shit. Maybe.
Hey, motherfucker. Don't I know you?
What the fuck?
I know you from...
- Get the fuck out of my face, man.
- What the fuck?
Get the fuck out. What?
What? What? Roll boy.
I don't fucking know you bitch.
See I don't take any shit.
Hey. Look me in the
eyes and say it.
I said I won't take nothing
from nobody. Ever.
You need a fucking drink.
Better go talk to Erin, fool.
She's been looking for
you all pissed and shit.
Don't look. She's behind you. She's coming.
I'm going to talk to Holly. All right?
- Hey.
- You're an asshole.
Where were you? I've
been calling you all day.
Just been dealing with
some bullshit. Come here.
Come here. I need to talk to you.
- So, you did get fired?
- Yes.
And Gabriel got fired.
We both got fired.
Got caught dealing.
- What's the money for?
- What money Erin?
The money I saw Gabriel give
you outside. What was it for?
So, you're spying on me now?
What does he owe you
money for Brad?
- Is Gabriel dealing for you?
- I'm not doing this.
We're having this conversation.
Gabe does what he wants to.
Get off my fucking back.
I told you. He's not going
to be dealing for me.
Fine. How are you going
to get him to stop now?
- Are you fucking...
- No, I'm not kidding.
What are you going to do when your
probation officer talks to your boss?
- Seriously?
- I don't know!
I don't know what I'm going
to do. I can't go back to juvie.
I can't stay here. And I can't
leave. I can't get out of here.
You can fucking get out
by yourself. Just go.
Just go! If you want to...
Hey, you guys need to
leave. I think it's time...
Fuck you bitch. Get
the fuck out of here.
- Get the fuck out of here before...
- Yo, Eddie. What's up dude?
Fucker.
Piece of shit.
Fucker!
You fucking bitch!
Hey! Brad! Stop it! Stop it!
Get off of him! Stop it.
- What's up now motherfucker?
- What the fuck are you doing? Stop!
- He's got a gun.
- You want to fight motherfucker?
You want to go bitch?
No! Erin!
Why?
Erin! No!
Get some help. Please get
some fucking help! Erin!
God fucking damnit!
Whoa. Damn.
That's fucked up, man.
That's some hard shit.
Well, we ain't going to accomplish
anything in this motherfucker.
These counselors are a
bunch of tools, homie.
You will leave Coldwater
Ranch a responsible adult.
Hey, you guys. Shut the fuck up.
25 miles, man. That's it.
Might be here a while first.
So, I got your back.
Get up! Move! Move!
Get up! Move it! Move it! Move it!
Get up!
- Explain this.
- It's for his ankle. It's infected.
I told you I snagged it from the
doc after he fixed my foot.
And I suppose you're
going to use this...
as a bandage?
Look, I fucking took that.
Okay? I took that.
It was me. He had
nothing to do with it.
Hm.
Double runs everyone.
Next two days.
And no downtime for a week.
These two get another
day to reflect.
Don't forget the lights.
Get the fuck out of here.
Little bitch.
Hey, Brad.
Brad, you awake? Brad.
Fucking nigger cripple.
Turn.
Jonas!
Shut the fuck up.
My leg hurts so bad.
I can't take it anymore.
I can't take this.
Help!
Let us the fuck out of here.
Yeah. Yeah. I can still escape.
What are you talking about?
Yeah, I'll be there. Absolutely.
Hey, Brownie! Brownie I've got a...
I'll call you back all right?
Come on.
Angie it was an accident.
It's right there on the report.
You've talked to everybody and we are
dealing with the individuals involved.
He lost the whole
fucking leg, Frank.
I know that, but we did
it by the numbers here.
He was injured. He was
treated, monitored,
- ...there was follow up care.
- The bruising on his neck.
That happened in the barracks.
- That's an entirely separate situation.
- And his testimony.
You've got Lunders' testimony.
Your counselor is lying
and I think you know it.
I've got to tell you. You've
got a big fight coming up.
You put me in a bad place, Frank.
All right, Mr. Reichert,
I forgot to ask you how do the inmates
get out of the barracks in an emergency?
Oh, there's a hidden key. The
trustees have access to it.
A hidden key. Okay.
Which trustees?
- All of them.
- All of them. Okay.
- I'm sorry.
- You're sorry?
- Yeah, I'm sorry.
- You are a fucking virus.
I wouldn't even make you a
fucking trustee right now.
I want you off my campus.
Go. You're fired.
Don't do this.
Don't fucking tell me don't do
this. Get the fuck out of here.
You have ten minutes. Pack
your shit and get out.
Hey.
Do you know what they're going
to do to us in the morning
when they see that you're gone?
That's if they don't pull a surprise
count. The next one's in four hours.
No.
You better make it worth our
while and get away with it then.
Key.
Level three.
He's gone. Must have used
something to get over the fence.
Hey. You all right?
You have no idea how
good this is right now.
Come on. This way.
Uh, Brad, this is Deputy Cross.
Hi Brad.
He's going to help you.
I told him your story and I really think
that you should be talking to him.
Everything's going to be fine.
You all right?
I'm sorry, but I have
to take you back.
Maybe if you had some
sort of evidence,
proof to back up your story
things might be different.
I want you to have
this. It was my dad's.
It's yours now.
Are you serious?
Thanks Deputy. You give
the Sheriff my best now.
All we ask of you is hard work, respect
and the willingness to change.
This young man failed at all three.
Now, he could be any one
of you. So, what do I do?
Do I just give up on him?
Do I send him away
like his parents did?
No.
We are in the business
of transformation.
That means I am patient.
It also means that he must be
held accountable for his actions.
Take off your clothes son.
What?
Take your clothes off.
Stop. Please.
Open your mouth.
Open your mouth. Eat the fish.
- You eat that shit.
- Shut the fuck up.
Eat the goddamn fish.
Eat the fucking fi...
Come on. Let's go.
Get up.
Stay there.
The bastards just keep
on coming don't they?
You're on E.
What happened to your family?
Wife ran off with the
fucking yoga teacher.
Kid...
put a bullet in his own head,
end of his second tour.
You got what it takes kid. You're
going to be wearing blue real soon.
What the fuck?
What the fuck are you? What are you the
fucking Gerber fucking baby, boy? Huh?
What's your name son?
- Billy Heckler, sir.
You got tits, man.
What are you in for?
- Bad grades and ditching.
- Ditching?
Ooh! Gerber's a bad ass.
Ditched a class.
They're going to love you
Gerber. Fucking Gerber.
Oh, it's funny, huh?
It's fucking funny.
Where you from?
Huh, where you from?
- Plymouth.
- Plymouth, ooh.
Yeah, one of them
religious pricks, huh?
Guess it never answers
your prayers, huh?
What the fuck? Get them
the fuck out of here.
Holy shit. Brad.
Either of you know engines?
Yeah, yeah. I know a little.
Let's go.
How long has it been, man?
It feels like fucking
forever, dog. Come here.
Fill the tank.
All right.
Whew. Fucking... I can't
believe it's you, man.
It's like you were dead, man. Your
mom didn't tell anyone anything.
What are you doing here?
Couple of months went by, man,
I got busted for some stash.
You know, I was in
juvie almost nine.
Fucking this morning State social
worker doesn't like me, man.
You know what she
tells my parents...
Listen, hey. She tells
them too much fighting.
No change of behavior. Only a
matter of time before state time.
Blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah. All that shit.
Guess our moms are
still talking, huh?
She'll get a discount now.
What's up with you, man?
What's wrong, fool?
What are you doing here Gabe?
After everything that happened,
why are you here right now?
Nice to see you too.
What do you want me to
fucking say to you Gabe?
- Do you know where the fuck you are?
- Oh, please. I ain't like I was...
back in the day, little bitch and
shit. Yo, I'm down now. I swear.
How about you? They
letting your ass out soon?
- Soon.
- Okay, well how long's soon?
Oh, I see. You're moving
up in the world, huh?
I'm a trustee. It keeps
them off my back.
Man, you a trustee?
You been out in these
weeds all this time, huh?
I thought those assholes in the van were
bad. Man, that Colonel is off his rocker.
It doesn't matter what I say. You
don't fucking get it. This isn't juvie.
This isn't some drug deal on the
corner. This is something else.
All right. What the fuck do
you think I'm going to do?
Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
- You got something to say, inmate?
- No, sir.
- If I did I would have said it.
- Hey, finish up.
Good.
Lunders, what crimes
did you commit?
Underage drinking, battery and
violation of probation, sir.
What are you going to do
about that Mr. Lunders?
I'm learning to be
a better citizen.
So when I return to mainstream society
I can function as a responsible adult.
All right. Let's go. Let's go.
Come on Lunders. What the fuck?
You look tired.
What the fuck's he doing?
I think he's...
probably waiting on
his boyfriend. Right?
I think so. I think so.
Sorry.
- You want some?
- That sucks.
There's a little bit
left if you want some.
Pick it up girls. Come on.
You know Holly and I were
together for a while before juvie.
She got knocked up
by some white boy.
Oh, good.
Yeah, it's pretty
fucked up sometimes.
I mean I think about
that night a lot.
Used to see her parents around town once
in a while too. They hardly looked at me.
You're not going to do
this right now, are you?
Colonel wants a word with you.
What the fuck? Right now?
They want you with the others.
If you can't do it I can probably bullshit
you into the infirmary for a few hours.
- I'll tell Jenson it's dehydration.
- Get these fucking handcuffs off.
Listen, a kid lost his
fucking leg here last year.
There's a big lawsuit and
this place is going to shit.
So, until they pull the fucking plug you
have to play along or I can't help you.
You won't be here long.
Yeah, well you know what? I can
fucking take care of myself.
Good, then fucking
take care of yourself.
Did you check his papers Josh?
Who Nunez? No, I did
not check his papers.
I will ask him.
Good job. I'm sorry.
What the fuck? You got a fucking
death wish motherfucker?
- I'll take care of it. I'll handle it.
- Yeah, you handle it.
You fucking handle it over there.
You handle your little boyfriend.
- You know what you're a lot of talk.
- Oh, yeah? I'm a lot of talk?
Yeah, fuck you. Fuck you.
If it was up to me I'd treat you like
the fucking pussy you are and I'd take
that armband off you and I'd beat you
down like all your fucking friends.
Yeah, fuck you. I'm not
going to cry about it.
I'm going to beat the shit out
of you. You fucking piece of shit.
- Let's go.
- Fuck you. Let's go.
I got you Josh.
Clock this motherfucker.
Come on!
Let's go!
- Get up Josh.
- Come on. Come on.
Get in there. Get up.
Get up. Come on.
Stay down.
- Josh...
- Come on. He's done. Walk with me.
Fuck!
Come on you fat fucks. Move it.
Do not let me fucking catch you.
What you looking at, huh? What the
fuck you looking at? Stupid fuck!
Up that fucking hill! Move! Move!
What the...
What the fuck?
Bitch.
- You fucking finished yet?
- Yes, sir.
Then why the fuck won't it work?
I don't know, sir.
The tank's topped off.
It's water. It's fucking water.
That's why it won't fucking work.
Who the fuck did this? Don't
tell me you don't fucking know!
I will bust you down
to fucking level one.
You want to fuck with me? Huh?
I'll rip you a new fucking asshole.
No more privileges. No more downtime.
Now push that piece of shit
back to the fucking garage
where the fuck it belongs.
You can thank your
trustee for that.
I want to know who the fuck
did this. Is that fucking clear?
Yes, sir.
Why the fuck are you standing there?
Get the fuck out of my way.
Move it! Fucking move it now!
Watch it. Watch it.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Let's go.
Pick him up. There we go.
All right. Well.
Let's go. Come on.
Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go, Brad.
Look if you don't fess up to
putting water in the tank
everyone of these kids are going to
be gunning for you in the barracks.
Fuck 'em. They're animals.
- You going to die me out?
- I won't have to.
They're not stupid.
Besides, why do you
think they haven't yet?
Wow. Go on.
Don't do me any favors big
bro. I can handle my shit.
Fuck you then.
Fine.
Pick up your goddamn tray!
All right listen up.
Your trustee has got something
he wants to tell you.
It's better if it comes from you.
Gabriel filled the gas tank
with water yesterday.
He's confessed.
All right. The trustee just showed
you what progress looks like.
He's leaving all that Plymouth,
homeboy bullshit behind him.
Nunez I suggest you follow
in your friend's footsteps.
He ain't my motherfucking
friend, man.
Does anybody actually know he's here for
killing his girlfriend? Anybody know that?
- It's a lot worse than that.
- Oh, it's a lot worse than that?
Well, why don't you tell
them why you're here. Huh?
Fuck man. I thought
you were my brother.
Yeah, well. That's
where you fucked up.
That's where I fucked up?
- That's where I fucked up? Huh?
- Yeah, you fucked up.
That's where I fucked
up, huh? Fucked up, huh?
Yeah, listen to your boss, man.
Listen to your fucking boss.
Yeah, keep walking.
Don't even fucking move.
All right.
We make mistakes.
That's why we're here.
Here's something funny. Somebody
stole my master key yesterday.
I am pretty fucking
sure it was you.
- What's up? Hm?
- What's up?
Oh, you're going to find out.
Oh, no.
One last time.
Where is my key?
I didn't take your
fucking key, man.
I don't know what fucking key
you're talking about. Okay?
Hm.
What fucking key? I don't know what
fucking key you're talking about, man.
What I...
Get the fuck off me.
Come on. Stay still.
Stop it!
Please! Please! I didn't take
your fucking key! Please, please.
I didn't take your fucking
key. I swear to God!
Come on!
That's enough.
Oh, what the fuck is this?
What happened to him?
Let's get you something to eat.
Yo! Yeah you going to let
him fool you guys too?
You know what? You make me fucking sick
coming in here marking your clipboards,
wearing your suits, backing
up to this son of a bitch.
You ain't any better than him. Waddle,
waddle. You got something to say old man?
Gabriel!
Yeah, that's right. Get the fuck out
of here pencil-pushing motherfuckers.
What are you doing?
They won't say shit because the minute
you leave they'll get beat for it.
- Get the fuck out of here.
- You're digging your own fucking grave.
This is it right here.
Fuck you. Get the fuck out
of here. Keep walking.
Get off me!
There's a hearing next week.
You called them didn't
you? Jesus Christ.
I should have let you
kill yourself Jenson.
That way you could just die on
your own terms, on your own time.
Nope. I couldn't let you hit bottom.
Could I? Had to give you responsibility.
Guess what?
All this, everything
that's kept you alive...
is going away, man. It's gone.
There's not a goddamn thing you
can do about it. You are fucked.
I'm fucked. At least I can rebuild.
I mean I'm going to start again.
I've got guys who want it,
got their shit together.
Not guys fucked up like you.
You catatonic, broken prick.
We're done. Got that?
So that means you can steal
all the syringes you want,
all the meds. Take 'em all.
I don't really give a fuck anymore.
Really. I don't care.
All I want are my medical files
and your keys on my desk.
You're on your own.
- The doc needs to see me.
- Stop, stop, stop.
He'll let me back in. Don't worry.
They're going to kill you
if you stay here, OK?
I need you to jump the fence and get
to Lincoln. It's 25 miles from here.
When you get there go
to the Sheriff's office
and ask for Deputy Cross
and give him this. It's...
It's your medical file. It's
all of doc's patchwork.
I wrote everything that
happened to you on the back.
They're not going to
send you back with this.
Get it to them. It's
25 miles, say it.
Gabe, 25 miles. I need
you to say it. 25 miles.
Yeah, okay. 25 miles. I got it.
Good. You can do this.
Yeah, I can make it.
- Hey, where'd you get this?
- Just take it.
It's yours.
I'm sorry.
What are you going to do?
I'll be fine. You should go though.
I don't know.
If those guys hadn't heard us talking
under the car about Holly's party...
none of this would have happened.
Maybe.
I'll see you Gabe.
Jenson. Jenson.
What the fuck?
Jenson?
Hey, this is Josh in the infirmary.
You guys have to get over
here right now. Fuck.
Colonel, what's your 20?
Colonel? Come in.
Help!
You've got to come to the infirmary!
Right now. Come on! Come on!
...not responding. Lunders!
Lunders. Sorry, my
radio was turned off.
Where are you right now?
I'm in the barracks. Where
the fuck do you think I am?
Who let you back in the barracks?
Jenson.
10-4.
All right.
You all know Gabriel is AWOL.
The authorities have been notified
so until the end of the day you're
confined to your barracks. I'm sorry.
Now...
Dr. Jenson was found dead in
his office earlier this morning.
The Sheriff's Department
is on its way.
So, I don't really know
if there's anything else...
It appears Mr. Jenson put
himself out of his own misery.
Now, if one of you gentlemen
broke in and killed him, fine.
Medical files have gone missing.
Those are Coldwater property.
If I don't have them back by sundown
I will kill each and every one of you.
- Get them inside.
- Come on. Let's go.
Gabriel was sneaky wasn't he?
Sneaky with the counselors.
Sneaky with that gas
thing, the truck.
See, here's the thing
that I don't understand
is how did he get down
off that crossbeam?
I don't know.
Ain't that a bitch.
Dispatch to Morgan. You still
at the Coldwater compound?
10-9.
Copy that. I'm on my way.
Use long-range recon.
All right. Let me get back to you.
Sir... they found a body on
the side of the forest road.
Male, possibly Hispanic,
15-17 years old,
red t-shirt, blue jeans.
Looks like one of yours.
We're going to need you and another
witness to identify the body.
There was blunt head
and facial trauma.
Probable broken neck from falling
head first after he crossed the road.
It was dark. The forest
road had no light and...
there's a steep drop
where he crossed.
All other wounds and
injuries are accounted
for in the medical file you
supplied Gabriel with.
Along with your written testimony.
The only real backup
for your story so far.
So, at this point you had no idea what was
going on at the ranch while you were gone.
What the fuck, man?
Fuck you!
How about now? How about now?
Huh? Hoorah motherfucker. Yeah!
Fuck, Colonel you need to
come in right now! Fuck!
Okay. Okay. Okay.
You guys need to listen to me.
Just look at me. Look at me.
I'm not going to tell anybody.
I just want to go home.
Listen to me! All right?
You need to let me go.
This isn't me and this isn't fair.
I'm not going to tell anybody.
Stop it! Stop it!
Who's got the pickax now
motherfucker? Who wants it?
So, you get back to the ranch, with
the Colonel. You saw what happened.
The Colonel retires to
his office. Then what?
I heard a shot.
Anything else?
I called Lincoln Sheriff's office.
Listen... can I get
some water, please?
Sure.
His mom's here.
Honey!
I'm so sorry.
I love you so much.
I love you so much, honey.
I'm so sorry about Gabriel.
I can't even believe it.
Brad!
No, sir. Not right now.
Yeah, I'm waiting to hear back from them.
They've got a real mess on their hands.
Let me call you back. All right?
It was late afternoon yesterday,
several inmates who either witnessed
or notified authorities of the
murders were brought in...
You believe this shit?
Below you're looking at one of the
inmates from the facility right now.
It's my understanding that there are about
two dozen officers surrounding him.
Caught four more
outside Lincoln County.
What do you think
of Lunder's story?
- He left a lot out.
- That's for sure.
Lincoln County Sheriff's here.
It's going to be pretty crazy for a
while with the media. All right?
I'm taking you to
another facility first.
Sir... they found a body
on the side of forest road.
Male, possibly Hispanic,
15-17 years old.
Red t-shirt, blue jeans.
Looks like one of yours.
I'm going to need you and another
witness to identify the body.
Brad, did you know Gabriel
Nunez died trying to escape?