So, first off, thanks for
stopping by my blog...
today, I'm with Tara Reiner.
Hi everyone!
She's just bought some
new clothes from the mall,
and we're going to go
through each of them,
and talk about them.
This is my second favorite shirt...
Are you okay?
I just want to go home!
If anyone is watching this, please!
Hey, you've reached Dan.
Leave a message...
Dan, hey.
Where are you?
I'm here.
So when you get this,
give me a call back.
Hey.
Where are you?
Um, I'm just at Rob's.
Who's Rob?
You actually don't know him.
So, are you not coming to meet me?
Uh, I'm gonna try a little
bit later, actually.
Who's that?
Uh, she's a friend of Rob's.
Who's that girl that
posted on your page?
What are you talking about?
Why didn't you come
over last night?
I need to talk to you in person.
Um, I'm gonna try and come
over a little bit later, okay?
Can you please get off your phone?
Uh, one second...
Dan, are you serious?
I have to tell you something.
It's cool.
I'm sorry, what's cool?
I feel like you want
to take a break.
Okay, I get it.
I'm down with that.
I was actually thinking
about the same thing.
It might do us both some good.
Look, I'll call you later.
Dan...
Happy New Year's Eve, everybody.
I'm assuming that if you're here
because you didn't do
very well on your finals.
I don't want to be here either,
but we've got to do this, okay?
So the first set of slides
that we're going to
go right into now
is the Darrison Hotel crime scene.
And this time, I suggest
everybody take some notes.
Sam, are you still there?
Hello?
Hey, yeah. Sorry.
This kid just...
How's criminology?
I can't believe you had
class on New Year's Eve.
Yeah, I don't know.
It was all right.
Everyone I know
has two weeks off.
All us medical undergrads are
working hard saving lives, okay?
We deserve our time off.
So you're coming tonight, right?
Be one to remember, I promise.
I don't know, Mark.
I think I'm just gonna stay in.
I've had a rough day, so...
I know, I saw.
Of course you did.
Private life is public knowledge.
I'll try to swing
by on my way home,
but I can't stay all night.
Happy New Year!
Hello?
Guys...
Ahh!
Fuck!
Oh, shit!
Ah...
Yup, m-hm.
Yeah, you definitely broke my nose.
Serves you right, Jed.
All his idea.
Glad you came, Sam.
Sam...
I hear you're back on the market.
- I think you've had too much, baby.
- Shh...
Hi, Sam!
I don't think we've met.
I'm Kaitlin.
Yeah, that really backfired.
So... really single now?
Anyways, I got 300
babe tickets here,
fresh off the press.
I'm gonna go hand these
out, you comin'?
- Probably not.
- What?
Fine then.
Anyone?
Wait! Quick photo before
we're all hammered?
I'm out.
Yeah,
yeah... whoa.
Cool, I'll link everyone.
Uh, Sam...
I need to add you.
- What's your last name?
- I deleted my account.
Nice!
Huh?
Oh, so... how do you keep
in touch with people?
I see them in person?
Whatever, I'll link you anyway.
Okay, say cheese.
Your dad's in Spain?
I thought he was in Mexico.
I don't know anymore.
It's the last I heard from him.
Same old, same old.
So what happened with you and Dan?
We broke up.
Guys suck.
Just the ones you date.
What sucks even more
is that I feel like
everyone knew before me.
People posting comments,
judging me on the Social Redroom.
Things no one would ever
say that to my face,
but online it's so easy.
Whatever.
Sorry, I think I'm just tired.
Further notice, please keep
windows and doors lock...
And sites like MySocial,
and the Social Redroom
give an unrealistic
view of the world!
These are theories,
they're conspiracy theories.
I don't -
Where's the proof?
Show me the proof.
It's social networking.
Eight billion pe...
What, are you filming this?
Well, I figure one
day you'll be famous
and we can release a sex tape.
Make millions.
And I can just, you know,
live in a big house
drinking champagne for breakfast.
Right, right.
Oh!
Not so fast.
Well, you know,
I don't mind the teasing, but, um...
I think we'll make
more millions if, uh...
you're on the camera!
What do you want me to do?
What are you willing to do?
I need some music.
Okay.
♪ ...is a reflection of now ♪
♪ Time draws near ♪
♪ Your faith comes
crumbling to the ground ♪
- Why is that so bizarre?
- I'm very concerned!
You should be concerned!
Your viewers should be concerned!
America should be con...
Today's incident has stirred
many painful memories
of last month's suicide
of 22-year old Cal Spencer
who took his life
after bullying messages
were posted on the
popular media site,
the Social Redroom Inc.
This leaves two more students
dead after today's events.
Mark...
Mark!
I don't know,
I feel like I just want to get
away for a while, you know?
Maybe just transfer.
Seriously?
Because of Dan?
It's not just because of Dan.
Mark!
I don't get you sometimes.
You're always takin' off.
Why don't you just
stop for a second
and try and sort it out?
I could help you.
Yo, Marky!
Would you just go see
what he's yelling about?
Yeah.
- What do you want, Jed?
- Look...
At approximately 4pm today,
police shot and killed
Jeremy Dubrowsky,
a two-year computer science
student at Kindred College.
This occurred immediately
following at attack by Dubrowsky
on another student,
yet to be identified.
Both students were pronounced
dead at the scene.
Police have yet to determine
Dubrowsky's motive
for attacking his fellow student,
however, early reports say
Dubrowsky was a recent target
of cyberbullying.
I saw that guy today.
This is just one of
four similar incidents
that have happened in the area
in the last few hours.
Although the official
causes are yet unknown,
police say the recent
increase of cyberbullying
may have played a role.
Ugh, come on, dude,
you're still in your dorm?
Have you seen what's going on?
About the student?
Yeah, it's brutal.
Yeah, well, that's not the
only thing that's happening.
There's cops everywhere,
and the entire residence
is on lock-down.
Okay, answer this.
There's something you gotta hear.
Listen...
Dude... dude,
what was that?
I've been hearing
that for the last hour.
It's creepy as hell.
They're telling us to
keep our doors locked.
I'm gonna send you some footage...
stuff that they're
not showing on TV.
All right, well,
just get over here quick, man,
where it's safe.
Reports are coming in from
all across the country.
We urge people to stay indoors,
and not let anyone in.
Following the violent deaths
of three students
at Kindred College,
more details are coming
of similar incidents
across the country.
Various student suicides
and physical attacks
in Burbank, Washington
have now been reported.
Authorities are now urging
people to stay indoors
and to not let any strangers
inside their homes.
As more reports flood in
from around the world,
we at CCAC News will
continue our coverage.
You can also visit our website
to see user-submitted
videos and photos
of these and other events.
The lights were flickering,
and I think that it's
whenever they come near,
like, they do something weird
to the electricity or something.
Riot in Los Angeles
takes the lives of twenty seven...
Fires rage throughout Bangkok
as the infection spreads.
♪ Time draws near ♪
♪ Your faith comes
crumbling to the ground ♪
♪ Still no one's around. ♪
♪ You, you don't
really want to go now ♪
♪ You can feel your
heart slow down ♪
♪ Are you ready for the showdown ♪
Yo, something's seriously
fucked up in Brian's res.
They're telling everyone
to lock all the doors.
The news said the same thing.
Yeah, um...
About that...
We're throwing a kick-ass
New Year's party here tonight.
Anyone see the problem
with not letting people in?
I mean,
what if the world really
is ending at 12:01?
What if this the year it
finally all just... stops?
Don't you want to go
out with some style?
The world isn't ending, Jed.
The media hypes these
events, you know that.
All right, well, what
if it's terrorists?
Jed, it's not terrorists.
I don't see anything.
Sam!
♪ It's time to
stand up and go now ♪
♪ Better be ready
for the showdown... ♪
This... is definitely better
than the party downstairs.
What was that?
What the fuck?
Hey!
You've got two seconds
to get out, man!
Steve!
I said get out!
Steve?
Steve...
What was he doing?
He attacked me.
He didn't mean to do it.
Did you do that?
It was an accident, okay?
He smashed through the door,
and then Steve had to push him out,
and he tripped and he
fell off the balcony.
Is he dead?
He looks pretty fucking dead.
Oh my god.
I barely touched him.
I told him to leave!
It looks like they're
calling the cops, now...
- I think we call 9-1-1 right now!
- No!
It will look better if it
comes from us, all right?
Someone tried to get
in downstairs too.
Something's go on, Steve!
Yeah, they've been telling
us not to let anyone in.
- He's dead!
- Someone tried to grab Sam!
And the news was saying
that we can't let anyone in!
Guys...
Listen.
Due to the high volume,
we cannot receive
calls at the moment.
We strongly urge you to remain
calm, lock your premises,
and do not let anyone
in or out of your homes.
I've never heard a message
like that before.
9-1-1 isn't supposed to
have an answering machine!
We've got to go down.
It'll be okay.
Get the lights!
Mark, what are you doing?
What the fuck are they shooting at?
Quiet!
No one gets in, right?
Yeah, well, that's what they said.
Mark, man...
There's a lot of people outside.
Jed, the lights!
Steve, you sure
picked the right night
to throw a dude out the window.
Okay, okay, just
keep the lights off
and try to be quiet.
Shit!
This is gonna keep happening!
We've got to barricade this place!
Windows, doors, everything!
It's okay.
We need to do it now!
Turn your phone off!
More than a thousand,
and the numbers...
Check the back door.
People infected seem to be getting
increasingly aggressive,
angry, violent.
Violent outbreaks
have been reported
across the United States...
the lives of 27 as
the police try...
A biological terrorist
attack on New York
leaving hundreds dead...
Bangkok, as infection spreads...
it's a mutation
of H1N1 virus...
keep windows and doors covered,
and please report any
signs of the infection.
The fastest viral
infection ever reported
has now claimed more
than a thousand,
and the numbers are
continuing to rise.
A biological terrorist
attack on New York
leaving hundreds dead...
Leave this child now!
Leave this body!
Hello?
Oh my god.
It says Jeanette was
arrested for murder.
Babe?
What's wrong?
I'm sending you a video link now.
It's basically a
list of the symptoms.
It's disturbing, but it's a list.
Judging by the time
the post was sent,
I'd say the girl got sick sometime
before the reports
started coming out.
I gotta ask you something.
Do you think this is it?
Do you think this is
the end of the world?
I don't know, man.
Sure as shit hope not.
Yeah.
Thanks for
stopping by my blog -
Guys...
Thanks for stopping by my blog.
And don't forget to
follow our videos
on the Bloggernaut,
and the Social Redroom.
Today I'm with Tara Reiner.
Hey, everyone!
Why are we watching this?
Just keep skipping
through it, okay?
Oh my god!
Now go to when she's sitting back
in front of the web cam...
Her ears and her
nose started bleeding.
She said she was seeing things,
and she was crying.
I'm too scared to leave.
I'm trying to be as
quiet as possible
because I hear people outside
and they sound like her.
Whatever she had,
I think it's happening to me.
I'm seeing things too
and they're so real...
Is there anyone watching?
Anyone, please!
Help me!
I can't go any further.
That's 'cause you're caught up.
What you're watching now is live.
I've watched this
a couple times now.
Ears and nose bleeding seems
to be the first symptom.
Shit, I gotta go.
I'll call you right back.
Can we message her?
Yeah, we can send her a
video chat request, I guess.
Mark, get over here.
Quick! Quick!
- Tara?
- Hello?
My name is Sam.
Are you okay?
No, I don't think so.
Can you help me?
Where are you?
What's your address?
I...
I don't...
I don't know.
It's not my home.
Do you have a phone?
Tara?
What's happening?
Yeah, there's definitely
someone outside.
- Hello?
- Chad?
The door's locked,
give me a second!
Mark! Mark!
Wait!
Stop! Stop!
Okay, look!
Look!
Please look...
Guys, it's Chad.
You've got to let me in.
Quick, there's nobody
out here right now.
Look, you've got to
let me in now, please.
Please let me in.
Is that Chad?
Yes.
Are you gonna let him in?
No.
He has the symptom, man.
Okay?
We just watched a video.
First symptom,
you start seeing shit.
Hallucinations, I guess.
Then your nose and your
ears start to bleed.
Just wait, wait!
Wait.
How do we know it's the
same thing as the video?
- I have to open the door.
- No.
Mark, I can hear you.
You can't do this, man.
You don't know what
it's like out here.
We're not supposed to
let anyone in, remember?
Steve, a little help?
How do you actually know
someone's sick, Jed?
Guys, it's Chad!
Yeah, hey...
His nose is bleeding, man.
His freaking ears are bleeding!
I love Chad, all right?
I really do.
But I'm not going to die in here.
Chad, just a second!
They're everywhere.
Look...
You gotta let me in now, okay?
Where else is he gonna go?
Mark wait!
Stop! Stop!
He's sick.
He is sick, man.
Okay?
I'm sorry, Chad.
What?
I can't let you in.
Mark, you gotta
fucking let me in, man.
Go to a hospital, Chad, please!
- You've got to fuckin' let me in!
Dude, let me in, please!
I'm gonna fuckin' die out here.
I'm gonna fuckin' die.
Fuckin' assholes.
No help here?
He almost fuckin' let him in, man!
What the fuck am I
supposed to do, Jed?
Fuck!
I couldn't help him.
Mark...
Mark, look at me.
Mark, please, look at me.
Hey...
I don't know what
I could have done.
You okay?
I don't have it.
Whatever that is, I don't have it.
Sam, you just threw up.
I'm okay, Mark.
We'll figure this out, okay?
I won't tell anyone in the house.
I'm not sick.
I'm pregnant.
What?
I'm pregnant, Mark.
That's why I came here.
To tell you, I guess.
I don't know what
I'm gonna do about it.
About it...
Wait.
Sam...
- I had to leave my floor!
- Why, what's happening?
- I don't know.
- Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
They just keep telling
us to move up one floor.
It's like fucking Russian
Roulette in here.
- I'm fine though.
- All right, good.
- Jed, I'm gonna have
to call you back!
Hey, you've reached Chad
Wilson, leave me a message.
Hey, Chad, it's me again.
Please... call me back, man.
Okay?
There are so many
posts of people dying.
Half of my friends
aren't responding...
Or their messages
don't make any sense.
I just...
I just don't know how
this many people can die.
What the hell was that?
Are you okay?
Yes.
I think I need to lay down.
I think we need to
keep an eye on her.
That's got to be one of the symptoms.
What is she doing?
She must have got
whatever it is
from that other girl.
I mean, this must
be what happens next.
First you're nose
and your ears bleed...
What happens, you get violent?
Yeah, violent, you start
acting crazy, I don't know.
I can't watch this.
You okay?
I wonder if I have it.
How could you have gotten it?
You can't be sick.
I need help, Mark.
Steve...
What are you talking about?
Something bad...
is gonna happen.
Steve, you're just being paranoid.
Take care of Kait.
Steve...
Okay?
I'm sorry.
Mark?
You're not safe, Steve.
Mark...
When it happens,
it will be so rapid.
So fast it won't matter.
They're trying to stop it.
I don't want to hurt them.
Don't fight it, Steve.
It's already happened.
Did you see?
Just now?
They were just here!
Steve, what did you see,
you're scaring me.
Stay away!
Stay... away!
He's infected.
- Jed, we don't know that!
- Yeah...
Come on, man.
I mean, look at him!
Steve!
Kaitlin, get back!
Mark!
No, no!
Steve! Steve!
Mark!
No!
I couldn't stop it.
You need to get away.
Look at your hands.
Mark, you need to get away!
Here, use this.
Put your hands...
Mark, whatever this is...
It's inside now.
Mark...
That wasn't Steve, all right?
I mean,
we can agree on that, right?
Mark...
Whoa, where are you going?
We're not leaving him there.
Fine.
But we're not touching him
unless we're wearing gloves.
We have to figure out what to do.
I can't stay here.
- Mark!
- Oh fuck.
I knew she was sick.
No! No!
She did it, she hit me!
What?
I was just sitting there!
- You're a liar! You did!
- Maybe they both have it.
- Jed, are you serious?
- Sam's not sick.
Please...
All right, well, what do we do now?
I'm okay, guys, honestly.
We tie her up.
Or she leaves.
Mark, we can't send her outside.
Well then we tie her up.
- We should just bash her head in.
- Jed!
What, I'm the odd
man out on this one?
Really?
Go ahead, do it.
Don't bash my head, please.
I wasn't being serious.
Okay, fine, maybe that
was a little harsh,
but we know what happens next!
I was just confused, okay?
I didn't mean to call you a liar.
You can tie me up,
and then you'll see
that I'm not sick.
Yeah, yeah, I'm gonna
go get something.
You okay?
I don't know...
Hey, hey, hey...
It's gonna be okay.
I'll keep you safe.
I know.
I'm not goin' anywhere.
You guys are cute together.
This was all I could find.
We're gonna keep you
upstairs just to be safe.
We'll check on you.
We just don't know what this is.
Why?
Why upstairs?
'Cause we don't want
to catch your crazy.
What is that?
Do you want to be with Steve?
Yes.
Mark, look at the lights!
Hold on to her, Jed!
I've got her!
Fuck...
Fuck!
Mark, it's not your fault.
I don't want to hear it, Sam!
Just...
Help me get her down.
It seems the human loss count
has been more than imagined.
At this time, the cause of
the outbreak is still unknown.
We are going to our emergency
broadcast system at midnight.
Our thoughts and prayers are
with the people of this planet,
and the millions of souls
humanity has lost tonight.
Happy New Year,
and may God be with you.
Holy shit.
Oh my god.
What happened to her?
Someone must have got in.
Can you go back?
Oh my god!
Oh my god, this is fucked up.
This gets worse.
Well, maybe...
maybe it's not worse.
I mean...
They say this is a side effect,
whatever this is that's going on.
What if everybody that has it
eventually... explodes and dies?
I mean...
If that's the case,
then all we need to do is just...
We just gotta wait it out.
Where are you -
Fuck!
Mark?
Hey...
Are you okay?
Why are you still in here?
James Trevor, the owner and CEO
of the extremely popular
networking site,
the Social Redroom
has been shot and killed
in Burbank, California.
Only 45 minutes after
news was released
of the Social
Redroom's involvement
in a recent worldwide
outbreak of violence.
As police escorted
the social media mogul,
a former employee opened fire,
killing Trevor,
and wounding two police officers.
No fuckin' way.
What is this?
It's our basement.
I saw something.
Before I...
Mark, we have to go.
Come on.
Mark, come on.
Why did you do that?
Are you okay?
I don't know.
- Mark...
- I don't think so.
I need you to stay with me.
I'm seeing things.
What if I have it?
- Mark...
- Steve...
tried to leave...
He knew.
I need to.
Please stay.
I can't do this alone.
Mark, please stay.
Don't go, please!
Listen! Listen!
Please stay.
We've been friends forever.
And you've always
been there for me.
I don't know...
I don't know if I ever told
you how much that means.
Maybe I didn't tell you, but...
You mean everything to me.
It's like I pushed everyone away.
Maybe I pushed you
away too, I don't know.
Maybe I...
Maybe I've been really far...
And I'm really sorry.
But right now I'm
asking you to stay.
And it's because I need you.
I really need you.
You don't understand.
I can feel it inside of me.
Mark, you don't have it.
You're fine, you don't have it.
Mark, please!
Mark!
Stay back.
What are you doing?
You need to get away from him, Sam.
You've been on it, right, Mark?
On what?
Jed, put down the knife.
I know what it is.
All right, I know what it is,
I know why people are getting sick.
There's a video...
will you watch it?
Jed, I need to leave -
I need you to watch it, all right?
Yeah?
Okay.
If anybody out there is listening,
please, you have to
believe me when I tell you
that the Social Redroom is to blame.
It is the cause for
this whole epidemic.
For the past three years...
we have been running...
a subliminal pattern
underneath our website,
trying to get users to visit
the website more frequently.
It was impossible for us to
track the billions of users,
so we...
we created a program
to do it for us.
We're supposed to believe this?
Keep watching.
This is the reason
why you feel the need
to add more photos,
to update statuses,
to, uh, um... browse more often.
And the update that
we released this morning...
Well, that is highly
more addictive.
The occasional nosebleed
was the only symptom, but...
they kept the real
side effects a secret.
Oh, god...
hallucinations, and depression,
and violence, you know?
All kept a secret.
After hearing about the
side effects, I, uh...
I tried to shut it down.
But it, uh...
It went into some
sort of survival mode.
Like a biological virus.
It mutated, it started
to change people.
The virus is moving through
those its infected.
It's trying to
eliminate the threat -
which is us.
If you are experiencing
nosebleeds or hallucinations...
There's no hope for you.
But I have posted a link
for those that aren't
experiencing that, okay?
It's risky,
but it might work for you.
I am so sorry.
Jed, this can't be true.
Think about it.
How else could a virus
spread worldwide in a day?
A fucking day!
Billions of people sick
on all different
continents in one night!
I was all right there, Sam!
You need to get away
from him, all right?
Just come over here.
You...
I'm sorry, Mark.
Come here, Sam.
I was on it.
What?
No, you deleted it,
you told us that you deleted it.
Jed, I was just on it upstairs.
Please, Sam!
Fuck.
You're saying that
'cause of him, right?
You don't need to
protect him, all right?
Just come over...
Come over here.
I don't want to be alone.
Please!
Please?
There's a cure.
There might be,
there might be a cure.
There might be, there's a link.
- What?
- What are you talking about?
Well, what is it?
Get the fuck back!
- The drill's downstairs.
- What are you talking about?
I will show you!
Okay.
Okay...
Brian?
Brian!
Dude, where are you?
Brian...
I watched it.
I watched the links,
you were right, dude.
What's going on?
Residence is overrun.
You all right?
Just come over here, man.
I'm trapped on the roof.
Well, is there a fire escape?
Just look for a fire
escape, man, all right?
Don't come any closer!
- I gotta sign off.
- No! You don't!
You gotta wait it out!
No, Jed.
That's it, man,
you just gotta wait it out.
They're dying off, I promise you!
I know.
There's no more time.
Sorry to be a downer
on your party, man.
I don't think I'm gonna make it.
Yeah, well...
The party kind of sucked anyway.
I gotta go.
Brian?
Brian!
He can't hear me.
Please!
Brian, please, please!
Brian, no, no!
No!
Jed!
Jed, don't!
I'm sorry...
Jed!
Hold the door!
Fuck!
Where's the link?
What you are about to see
is a procedure that we feel
might be the cure for
what they are calling
the 'Redroom Virus'.
This virus attacks the
amygdala area of the brain,
which stimulates an
over-production of cells
which creates a new kind of brain
in the form of a tumor.
This is to accommodate
the overwhelming number
of new signals the
brain is receiving
from others infected by the
Social Redroom dot com.
It is this increase in brain mass
that is causing these hallucinations.
From our limited research,
if you are already
experiencing hallucinations,
this surgery will not help you.
It means that the tumor
is already too deeply entrenched.
Before you begin,
make sure that your patient is
immobilized, secured to a
chair or a table with a rope.
Or a belt will suffice.
First, make an incision
at the pre-frontal cortex,
either here or here.
Once you have exposed the skull,
you'll need to drill a small hole
large enough for a hobby knife.
And be careful not to drill too deep.
This is the most important part:
Once the hole is drilled,
a black artery will appear.
This is the artery
that feeds the tumor,
and accelerates the growth.
This increase in brain mass
is the eventual cause
of the skull bursting.
Even after death, the
tumor continues to grow.
We don't know why or how.
This is what you've removed.
That's in our heads?
Is this possible?
What?
No.
It's brain surgery with
a household drill, no.
You heard what he said.
We'll die anyway.
We can't do this.
We have to.
I'm not drilling a hole
in your head, Sam!
That's insane!
Mark, we can do this.
I'm sorry, Sam.
I can't.
I'm sick.
Please don't...
Please don't make me do this.
Okay, then I'll do you first.
If the video's right,
then it's too late for me.
Look at me.
We're not gonna die down here!
What if it doesn't work?
It has to.
We don't have much time.
We have to do this.
Hey...
If something goes wrong...
it's okay.
There's no other way.
What you are about to see
is a procedure that we
feel might be the cure
for what they are calling
the 'Redroom Virus'...
Bite into this.
Which stimulates the
overproduction of cells,
which creates a new kind of brain
in the form of a tumor.
This is to accommodate
the overwhelming number of
new signals the brain is
receiving from others
infected by the Social
Redroom dot com...
She's going to die, Mark.
Why are you fighting us?
What?
Okay, are you ready?
Mark...
You can feel it, Mark.
Chad?
How we're all connected now.
Everyone knows
everything about you.
And you know everything
about everyone else.
If you listen to us...
we can save you.
Your pain...
will be our pain.
You're not really here.
If you operate on
her, she will die.
No.
Mark, focus on me.
Ah...
Mark!
Please don't leave me.
Not you.
I can't do it.
Get... get out.
Mark...
Mark, I can't do this alone.
You're not alone.
I love you.
I love you too, Sam.
Mark...
Mark!
Law enforcement officials...
infected seem to
be coming back...
has shut down networking sites...
will continue to keep
you informed by radio
as long as it's safe...
The brain hemorrhage did
not kill all the infected...
telepathic bond between the dead.