NARRATOR: The year 1453.
From the lands of
Constantinople,
a mighty force of Ottoman
Turks sweep across Romania,
threatening the very
heart of Christendom.
From the ashes of destruction
arose a young Romanian prince,
a knight of the secret
Order of the Dragon.
A direct descendant
of Abel himself,
the prince was charged to vanquish
the Turks from his homeland.
Before leaving for battle,
he appointed his one true
love to rule in his place
until he returned.
He ordered his
four best knights
to guard her with their lives.
Protect her.
Some say he fought
with the power of God.
Others say the blood
of the dragon.
Those who dared
whisper his name
would feel the fear
in their tongues.
Dracula.
Far from the bloody
battlefields,
another war was being
fought at home.
Taking advantage of
their master's absence,
Dracula's own advisors plotted
to overthrow the throne.
Unhappy with the
prince's visionary ways,
the traitors dared not
challenge Dracula directly.
They found his gentle bride
to be a much easier target.
(SCREAMS)
The battle was over,
but the war had just begun.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
My love.
I am victorious.
Elizabeth?
Elizabeth.
What did they do to you?
It was an ambush
your Highness.
Why?
We all tried to defend her.
Now you can join her.
(SCREAMING, GROANING)
I have killed for God,
this I swear:
The hands that fought for him
will now be turned against him.
I renounce him
and all who live
under his name.
(SCREAMS)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
I renounce him
and all who live
under his name.
I have blessed myself,
baptized in blood.
Eternal life begins
after death.
Ours begins now.
Your Highness.
I heard fighting.
I thought it was the Turks.
I have killed for God,
this I swear:
The hands that fought for him
will now be turned against him.
NARRATOR: Some legends
say Dracula was cursed
with immortality as punishment
for his defiance,
to live with his tortured soul
for eternity.
(CROW CAWING)
(ANIMAL HOWLING)
The carriage is too
slow, we must leave it.
Keepers, gather around.
(GRUNTS)
(ANIMAL HOWLS)
MAN: Alina, you take Esme
and go on ahead to the
rendezvous point.
We'll try to meet
up with you there.
We will stay and fight.
You're light and have
the fastest horses.
Find Leonardo, he'll
know what to do.
Come with us.
I'll stay here with
the other knights.
We'll hold them off
as long as we can.
Now go!
(ANIMAL GROWLS)
(ANIMAL HOWLING)
We should move into the forest.
We can lose them there.
We need to stay on the road if
we're going to find Leonardo.
But we'll never make it to him
if the creatures find us first.
Come on.
This way.
- (CREATURE GROWLS)
- (HORSES NEIGHING)
Steady now.
Easy.
(CREATURES ROARING)
Come on, Esme. Faster.
Leonardo should have
been here by now.
This is it.
- Where is he?
- (LEAVES RUSTLING)
- Something's not right.
- (THUNDER RUMBLING)
I don't like the
looks of this place.
- (CREATURE GROWLS)
- What is that?
- (CREATURE ROARS)
- (HORSES NEIGHING)
Esme!
You okay? Esme?
Talk to me.
(GROANS)
Where is your God
now, Crusader?
DRACULA: Wrath, this man
was one of the Keepers.
The Lightbringer isn't here.
Find it.
The Lightbringer
couldn't get far.
Spread out.
Take the prisoners
back to the castle.
The rest of you, follow me.
(WHIP CRACKS)
Look. What is that?
You're going to be okay.
Can you sit up?
Come.
(STICK CRACKS)
Get up.
Get up. Come on.
Come, come, come.
(MEN LAUGH, YELL)
MAN: Who have we got here?
Looks like somebody
lost a pair of wenches.
- Feisty ones at that.
- You're not the undead.
- And you're not knights.
- You're just common thieves.
I'd prefer to think of
us as extremely charming
and witty thieves.
Hmm. I see there's nothing
common about you, either.
- MEN: Ooh.
- (WHISTLES)
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am the great Lucien Merel.
Really, what's so
great about you?
Some would say my excruciatingly
handsome good looks.
Are those people
blind or just drunk?
- Ooh.
- (CHUCKLES)
Look, darling, we want
what's in that box.
So why don't you
just hand it over
and we can all go
on our merry way?
Over our dead bodies.
You'd certainly make a
lovely pair of corpses.
Move along and no
one gets hurt.
(LAUGHS)
(SPEAKS NATIVE LANGUAGE)
We have got you completely surrounded.
(MEN LAUGHING)
What did you do that for?
- I warned you.
- Boys, take the box.
That box is more important
than you could ever imagine.
MAN: Really?
Oh, yeah. I'm real scared.
(GROANS)
- There you go.
- Whoo. Sorry.
Told you we were witty thieves.
We're delivering it to a man
named Leonardo Van Helsing.
- Never heard of him.
- If you want money,
he will pay handsomely
for your assistance.
But if you choose to
steal what's his,
he's a dangerous man.
And so am I.
- Sorry.
- Boys.
See ya later, wenches.
- Wait!
- (GROANS)
Now what?
Take us with you. Just
to the next village.
- This is what I'm talking about.
- Dude, listen, don't do it.
- This is what happened last time.
- Women are nothing but trouble.
- What are you doing?
- Just go with it.
- But she's beautiful.
- You can buy women
which will be less of a headache
than those two up there.
Are you insane?
Just play along.
- Sorry, boys.
- (SCOFFS)
We have lost him again.
So what would we do with you?
(COINS CLINK)
ALINA: We can pay
for safe passage.
And Esme is a great cook.
- I am?
- Yes, you are.
Fine. But you'll do as I say.
- Understood?
- Yeah.
- Until the next village.
- (THUNDER RUMBLING)
(GROWLS)
GIRL: What's happening to us?
Where are we?
I'm so scared.
Welcome.
You must be tired
after your journey.
Let us go.
Do not worry. You'll
not be harmed.
I am Renfield.
Chancellor of this kingdom.
Come. I will see that
your needs are tended to.
GIRL #2: Who's this? Who's this?
What does he want?
(SNIFFS)
Come.
I will see that your
needs are tended to.
WOMAN: (SPEAKING NATIVE LANGUAGE)
All the comforts of our
castle are open to you.
Through here is the great hall.
Enjoy.
(WOMAN SPEAKS NATIVE LANGUAGE)
(GIGGLES)
RENFIELD: All sorts of pleasures
and adventures await you.
(SPEAKING NATIVE LANGUAGE)
This is the main dining room.
You are our guests.
We want you to enjoy
your time with us.
- It's beautiful.
- All of this is for you.
Whatever you want or
desire, it's here.
We want to make you feel
at home and welcome.
Everything has been done for
your pleasure and enjoyment.
The music...
company...
comfort...
all is for you.
We hope that you will
learn to love us,
embrace your new life with us.
I will leave you now.
The master will see
you again tomorrow.
Sit, eat.
Enjoy.
This is your new home.
(CHATTER)
The newcomers have settled in.
I don't like strangers.
There is word of slayers
arriving from as far
away as Kvenland,
the frozen wastes of the north.
With so many enemies
aligned against us,
we must increase our numbers.
Just think...
with the Lightbringer
in your possession,
we will no longer have to worry
about these things again.
We'll find it.
And then you can have as
many followers as you wish.
Just think, sire...
once the Lightbringer
is in your possession,
no one need die again.
Except those who defy me.
(GROWLS)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(ANIMAL HOWLING)
(CHATTER)
I say it's gold.
- No, it's too light to be gold.
- Oh, what do you know?
LUCIEN: Well, whatever it is, they've
spared no expense on the lock.
This is a bad idea, Alina.
What other choice did we have?
Gather 'round, boys.
Moment of truth.
- Come on.
- MAN: All right, open it up!
Come on, a little enthusiasm.
(CHEERING)
Open it already.
- It's just a walking stick.
- MAN: (LAUGHS)
All that effort for
a piece of wood.
We cannot lose the
Lightbringer.
Wait, what did you say?
The Lightbringer.
It alone has the
power to defeat
Dracula and the
creatures of the night.
(MEN LAUGHING)
Wait, so you're
saying you think
this is some kind of
magic walking stick?
It's what Cain used to slay Abel.
It was the very first weapon.
Whoo! You don't say.
The blood of innocents
transformed it into a
tool of God's vengeance.
- Did you bang your head?
- I think so.
The trail ends here.
Spread out.
In the right person's hands,
it has the power to
wipe out entire armies.
You're putting a lot of
faith into a walking stick,
aren't you, sweetheart?
(MEN OOH)
Oh, what a strong
one here, boys.
Trade you for a kiss.
(MEN CHEERING)
What is it about
this walking stick?
It's an ancient holy relic.
It's taken us years to find it.
There were others with us who
gave their lives for it.
I'm sorry.
We may not be knights,
but we respect that.
There might not be a market
for religious artifacts.
Should we give it back to them?
- A thief with a conscience?
- Maybe even a heart.
MAN: The Lightbringer
should not be passed around
like a flagon of cheap ale.
I told you he'd come
for the Lightbringer.
What is happening here?
What are you two doing with
such companions as these?
What is this flirtation?
Open your eyes. Look.
Is this the people to share
your sacred secrets with?
- She was the one that told...
- No, you!
No, no.
I am disappointed
with both of you.
What would your
father have said now?
And he trusted me
with your care.
Excuse me.
Who are you, old man?
I am Leonardo Van Helsing.
And who are you?
- I am Lucien Merel.
- A great adventurer.
World's finest poet.
Lover.
Thief.
- Very amusing.
- Very.
My friend, you have something
that belongs to me.
Do I?
(ANIMAL SCREECHING)
MAN: What's going on?
(HORSES NEIGHING)
The scourge.
What did you do, old man?
You brought them here.
You fool!
They've come for
the Lightbringer.
MAN: Pack your weapons.
Wrath.
I should have known.
Who here carries
the Lightbringer?
He does.
I stand before you
in the name of God.
Prepare to send you back
from whence you came, demon!
Kill them all.
(GROWLING, YELLING)
Something's wrong.
Protect the Lightbringer.
You're coming with me.
Let go of me!
Lucien!
Alina!
No!
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(GRUNTS)
Let go of me!
My lord.
Forgive me.
Wrath, I'm disappointed.
You were but a young boy, yet you
stood bravely against my enemies.
- I will remain loyal to you.
- (SCREAMS)
Now I have given you strength to
match your courage and yet you fail.
How is this possible?
Sire, they used
the Lightbringer.
But that's impossible.
The...
(SNIFFS)
You.
My God.
Dracula.
You do exist.
Elizabeth.
My friends will come for
you and kill you all.
What is your name?
When my lord asks a question,
you will answer him.
Calm your temper, my knight.
No reason to
frighten our guest.
Alina. My name is Alina.
Ah.
A Greek name, I do believe.
If I'm not mistaken,
it means light.
It also means fire.
You are hurt.
Go ahead, kill me.
Oh, on the contrary.
No one shall touch you.
Renfield,
show our guest to
the west wing.
- See to her injury.
- The west wing, my lord?
The royal suite...
for Alina of the light.
As you wish, my lord.
My lord.
(DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
Do not give up hope.
I feel that Alina
may still be alive.
Look on the ground behind you.
I believe
that this sign is telling us
that your sister
is not only alive,
but somehow thriving.
We'll save her.
LEONARDO: Yes.
We will leave now.
Even though the scourge
of Dracula's army
cannot rise in the day,
we will travel
throughout the night
and we will save her.
- You're not coming?
- No.
- This is where we say goodbye.
- Even after all you've seen?
The scourge, the Lightbringer,
you want to leave?
I don't even know what the Lightbringer
is or why it responded to me.
The question is not
why it chose you,
but who you really are.
Not interested.
Have you not seen the giant
pile of bodies here?
Next time will be different.
There won't be a "next time."
Well, what about your friends?
Don't you want to avenge them?
And what good would that do?
They're dead and they're
not coming back.
Or have you got a little magic
walking stick for that, too?
What about Alina?
What about her?
Come, Esme. Let us go.
You can't force someone
to do the right thing.
And you don't want to be alone
when the undead return.
Hey, wait up.
(SIZZLES)
My lord,
the Lady Alina is resting.
What do you think, Renfield?
There is a remarkable
resemblance.
But is it more?
My lord, be wary
of coincidence.
The girl may bear her
face, but never her soul.
Is it possible
for us to return
to this Earth?
Born again in another time?
Be careful
where the parts of your
mind wander, my lord.
I fear they will only
lead to disappointment.
I would welcome disappointment.
The elders said we should
not dwell on the past.
The elders are gone,
along with their
outdated beliefs.
Should not some of their
beliefs be reconsidered?
No.
We have our own ways now.
I see you are still young
at heart, my master.
I'm not unsettled. I
need her, Renfield.
Are not the women of
the castle enough to
sate your appetite?
A thousand of them could never
fill the void she left behind.
You should rest.
How could I possibly
think about sleep now?
(SIZZLES)
Power of our armies
lies in your power
of regeneration.
Without it, it would grow weak.
See to it that the
boards are replaced.
You know my heart cannot
leave this place.
Renfield...
watch over her for me.
Of course, sire.
Esme!
(GROANS)
(CROWS CAWING)
RENFIELD: Who knows?
The master is beguiled,
grows weak under her spell.
He'll surely make a mistake.
I feel your pain, my knights.
My lady.
You should be in bed.
And for their failure to
protect his beloved queen,
he imprisoned them
for all eternity.
RENFIELD: You know of the four knights?
Yes, but I never believed
them to be true.
Only stories mothers told their little
girls before they went to sleep at night.
And what story did
your mother tell you?
Once there was a
great, handsome prince
who fought gallantly
for Transylvania.
He defended us
against our enemies
until one day
he turned to the dark side.
He lost his faith.
He put his own selfish
desires ahead of God's.
He was let down by his knights
who were supposed to
protect his one true love.
His princess.
Elizabeth.
He was a great knight.
This country owes him a great debt
for his sacrifice and courage.
Yes, he...
loved his princess
with all his soul.
What do you know of love?
God is love.
Everything else is a pale
shadow in comparison.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, perhaps that explains
why my master prefers
the shadows.
Here...
God has no power.
How can you serve such a demon?
There is much you do not
understand about loyalty.
I was born into the
Keepers of the Light.
The first words we learn are
oaths of honor and loyalty.
My loyalty is to the land.
And as long as my master
rules over it, to him.
Your master is a monster
that should be destroyed.
There is no
earthly power
that can defeat my lord.
What about the Lightbringer?
(CROWS CAWING)
LEONARDO: Lucien,
what do you know of your past?
LUCIEN: My parents died
when I was very young
and the only other family I've
known was killed last night.
LEONARDO: What if I told you
you were from the
bloodline of Cain?
Who?
From the Bible and the Book
of Genesis. Cain and Abel.
I don't go to church much.
After Cain killed his brother,
God condemned him
and his offspring
to a life of crime as
murderous cutthroats...
and thieves.
Isn't half of humanity
related to Cain?
LEONARDO: On the contrary, Adam
and Eve had many children.
Cain was the firstborn,
then Abel, then Seth.
Okay, spare me the
whole family tree.
You, my boy,
are a very rare breed.
Tell me something I don't know.
There they are.
The Carpathian Mountains.
Bows and arrow don't
even faze him.
You're wasting your time.
At least we're doing something.
Yeah, something that's
gonna get you both killed.
Alas, Lucien is right.
Our weapons are a
feeble defense at best.
Told ya.
LEONARDO: The Lightbringer...
the Lightbringer
must work for us.
We must find a way.
Let me see.
Why doesn't it
work for you two?
Oh, well, I guess the
Lightbringer only responds
to the bloodline of
it's former master.
All right.
Let me try.
Well, so much for your theory.
I don't understand. It
worked for him before.
Something must have changed.
He must be of the
blood of Cain.
The blood of Cain.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?!
Ah!
Now...
you must believe.
It's fitting that Cain killed
his brother with a scythe.
He was a farmer, you know.
Keep your feet under you.
- Yeah, I'm trying. I'm trying.
- Always balance, balance, balance.
Never cross your legs.
Just balance. Dance, you see?
Keep your movement fluid.
You'll get it. You'll see.
Tell me, old man, how do
you think this thing's
even going to beat
Dracula's army?
Because Dracula is a
descendant of Abel.
If God cursed Cain
and his offspring,
what would he have bestowed
on the sons of Abel?
The favored ones.
Come, come, come!
I don't know, I'm not
good at riddles.
A life of nobility
and privilege.
And what was Dracula before
he embraced the powers of evil?
A prince?
A prince.
The Lightbringer,
the original weapon
that killed Abel,
is the only thing that
can kill Dracula.
So what happens if Dracula
gets a hold of this thing?
Dracula is from the
blood of Abel.
The Lightbringer
does the opposite.
It brings the dead
to life.
(ROARING, FLUTTERING)
(WOMEN GIGGLING)
Where are you going?
I'm leaving.
And you should, too.
But why?
This is my home.
I like it here.
The person who owns this
castle is a very evil man.
If you can even call him a man.
He's nice to us.
I'll show you.
(MUSIC PLAYING, LAUGHING)
(HISSES)
(VOICES OVERLAPPING)
WOMAN: Lie down.
Alina...
How dare you touch her
when I had forbidden it.
Don't worry. No harm
will come to you.
I told you to protect her.
I had no idea she'd left
her room, Your Majesty.
Is she all right?
Ah!
Life is learning
everyone has challenges.
Well, that's easy to say when you're
not carrying the curse of Cain.
Here we are.
Welcome to Bistritz.
The crossroads for every
demon slayer on this edge
of the Carpathian Mountains.
Could use a drink.
Slayers do not consume alcohol.
ESME: It dulls the mind
and slows the senses.
Well, good job I'm
not a slayer, then.
None of that.
Here.
Why is your head down?
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
The past is not nothing.
Let me console you.
Only when you know
who you truly are
can you use it for good.
Don't feel sorry for yourself.
I'm not feeling anything.
I don't know what
he's talking about.
Seat's taken.
Have respect.
This is family.
This is kindred.
To whom do I have
the honor to speak?
My name is Andros.
Son of Cormac the Wolf Slayer.
I'm a demon hunter.
From where have you come,
Andros? You've come a long way?
Beyond the frozen seas,
far to the north.
You sit with us. These
are my good friends.
Barkeep, bring us as much
food as this table will hold.
We may not drink, but that doesn't
mean we can't eat like horses.
(LAUGHING)
So tell me,
what brings you to Bistritz?
Tales of a demon called Dracula
and of a slayer called Van
Helsing who seeks to hunt him.
I am Van Helsing.
In my land, these demons
are called Gruntiak.
My sister was taken
by these creatures.
Now, I've spent many years
traveling, avenging
my family...
Long time to hold a grudge.
What we are fighting here
is no ordinary demon...
but a vampire.
Lord Dracula
is as strong as 100 men
and as cunning
as he is strong.
He lures his followers
with promises
of eternal life
and beauty.
To drink from his blood,
to become one of them.
But you become
a slave to the curse.
The blood is the life.
Well, we should be safe if
we don't drink his blood.
Unless you are bitten.
In that case, you
have three choices;
You can pray for a quick death,
you can drink
from him and live
forever,
or you can turn
into the accursed.
Nosferatu.
From necurat,
meaning unclean
and a sufferite.
A suffering to be bitten
and not drink from
Dracula's blood
is a suffering without end.
(SCREAMS)
So, my warrior friend,
now that I have told you,
is this danger a price
you are willing to pay?
I do not fear it.
Yeah, pay attention,
young ones.
Throughout history,
whenever barbaric
poisons have taken hold
and evil seems poised
to flood the Earth,
heroes have always risen up,
willing even to
sacrifice themselves
that future generations
have the opportunity
to seek peace.
These heroes are
from God himself.
I am always humbled
to be in their presence
and I have striven always
to be one of them.
I would drink to that.
If you let me.
I am happy to be
with each of you.
We haven't been introduced.
I'm Esme,
slayer in training.
And the rude one
here is Lucien.
I wouldn't be in such a mood if
you just let me have some wine.
Wine's no good. It dulls the
mind and slows the senses.
Spoken like a true slayer.
(LAUGHS)
It's a conspiracy.
It is. It's a conspiracy.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Do not fear me.
I saw what you did
to those girls.
I perform acts of mercy,
yet you would call for my head.
You have a distorted
notion of mercy, sir.
I give eternal life so
those may live in peace
and happiness.
Only the Lord God can
give eternal life.
I should kill you now
for your blasphemy.
You would not be
the first to try,
but I think you would find I'm
a very difficult man to kill.
You're no man.
You're a demon.
A man I was once.
A man I may yet again
hope to become.
ALINA: She was very beautiful.
Yes, she was.
I'm sorry for your loss.
DRACULA: It was given
to the Queen of Sheba
by King Solomon himself.
A token of his eternal
love and devotion.
- Why don't you try it on?
- I couldn't.
But you are my guest, I insist.
It looks better on
you than on display.
Am I a prisoner here?
Of course not.
May I leave?
Not just yet.
Then I'd like to go
back to my room.
LEONARDO: We leave for Bukovina.
There have been reports of
activity near the Borgo Pass.
We start there.
Wait, you don't even know
where Dracula's castle is?
No one does.
It is rumored
to be on the crest of the
Carpathian Mountains
near to the Borgo Pass.
RENFIELD: I'm told that slayers are
gathering in growing numbers in Bistritz.
Something amiss, my lord?
Heavy loneliness
eats at my heart.
Let me guess, Miss Alina.
She will never see me as
anything but a monster.
I should turn her.
Make her one of us.
I don't know if
that's wise, sire.
If she is indeed
your true love,
give her time to remember.
If she loved you once,
she'll love you again.
My lord.
Never have I regretted
what I have become...
until now.
(SCREAMING)
They are in Bistritz. It's not like
them to attack an entire village.
They're becoming
more aggressive.
Or desperate.
Go, we still have
to protect them.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(SCREAMING)
Wrath!
A noble hero.
Make that two.
Where is my sister?
She's with the master.
Remember me?
Why, if it isn't the thief.
I've learned something
new about myself.
Kill them all.
(GROANS)
You've done it.
You've done it!
Dear Lucien, you've done it.
(PANTING)
Wrath.
Not bad for
a half-trained boy.
When they return for
the Lightbringer,
they will be in full force.
Esme, where are you going?
To get my sister.
I'm coming with you.
The young ones have taken over.
Shall we?
I may have one more
battle left in me.
My champion.
Greatest of all my warriors.
WRATH: The boy...
he wields the Lightbringer.
He is a descendant of Cain.
We've underestimated him.
I will give you what you
need to defend him.
Go.
Bring the Lightbringer to me.
(SCREAMS)
(GASPS)
I think I remember.
Do not weep for the
past, dear Alina.
Too many tears have
already been shed. Come.
Let me show you something.
'Tis here I seek my
solace in stars.
According to Plato, the universe is
one soul divided into equal parts,
each one assigned to a star.
And those who live a
full and virtuous life
return to their native star
while others return to Earth,
again and again, until they
find their life's true purpose.
All these years,
I've searched the skies,
hoping to find the light
of my one true love.
I don't understand.
Search your heart...
and find me.
(HORSE NEIGHS)
I thought he was dead.
Dracula has powers
of which we can only dream.
ANDROS: He's come
through the Borgo Pass.
We must be very close now.
I am sure.
Do we even know what
we're looking for?
Castle would have to be
in a defensible position.
On a mountain.
Against a cliff.
- I just hope we're not too late.
- Have faith.
Look who's talking
about faith now.
(LAUGHS)
Dear Lucien.
There's a compass.
But it's not heading north.
ESME: Maybe it's not supposed to.
Paprika hen... fowl.
Prepared in the traditional
Hungarian fashion.
Just the way you like it. I...
I'm sure you will like it.
Are you not having any?
Alas, my palate
has changed over the years.
(SCOFFS)
Of course.
I'd forgotten.
Oh.
(CHUCKLES)
Why do you want the
Lightbringer so badly?
What do you need with
yet another weapon?
Oh, it's not just a weapon.
With the Lightbringer, I
can assure that no one
ever loses the ones they love.
You'd make yourself
equal to God?
Oh, not at all. No, God has
the power to create life.
I'll just prevent him
from taking it away.
RENFIELD: Ahem.
Apologies for the
intrusion, sire.
Wrath sends word
that the thief and his
comrades are heading this way.
Lucien.
You know this man?
Um...
he'll be with my sister.
They'll be looking for me.
Many have tried to
find this place.
All have failed.
We are hidden from
the eyes of mortals.
Do you have feelings
for this man?
(SCOFFS)
I...
seem to have lost my appetite.
If you'll excuse me.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
My lord is troubled.
Blood will make
you feel better.
Drink from me.
I cannot.
Leave me.
(CROWS CAWING)
(CREATURES SCREECHING)
We're close.
Then let's hurry.
ESME: I don't see anything.
It should be here.
Wait... I see something.
There.
After a lifetime...
finally.
Now we need to
find a way inside.
Only two choices;
Up or under.
(LAUGHS)
And how would you know?
When you've robbed as
many castles as I have,
you'd know it's only
towers and dungeons.
Royals have no imagination.
So who goes up
and who goes under?
- (GROANS)
- The smell of death.
(GRUNTS)
This is disgusting.
ANDROS: Maybe the smell will
keep the vampires away.
Now we must divide.
Esme, you stay with Andros.
Godspeed, my friend.
Until we meet again.
Come on. Let's find Alina.
(GROWLS)
Wrath.
Just you and me.
I thought I'd never
see you again.
My luck. Come on, let's go.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Leonardo Van Helsing.
Stand for the master.
You've waited for this
moment for so many years.
And here you are. Welcome.
I have come with
no other intent
but to end your
poisonous ways forever.
I believe you.
And yet I'm impressed with you.
Your courage.
Your fortitude.
Your persistence.
Your knowledge
about me.
And in many ways, perhaps you know
me better than I know myself.
If I were to make
you one of mine...
what conversations you
and I could have.
Have you turned the girl?
No.
Not yet.
What can I offer you
to set her free?
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Lord Dracula,
have you ever considered
that this God you
turned against
truly does exist
and if you take this girl,
you will never be able
to forgive yourself?
You're suggesting that my soul
is not completely lost.
No one, in my thought,
is completely lost.
I see it, they have the power
to seek redemption
and God's mercy.
Renfield.
Master Van Helsing,
we'll speak again.
We will let him live.
For now.
I must rest.
Could it be any
darker down here?
The dead don't need any light.
Where are your companions?
The one who wields
the Lightbringer.
He is coming.
Good.
That's what we were hoping.
(SCREAMING)
Leonardo.
Leonardo!
Leonardo, get up.
Get up!
ANDROS: Stand back!
WOMAN: Andros.
Andros.
Demetria?
My brother.
You've come for me.
I thought you were dead.
Andros, that's not your sister.
I've missed you.
Come to me.
To see you again, here,
it's like a dream.
Andros!
Yes, my brother, a dream.
From which is there
no wakening.
(GROWLS)
- (SCREAMS)
- ANDROS: Demetria, no!
Hurry. Over here.
Andros, help!
Get away from her.
Come on, let's go.
Esme.
Over there. Watch out.
- Leonardo.
- Alina!
- Esme!
- I knew we'd find you.
I never gave up hope.
- LUCIEN: Protect the girls!
- He's not moving.
- Leonardo.
- No.
We're completely surrounded.
- I'm not leaving you, old man.
- Go, go away!
- No.
- I've been bitten.
It's only a matter of time
before the transformation
is complete.
- No.
- Then we'll all go together.
Esme, get me my crossbow
and twine.
Twine.
I love you all.
And your father
would be proud of you.
And whatever blessings
I have left to give...
I give them...
to you.
No.
(SCREAMING, HISSING)
Leonardo, no!
ANDROS: We're running
out of daylight.
Let's go, let's go.
Come on, come on.
- Come on. Let's go.
- ANDROS: Go!
- (SCREAMING)
- Now, now, go! Take her!
Come on!
Don't stop! Go!
Catch.
Out the window, both of you!
(YELLS)
(SCREAMS)
LUCIEN: The sun is setting.
ANDROS: Into the woods.
(GROWLS, SCREAMING)
(GROWLS)
Sire.
Do not confuse your
friends for your enemies.
I have but one enemy now.
We have the location and the
layout of the stronghold.
- Now's the time to attack.
- And this time,
the element of surprise
will be on our side.
- (CHEERING)
- ALINA: None of you should go.
You don't understand
him like I do.
He's a beast only because
he's been treated like one.
You've gone soft because
you're under his spell.
No.
I kept this for you.
Hold on to it for me.
(GROWLS)
(GROWLING)
(ROARING)
- To the throne, men!
- (CHEERING)
To the throne, men!
You invade my home...
How dare you?!
(ROARING)
Destroy the intruders.
Dracula!
ALINA: Stop! Stop fighting!
You took away the only
thing I have ever loved.
You're incapable of love.
All you know is death.
Dracula!
Let her go!
She is not to be harmed!
Sweet blood of Cain.
We're the 'cause
of all this death.
I would tear the
world apart for you.
(YELLS)
Renfield.
Why?
Because you gave her
dominion over your heart
and this land.
A mere concubine.
You defy the elders
with your willfulness
and decadence.
Your love is a disease
that had to be extinguished.
I will bring this country
back to the glory
- it once knew.
- No!
I've already killed you
once, my princess.
(ELIZABETH SCREAMS)
Esme, catch!
(GASPS, GROANING)
Perhaps it's better this way.
No one should live forever.
Alina.
Stay back!
No.
It's over.
Alina...
take me back to the chamber.
You can heal yourself.
I know you can.
Let me spend these
last moments with you.
It's better than
a century alone.
I'll be waiting for you.
NARRATOR: Burdened with the
curse of a broken heart,
Lucien vanished
into the wilderness
just as his forefather
had so many eons ago.
No one knows where he went
or if another descendant
of Cain will appear
when the time is right.
And so ends the untold tale
of the first crusade
of Dracula.
Many slayers fought
to find him,
including descendants
of the great Leonardo
Van Helsing.
The castle destroyed,
all that is left in ruins,
but Dracula still lives.
I know this to be true,
as I wait to reunite
with my one true love.
Heroes die,
death is eternal...
but real love is forever.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
http://subscene.com/u/659433
Improved by: @Ivandrofly