Still !
Look, Zhomart!
They look like Dsungars.
Follow me up there!
There are two!
Fast, Sartai! Quick! Get out of here!
Zhomart! Stand up!
One less.
That was a child.
Why did you do that?
Now do not get upset so on.
You know how it is.
Today was just a child,
and tomorrow it's a soldier.
Enough. Let's go.
Drive them together!
Let no escape!
Father!
At least let the children and the old people go!
Now this is our country, Kazakh!
You have lost nothing here!
Save yourselves if you can!
Let your cattle and your possessions
back and get out of here!
Father! Father!
Father!
Hey! Dsungars you dirty bastard!
Clarify the  we as men,
if you dare!
Father!
Father! Father!
You can not die!
Father, no!
- Father!
- Sartai!
My son. Running, fast!
Let him go!
Sartai, run away! Sartai, fast!
Aibek!
Korlan, take Aibek!
Sartai!
Mother! Mother! Please wake up!
Sartai, come on!
Korlan! Sartai!
Hurry up, hurry!
Run fast in the fields!
We can only flee.
Aibek, look! There are Sartai
and the others. - Hooray!
- Sartai, you're back!
- Korlan!
Well, you, how are you?
Kamshat, Aibek, are you all right?
- Taimas is difficult that?
- Have you been taking care of our home?
- I'm very hungry!
- Taimas, son.
Hello, Mother.
Nice to be here again.
Look at the times of the many meat!
Asalam aleikum!
ALEIKUM salam!
How are you?
Well, my boy. Tell!
Was your hunt successful?
I have killed a deer.
You're a good hunter.
- Has no one seen you?
- No.
We were careful and have kept their eyes open.
But if we had encountered enemies, my arrows had done it.
That is right!
- Yes, hit!
- A very nice results.
Well done!
Very good, Taimas!
Screaming swung the mighty Karaman...
... His sword and struck full force with
Alpamys Shield.
Alpamys
spectacular block the blow and hit Karaman's head.
He split him like a nut.
Karaman's warriors made returns and fled.
Since then freezes in fear Alpamys' name
his enemies.
He had the will to defeat it,
and courage helped him.
If Alpamys today would still be alive,
... then the Dsungars would never trust
to attack us.
He is still a hero among the Kazakhs
,
... the steadfast fight against Dsungars today.
A shame that they did not join forces and fight together
.
Like I said!
Nowhere to see a Dsungar.
This is our beautiful desert.
Enough with the game of hide
in our home!
Listen to what it .
Talk almost like a man
who  catches me, has won!
So you've let you instigate of Taimas
, am I right?
Do you think I do not know that you were in the
steppe? My only makes us trouble.
Do you want that?
Your carelessness can threaten us.
Uncle? Do not treat us like children.
We are already grown up.
Korlan is a real woman and I'm not a fool.
So do not blame Taimas.
All right, calm down.
Listen to this boy only!
You've become quite large.
If so, I'll take you
well with New Year celebrations.
Now, children, looks like a village!
I hope you have not forgotten her.
I want a fair fight.
And always remember what you have learned.
Yes, that makes it good!
And nice keep it up!
Sanzhar is our winner!
Stay close.
I go to the eldest.
Do not worry about us.
Rakhimzhan, look
Is there Nazar?
And who is now wrestling with each other?
're Next fighter?
Aset, and what is your name?
Be so good,
... go to our guests and welcome them,
it's also a girl there.
- Asalam aleikum.
- ALEIKUM salam.
- Happy new year.
- Same to you.
- I welcome you.
- That's nice of you.
Women sit with us and eat something with us.
Go ahead, we do not run away.
Come! A fight circle!
I greet you!
The prize to the winner of the duel will be honoring...
... Presented by Kassym the son
Rakhimzhans, the Generous!
A special recognition for the winner!
This kaftan is
which adorn the shoulders to win the fight.
A fine piece!
Whoever challenges the master? Who wants to?
Try your luck!
You will beat him!
Oh, there's a brave opponents.
It is decided.
You, take his things from him.
Take your top off.
These are my boys.
He will never beat him.
I hope you know the rules.
Get ready.
The rest you can Start.
Our fighters will defeat him!
And go!
From ! The fight is over!
Let's go!
I do not know your name, but
of the victory is yours! Congratulations!
Well done!
This boy is really quite strong, fights very well.
Yes, he has talent.
Make yourself at home.
From where do you come from?
I do not know you.
We come from a distant village
. This is Sartai and I'm Taimas.
We are Kazakhs like you.
Hey. Whose daughter is this?
This? This is Kassyms sister.
Kassym?
I challenge one of your friends.
And if I win,
you put me in front of your sister.
- Dream on!
- Kassym! Ayur is there.
- Zere, go to the last yurt!
- Yes, immediately.
Welcome , Ayur, the brave!
Nice that you are here!
Take them off the horses and binds to it!
Continuously since yesterday we sit in the saddle.
I hope the celebrations went well.
Let's go.
Do not sit around,
makes the food ready.
Kassym, come with me.
Have you not heard? Stands up.
Let's go.
Here. This can keep her.
It is not only outrageous, but also arrogant
!
Enough is enough!
Why are you arguing?
I know a man who
of hiding from the Dsungars,
... but I know
... that his heart is free.
But you let enslave you,
although you are free. You mock us.
We should go back to our guests.
Hey, the food is ready?
Go and bring it forth.
Uncle? I do not get it.
Why does Rakhimzhan to
as they are good friends?
Who knows?
Maybe he pursues his own goals.
The village and protect his family.
If it were me,
I would tear the two apart.
Especially these Ayur.
He ​​provides for our girls.
You're right, I can testify to that.
Recently, he has been asking about
Rakhimzhans daughter.
I just patience.
One day there will be justice.
Our time will come.
And I'll be the first to congratulate you of
.
Korlan...
Where did you get that?
Sartai , we can not
longer hide from her.
Korlan?
Last night we killed two
Dsungars in the steppe.
Lot, Sartai, kill him.
Please! Have mercy! I beg of you!
I beg of you!
- White Nazar it?
- No.
- How much do we have to hide?
- Korlan?
It's time for revenge.
I am to you.
I will fight with you.
I swear that I will fight to the death in
.
Whatever happens, I will do everything
to destroy the Dsungars!
- I swear!
I swear.
Today we will ride together in the steppe.
It is almost done.
Go and see what's going on.
Did not you  before, wake us up,
when the food is ready?
In the time you had to cook a soft
stone.
What happened?
It's all good, Korlan. Let's go.
Uncle Sabit! Grandmother!
Come quickly here!
Who is that?
Do not come any closer!
Sabitzhan who the, what do they want?
One step closer and I'll kill you!
Leave us alone!
Ye shall disappear!
We do nothing to you.
What happened? Where are you from?
I'll tell you.
The Dsungars have people killed and our cattle.
We got away just yet.
We are already on their feet for
days.
Move strangers have shared with us their food,
... But it hardly gave himself for it
then accompanied us.
Go with us. The
is safer for you than be alone.
We need to start to worry
for ourselves.
What is your name?
Sabit.
Good. We accompany you.
Sultan Abul Khair has arrived.
Asalam aleikum.
Asalam aleikum!
ALEIKUM salam!
Come in, Sultan. After you.
Sure you know what is going on in the steppe
straight forward, is not it?
The Dsungars have shifted their forays into our country.
You gather thousands of soldiers.
Why we must fight them now,
... as long as their horses still from the winter are weak.
The people are ready to fight for a long time
.
All we have to do is to pull the
khans and sultans on our side.
You speak of what the
bitter truth for all of us, unfortunately.
Let the khans and sultans
inform them.
Yes.
Invents, I Iüge. It's true!
Who is that? There's a girl.
Do not twist your head.
I do not smell anything good.
Nonsense! We grab us!
Then just pass on to the horses.
- What are you doing?
- Fast, it escapes!
Come back, it's a trap!
Damn!
Fast, we drive
the horses together!
Taimas! We ride through the canyon,
to cover our tracks!
- This is too big a detour.
- Does not matter!
Clear! There are only children.
Take your bows down
do not be afraid.
Where are you from?
And where do you want?
We are warriors who want to take revenge on the
Dsungars.
These horses we have stolen from them in order to trade against
guns.
This country needs you.
What is your name? Who was your father?
My father was a warrior.
He ​​died in battle.
Our brothers and fathers were all killed by Dsungars
.
I'm Sartai. And your name is?
My name Borybai and this
here are my warriors.
We move west.
Soldiers gather there, to put
Dsungars to defend against.
We could use you.
No, we
fight on another front.
We will even take care of them.
Listen, what do you say
... if we half the
horses for a few weapons...
... And swap clothes?
And then join you?
We can not do that.
We run your own war.
Well, you shall get,
what you need.
I'll talk to him.
So?
I hear.
Were these horses just so around in the desert?
Or are they perhaps come naturally to you?
Carelessness could cost you your life.
Have you ever thought about it?
It is not the first time
... that we escape the Dsungars are
. As you can see, we are still alive.
Support us but rather, blame and
not because we dare something.
good. We do not argue.
Then the horses in the barn houses.
Then we'll see.
I knew he would have to talk to
.
I do not understand how can Rakhimzhan
fraternize with the Dsungars.
Rakhimzhan Who is this?
A man who is willing to give
to his enemies.
Or, Sartai? That he is!
A cowardly dog.
Yes, but he has a pretty daughter.
What interests me is the daughter of a traitor?
Let's drink to her village,
and what to ask girls!
Sounds good.
We ride directly toward tomorrow.
This is difficult
there was controversy. You know that
So what? We go to them and smooth things
.
Tell them that you're sorry...
... And then we can finally take care of the important things to
.
Asalam aleikum!
ALEIKUM salam, sit down.
Take something to eat.
Come, go over there.
Ayan? Go and bring them something
mare's milk.
Good to see you again.
So I did not expect.
I hope that I have not offended you
.
Do not worry, I overreacted.
Please forgive me, I was rude.
Yes. If I may ask...
Where are you from? What are you doing here?
We move around and want to argue against the
Dsungars.
We are from the village of honorable Nazar.
We have vowed to fight the enemy together
.
- Amantay?
- Yes?
- How about if what you sing to us?
- Sure, give me my dombra.
I already walk around on this earth as long as
.
I can not even count that I have trodden the paths.
I have met warriors,
like lions.
I've seen
who protects her clan men.
And recently I've seen a cock
... the strutting among his whole
hens.
But then I saw that only
some feathers from him were left
... rushing down as a hawk from the sky and grabbed him
himself.
I would give you an answer,
... if I would have mastered the art of playing
.
What a strange song is that?
We sing about the Dsungars  bones,
we scatter in the desert!
We welcome our enemies are not welcome.
Unlike the people, the
fraternize with their enemies.
I see.
Your
fed us and then spits it into our faces.
My dear
should avoid pushing your luck.
No one will give you protection here.
How about when you
the Dsungars are not complacent,
... but it makes you complacent?
What the hell are you going to tell me about?
That's it. You'll
rude again. The second time
If you were not my guests would,
I personally continue chasing you out of here.
- Hey, show us your saber!
- No, disappears!
- Please!
- Pulls leash!
Vulgarity!
Hey, wait. Wait a minute!
Who are you?
My name is lliyas.
Appreciate your Rakhimzhan incorrectly,
he is very good-natured.
It helps orphans and widows.
Mich. He has also recorded with him.
You must not condemn him,
because he is trying to protect us.
He does it for our own good.
Have you forgotten that you're
Kazakh?
Or maybe you want to be a slave to the
Dsungars?
What are you talking about for a nonsense?
"Slave," I'll show you!
If you're brave, fight!
Why are you doing nothing?
I'm not from here.
I teach the children.
But I am always willing to provide me
the enemy.
Then opt .
Come with us, or stay here.
I'm going to get my books.
Without them I'm not coming.
Agreed.
How do we find a way out of this impasse?
Either we are slaves for the rest of our lives
... or we begin to
to fight for our country!
- Yes, exactly!
- Very true!
Our only chance is a trading
with Galdan, or we're dead
Absolutely not. That would not be good.
No, that's not good!
Otherwise we will always draw the short straw
! We need to negotiate!
We are not many, and our country is broke.
Dsungars with the parts we have, and there is peace!
No, this is our country!
I share nothing with these monsters!
Calm down!
We do not want
killer in our country!
Mortal enemies can never be friends! The hate for it to sit deep.
Bugun!
If we sell them our country today,
... then it could be
our women and children tomorrow.
No compromises!
- Exactly!
- Right!
And who of you is willing to fight and die
?
Tell it to me! Who? Come on!
Silk but reasonable!
You will not regret it, if you negotiated with the
Dsungars!
You're the one who spotted our flag!
Not Dsungars.
We must finally unite!
He's right! Enough is enough!
- Do not compromise!
- Exactly!
It brings us nothing,
... to accuse each other.
- This is also true.
- Yeah, right.
Our goal should be to
all to pull together.
Only way we can regain our freedom
.
We need to unite.
- Yes!
- Right!
Do we's finally!
My friend,
... exactly this attitude I expected from you.
I say unto you, my brethren,
is... from this day on the honorable...
... Abul Khair Mukhamed
lead the Kazakh army!
- He is our commander!
- Yes!
Come to bed!
- Bugunbai to be his right hand.
- Yes!
Then your blessings.
Yes!
- Amen!
- So be it!
Sagittarius, Allah, our people and bring us
by your kindness to victory.
- Amen.
It is  to take the time to fight for our freedom
!
In the battle!
Do you remember,
... that was spoken in Rakhimzhan about the
Akzhar Fortress?
The Dsungars use it as their base
. There are no residential buildings.
What do you think, if we provide a
bit of an uproar there?
Then we should prepare.
And well equipped. We are only five.
No, four and a girl. Even if we do not take the mounting
... we'll scare them a
terror.
We should go to the Shagal Bazaar.
There we can...
Collect information.
We are planning on.
Good idea, so let's do it.
Let us leave today We should not waste time.
- Korlan, lliyas?
- Yes?
Wait here for us.
Take care of the weapons!
You look at that.
This is a lion.
Hey! Disappears there!
Power that you
come off here! Go on, get out of here!
Way! Have you not heard?
You stand in your way! Make way!
We share us best.
Keep your eyes open and you realize what you hear.
I hereby declare,
... that in the case of
Kazakhs three brothers...
... The verdict of the judge is as follows:
For horse theft...
... And the murder of a Dsungar...
... The eldest of them is punished with death. The other two are sold
as slaves and the money...
... Benefit of the
Dsungars murdered family.
! Kazakhs!
Kazakhs, arise!
This is our country!
Only we have the right!
Fight the Dsungars
until their last man!
You bastards!
And makes the two others your slaves.
We do not want to continue to care for us.
We have not made us guilty before God
! Take them away!
Here forth with the scum!
Bring them over here!
Set it on the car!
For this, you will still pay for this!
', She captivates! Tie them up!
This is what happens to those who dare to stand up to the
Dsungars!
Who gives them the right to judge
about our country? These bastards!
Tomorrow will watch
twenty Dsungars the slave caravan.
Shall we attack them?
Do you know who gives the orders?
Who?
Ayur.
I have an idea.
I know who is
certainly like to help us.
Listen.
If you be free...
... And you want revenge on the Dsungars
, do what I tell you.
Here.
Hidden das.
If we attack the caravan tomorrow
'll stab her so the guards.
And you are who? '
I'm Sartai.
A Kazakh, just like you.
Good.
Freedom or death!
Hey! Way there! Get out!
What you doing?
Dirty Pack! Take that!
Come on, faster!
Run on, you rats!
- Caution, Kazakhs!
- Men, gather yourselves!
This is it.
You are surrounded.
Surrender, or you will be killed.
He said we were surrounded and
that we should surrender.
Do you know who I am? If not,
I will tell you like it!
I am the son of the powerful knight
Zhonon Batur!
On your place I would think twice
me, because just what you are doing!
If you value your lives,
not keep up us on longer!
If you are Ayur,
I challenge you!
He has proposed a duel. Your
against him.
What are you doing? A duel?
Trust me, I know what I'm doing.
This can not be.
He ​​defeated him.
I won. Remind yourself
my name! My name is Sartai!
Attack!
Korlan! Let them flee.
Yes, it runs! Go tell everyone that has
Sartai won!
Lliyas  You can read about it?
Show me.
- This is not just a simple letter.
- You. For whom is this letter for?
If you spare me,
I'll tell you.
According to your law would hang you anyway.
It's enough
if you give me a horse.
Sartai!
You have been good.
It was a pleasure.
Can we join you?
My name Asan,
this is my brother Usen.
What do you think?
You will not regret it.
Agreed.
Sartai? If we let him go, he is
tell us something about this letter.
Is it something important?
We really want to listen to his chatter?
Kill him like the others.
You just want to kill him?
We should prefer
collect information.
I do not care. If you can not,
I'll do it myself.
- Stop Taimas.
- Leave me alone!
Those bastards want to drive us out of our home...
... And now they have to bleed for it!
We will only take weapons and horses.
We can use any baggage.
Oh yeah? Since when do you decide
everything we do?
Sartai is right.
Take only the essentials with.
Yes, of course.
- We will spare you.
- I thank you.
The letter should by Akzhar.
A day away from here.
I understand. You are free.
Go where you want.
On! We've been here too long.
Taimas seems upset.
Let him.
He calms down.
Chinese tea.
- How good it smells! Smell!
- Everything stolen.
I hope this ends well.
Not underestimate the matter.
Sabitzhan.
We have not stolen anything.
We have saved our brothers.
How long we should still hide?
Approximately forever?
The Dsungars come!
Listen everybody!
What is this uproar?
What happened?
We are looking for a Sartai
Where can we find him?
The Knight Zhonon Batur
wants to speak to him.
If Zhonon has something to say, then
I will speak with him personally.
This will not please Zhonon.
We have an explicit command.
What do we do?
No time!
Do not say we did not warn you.
It will not be easy.
We need a plan.
First, we should draw out the warrior
from the fortress.
And then they all kill
between these two hills.
So it should be easier to get into it.
We attacking at night.
We do not know how many there really are.
At night they come out not sure
. We must do it now.
We are strong enough.
We need to catch before.
Since there are certainly 50 man
They have a whole arsenal.
We need to find another way,
otherwise it's too risky.
We should not underestimate that.
What is another way?
I have an idea.
But it is not easy.
Wait here.
You can purely .
Dear Zhonon. My sincere condolences.
There is no day without pain.
Believe me, I understand your pain.
I also have a son, you know.
I know.
War spare no one.
He died in a battle like a true man
No one is to blame.
But now I need to find this thief Sartai
justice and punish him.
Not because my son has died
... but because he shed the blood of innocents...
Stole their cattle and
.
This is why I am now asking you to
following favor.
Bring Sartai alive to me,
, or bring me his head.
I understand.
But that unfortunately is not so easy.
Maybe.
But I want it.
A white camel
crosses the land of nomads.
At first we thought you were a
Dsungar.
I'm here on business, you know?
I am interested in a girl.
Really? How's she like?
I really like them very much. She has captured my heart and
I always think of it.
And if she is not what she claims to be
?
She is smart and she is beautiful.
You would be a good wife, I think.
Then go easy on her and talk to her.
Maybe they can not stand you.
I am a warrior, all appreciated.
The girls also.
Insignificant chatter.
You can rather keep to yourself.
You have not yet discussed with her father
.
Have you no manners?
Everybody here  '?
Yes, they rest a bit.
A rider approaches,
ringing the alarm!
Help! Open the gate!
He's one of us!
It's one of us!
Open the gate!
Who are you and what do you want?
I only speak with Yessen,
your commander.
Why only him?
I bring a letter from Knight Zhoron Batur.
Originally, we started out to third
Shagal.
But Kazakhs have attacked us and only I survived.
Zhonon sends us a warning.
He writes that we should take us from
Kazakhs in the night.
- What's your name, where are you?
- My name is Gunga.
I am from the clan of Tsevden Batur.
from far away. No wonder
I do not know you.
You beat yourself seemingly well.
Be our guest.
Give him clothes.
And let him rest. - Got it!
Let the boy out of his sight.
I want you to guard him around the clock
. - Got it!
Can you see him anywhere?
No, nowhere. And it's
too quiet. We wait.
Hey! Where are you going? Since
gunpowder in it. Not sniffing around!
- I have to relieve myself.
- Then go that way.
Where long, you say?
There long.
Guards! Guards!
Fits on, he got away!
I think it goes.
This is it. Get on the horse!
Hurry up!
Lliyas!
I can not see him anywhere!
We need to find him!
Lliyas!
- Lliyas!
- We can not go without it!
- This is it! Come!
- Lliyas!
You scared us to death!
We get out of here!
Lliyas, I got you.
Give me your hand.
Up you go!
- All right, get out of here! Quick!
- Fast!
We ride back!
What did you thinking?
What if they now follow your footsteps
and come here?
How do you think
is this going out?
You should think,
before you act.
Your blind heroism can
we all fall into ruin!
That's all grown on your
crap Taimas.
- Uncle!
- Yes?
It gives me slowly with you.
Behave kindly appropriate.
Got it?
A  Sartai always reaps all the glory.
And I will always blamed.
Stop it, Taimas! We all have in common
risked our lives.
Red's only one you! He is the one who is honored
and the girls get.
Taimas, you are simply just jealous of
Sartai.
I'll show you,
how envious I am!
- Come here!
- Apart!
You all fell for it, huh?
I go.
Taimas?
Taimas!
Waiting!
Your stubborn children!
Do ye still be heroes?
Salaam aleikum!
ALEIKUM salam!
Are you from around here?
Maybe you can tell us where we need long.
Where are you going?
We are looking for a Sartai. It is said that
he is fighting against the Dsungars.
Oh really, is that so?
Do you know anything else?
We heard that he
recruited us as orphans.
He is very brave.
Let us join him.
Have you even heard of another
warrior from his group?
From a Taimas maybe?
Taimas?
- No. I have not.
- No, I do not.
Why do you want to join necessarily
Sartai?
Many groups are now fighting against the
Dsungars. Join with them.
No. We want to join Sartai.
- So you know where we need long?
- No, I do not know.
I do not know him.
We are riding on.
Great. They ride directly toward him.
Sartai?
I'll be right back.
This will be Taimas.
What is it?
I'm short today in
Rakhimzhans village was.
I've seen the Dsungars,
of your father killed.
What did you say?
Let's ride it tomorrow.
Sartai? I need to ask you something.
And what?
How come every
that just talking about you?
You are not alone.
We are a community.
Why did you start bossing all
?
It is not intentional.
We have vowed to kill the Dsungars
! And now thou wilt spare her.
Korlan would do anything for you
... but you can only think of Zere
, daughter of the traitor.
I do not understand you.
Korlan loves both of us since we are children.
Drawing with cere not as pure.
Well, something has changed.
Iliyas  now stands between us.
Why are you all listening to him?
Korlan, you and I
should disappear.
Let's talk afterwards and are now looking to Dsungars.
Father!
Mother!
Nazar! Taimas is back.
But Sartai not sitting on his horse.
Taimas! Where is Sartai?
Where is Sartai?
We are riding down the mountains...
... And then fallen into an ambush.
And Sartai...
What Taimas?
Sartai was killed.
Sartai!
Why are you riding in the desert?
Sartai wanted to Rakhimzhans village.
I could not talk him out of it.
He did not listen to me.
Where is his body?
- You took him away.
- Oh no!
What a misfortune!
Terrible times!
Oh, what a terrible time!
Give me the knife.
Father!
Thank you.
Here we go.
- Father, where are you? Mother!
- Sartai, run away!
Let no escape!
Drive them together!
Father!
Wake up.
Are you thirsty, my son?
Sartai?
Sartai.
- Can we come in?
- Yes.
- We get something to drink for Sartai.
- Sit down yet.
Here, drink this!
Thank you.
Hey, not lounging around here.
Out!
Father.
Sartai. Are you okay?
Zere, who gave you permission to be here?
That was me. It's fine.
If you have served
Sartai you can go again.
Kassym, accompany Zere
and her friends.
You have recovered you again.
That really makes me happy.
Listen to me now too well.
The Kazakhs are planning a battle.
I've heard that
gathered an army.
Where you would be better off
... than continue to maintain your reputation as
thief.
Your courage would certainly be an asset to the
warrior.
I think about it.
May God protect you for your care and kindness
.
Just one more thing:
Please give me a good horse.
I want to go tomorrow.
Now What?
What's Next?
Let the dead rest.
What is with you?
We will continue to fight.
We riding in the desert.
Who is coming?
What should we do there?
We will practice on the Dsungars revenge.
We kill everyone we see.
You are right.
It brings us not to be trusted.
Taimas! Then you should lead us.
Nazar is there.
A salaam aleikum!
ALEIKUM salam!
Get ready you.
We want to go and look for Sartai.
Old man, we can decide for ourselves
what we do next!
Come on, let's go.
Believe me,
... if you once again Uncle Nazar
insult, I cut off your tongue!
I know that Sartai still alive.
How do you know that Korlan?
I can feel it.
Do you want to accuse me of lying about
?
Taimas, I want you blame for anything.
Help us.
Comm
on break, as long as the
village is still intact.
Kassym, listen to me. Take two
warrior and then wait for Amantay.
If it is there, will you take him to the
western plains, you hear?
Then come to us.
Yes.
What Sartai?
Take him with us?
Zere, Sartai will only stop us.
We can not just leave him.
- Will he come with us?
- Yes.
Tell him that he walks with us.
Tomorrow you'll regret that, Father.
Are you ready to move away, my son?
I am.
Sartai, we will go out soon.
Father has allowed
that you can go with.
Your family is in danger,
when I'm with you.
I plan today
night ride back to the mountains.
Please come with us.
Please come with me.
No, I can not.
Then I'll come with you.
No, you can not go without the
blessings of thy father.
Zere, I love you to the very first moment
.
But now it's time for us to part
We can not be together.
What does that mean?
How can you just leave me?
I...
Hurry up a little!
We must have crossed the mountain pass before sunset
!
Nazar is here.
- A salaam aleikum!
- ALEIKUM salam!
Good luck for the resettlement, Rakhimzhan.
But why you are so in a hurry?
Is there anything wrong?
Sooner or later it would have been so far anyway.
By the way, we got your
Sartai to hurry.
Sartai?
Sartai!
Korlan!
My dearest brother!
You're still alive, Sartai!
- We thought you were dead
- Allah had an eye on me.
Sartai!
We have cried so much about you,
it was bad.
Korlan has been right.
- Our enemies are looking for you everywhere.
- Sartai, you're alive!
I wanted to ride tonight.
Uncle Nazar!
My boy, you're alive! Thanks be to Allah!
Your hero is in good shape.
- His wounds have healed very well.
- Thanks be to Allah.
Thanks be to Allah!
Main thing is that he is healthy and alive.
I have done everything I could.
Nazar is here, so there is no need to worry
.
May Allah bless you. I thank you with all my heart
, Rakhimzhan.
Sartai
and I will return again to the mountains.
The other guide you safely on your
dangerous path.
Thank you, Nazar!
- My boy.
- Stay healthy and take care of yourself.
Good luck to you.
I am Zere very grateful for their care and assistance.
And I hope there are better times
for us.
May you keep quite.
It is good to know that my son...
... And my daughter a friend like you have.
Have a good trip home!
Do good on you night, my friend.
Yes, we will.
We care of each other.
I know that. Allah be with you.
Allah be with you.
Until we meet again.
Where is Taimas ?
- He came with us,
- Sartai.
-... but suddenly he was gone.
- Oh, what do you need it?
Come on, guys,
Sartai help a bit.
For now, we go back to the village...
... And recover something of the excitement.
Come on, my brother.
- God willing, we shall meet again!
- Good luck!
Take good care of yourselves!
I'll stay here.
You go go and inform the commander.
Alright.
Woes Wilde.
Skin off!
Out of the way!
Way there! Make way!
Come in, but places the weapons.
I greet you!
Good to see you. Sit down.
If I may speak, we count
approximately 2,000 soldiers in Anyrakai.
And  10000 stand ready in the east.
Kazakhs We monitor every step.
What do we know about the exact plans of their leaders?
Currently gather your armies in two ravines Anyrakai.
In a few days they will be
far...
... And certainly do not feel it, then
attack us.
The 20,000 warriors of Luvsan-Daichin...
... Travel approach from the west and
combine to form a single unit.
What do you think, how much have the warrior
Kazakhs?
Less than 15,000.
They are also very poorly organized.
There is disagreement among their leaders.
Not all Sultans have agreed to draw with
in the war.
If that is so, we have
a good chance to beat them.
We are well equipped.
But we must not...
... Our troops thin out,
which are on the eastern flank.
Luvsan-Daichin executes the command.
Follow his orders!
Zhonon.
I would like to express you my condolences.
I thank you, sir.
Will not return without a victory.
I will not tolerate defeat.
This is our country.
Enough!
Stop it!
The victory will soon be ours.
The Kazakhs are miserably perish
and beg for mercy.
But we will flay alive!
Let's drink to Luvsan-Daichin!
Drain your mug! We drink!
Hey! Bring us wine!
Yes, yes!
Go get wine!
Bring me Sartais head.
And I want you Rakhimzhan kills.
To command.
Get out of here!
Skin off! Clear the way!
Rakhimzhan,
we are now back riding again.
You are now almost safe.
Just go, dear. Says Nazar,
that we will soon be on target.
A good trip.
Allah protect you.
What should we do?
I do not know. My head smokes.
I always wanted revenge,
but it has never been what.
There is always a way out.
I've heard that the battle will start tomorrow
.
The large Kazakh warriors will fight the
Dsungars.
Is that true? '
I would not have thought of Taimas.
He ​​has deceived us all.
If we get him,
I will kill this traitor.
Wait!
, Stand still!
- Who's that?
- This is Zere!
Please wait!
Take me with you.
I will come in to Sartai.
- Go back where you came from.
- Never!
Not even if you kill me.
I'll come with you. Return
go back home and keep us no longer to
!
We have no time for this.
No one will miss me with the whole
turmoil.
Please understand, I need to urgently
Sartai.
If there is no love
Sartai will be pleased.
Suppose they do with us.
It keeps us not already on.
What do you think?
Rakhimzhan!
Rakhimzhan! Zere is gone.
We can not find them.
Disappeared? Where should they go?
Addiction to her! Hurry up!
But what she up to?
Sure they will be followed
the other.
Two are with me riding and looking.
Manarbek! Take care of the people.
Why are you so desperate?
Is it just because Sartai?
On Listen to mock me.
My father would never let me go.
Do you think it was easy for me?
Or are you just jealous?
Do not be silly.
He ​​is like a brother to me.
Korlan. There is Rakhimzhan.
Stop immediately!
What are you thinking? '
Easy to disappear?
You bring us shame!
I knew you and
Kassym other hand would be.
But I could not help it.
Rakhimzhan, they would not listen to us.
We told her,
they repent.
Zere, you'll come back to us now with
.
We'll talk more about that later
Now we should turn back, the
Dsungars getting closer.
I beg you!
Not make me unhappy. - Enough!
Bring not more shame on us.
Kassym, Kassym!
Amantay is there.
- Salam aleikum!
- ALEIKUM salam!
We have been waiting for you.
- Where is Rakhimzhan?
- Gone away.
I will wait for you here.
Then we ride out!
We must lose no time! - Got it!
My two rides back to
caravan and tells them
... that I've taken with me as agreed
Amantay.
Father, what shall we do?
Stay calm.
I have gone on with them.
Zhonons permission.
Do not hold on us.
Let us pass.
After you we were looking for. Attacks!
Kill them! Kill them!
Father!
Do not come near me, bastards!
Father! Forgive me.
Father! Forgive me!
- Zere! Racing, my child!
- Father!
Save yourself!
Her killer!
I want you to go to Sartai!
Will happily!
Go to Sartai!
Father!
Kill them!
Zere! Get on a horse, quick!
Father!
Usen!
- Korlan, Zere created out of here!
- Come on!
Do not let them escape!
Korlan!
I'll hold back!
Disappears!
You  Grab the girls! Go!
Come on, quickly!
USER the whip, or you get nowhere more
.
It goes no further.
The horse is exhausted.
Take mine!
Hold on.
The horse finds his way alone.
- I thank you.
- Farewell!
Bring Zere home.
Zere!
Sartai please tell that his father would have been proud of him
!
He ​​is the Kazakhs lead to freedom!
Kill them, soldier!
Mother.
Mother, please stand up.
Taimas, where have you been?
- I'll tell you later.
- We have taken care of us so!
- We have to go now.
- You're back!
- Why must we go?
- Mother, please, quickly.
Taimas  what's happening here? What's going on?
Introduce yourself rather immediately.
- Nazar?
- Get him out.
Nazar? What is going on here?
My son! Tatmast
What do you do with it?
Taimas!
Mother!
There is no mercy for those who wear
evil in their hearts.
What does not matter?
Your mother will not know what you've done
.
What do you know already?
Bring it On! Kill me!
We will determine his punishment later.
Zere!
What is it? Where is Korlan?
Korlan and the other...
-... were killed.
- Never!
Tell me that's not true.
Yet.
I saw my father die.
Korlan and the other could not save us
.
They were all killed.
I ran away,
... to come to you.
- This is all my fault.
- No, it's my fault.
It's my fault.
Nazar!
Calm down. This is Allah's will.
He has brought in the prime of their lives to be
Korlan.
Calm yourself, my dear.
Nazar.
Nazar?
- Sabitzhan...
- Be strong.
By Allah!
Please do not!
Korlan is dead
You've killed so many people,
... but your vest is whiter than white!
You go out as innocent, right?
You have everything you've dreamed of you!
You have the fame and the
girl by your side!
And I am a traitor!
Bring it On! Kill me already!
No, Taimas.
I forgive you.
Then let me go!
I need to find Korlan and bury them.
No one is against our warriors.
With God on our side we will defeat the Dsungars tomorrow.
Very good!
A salaam aleikum!
ALEIKUM salam, sit down with us.
I greet you.
Take a seat, Abulkhair.
This here is the young Sultan Abilmansur.
I knew your father and
have already heard a lot about you.
Greetings. It is my honor to
get to know you, Abulkhair.
He ​​takes after his father, that's good.
Unfortunately, the two could never meet.
Now it is as hard as a stone.
I already see him fight.
He ​​is wild as an untamed horse.
My Lord. Amantay is there.
Let him come.
Amantay? Who is that?
One of us.
He ​​will bring us important news.
- A salaam aleikum!
- ALEIKUM salam!
Tell us what you know.
Luvsan-Daichin.
He has an army of 20,000 men ..
... And marched with this in our country.
That is, there are at least 30,000
together. What do you think?
It would not be our first battle.
We fight every day against them.
We have no choice but to win.
Let us not put off their number of
.
True words!
This battle is crucial for the future of all Kazakhs
.
If we lose this war,
then we lose everything.
So we have to win.
Taste it what it may.
Korlan!
Forgive me that I thought
bad about your father.
My father gave us before he died
, given his marriage blessing.
It is certainly not the right time, but...
... Think about it.
I have to make up for past
.
You have to go back to your family.
Sartai.
No matter what happens,
I'll stay with you.
Zere.
Do not be angry, but it's not a good time
it.
Sartai! The Dsungars are coming!
Aibek, go and hide with
cere and the other in the forest.
Preserves peace! Goes into the mountains!
If all the mountains!
Where is Sartai?
Zere, come here.
There are Kazakhs!
- Salam aleikum, Kassym.
- ALEIKUM salam.
Where is Zere?
In safety. She hides.
I'm sorry about your father.
You know so already.
I do not want to lose my only sister
. Get them here.
I offer you my head
... if I'm guilty in your eyes.
We ask for your blessing.
Morning already we are moving into a big battle
, in honor of our nation.
I have only one concern.
If I should die there,
who cares about my sister?
We should honor Rakhimzhans
last words.
Accordingly, I am ...
... Zeres responsible for welfare.
This should lead us his last will.
You have my blessing.
Tomorrow's battle will decide on
all our lives.
We stand side by side until the end.
So be it, brother.
A long time ago I took
big responsibility for you.
I do not know how long
I prayed to Allah.
And now I see
what 've become a strong man you are.
Therefore I will give thanks to Allah.
Allah hear us.
May you be free from the enemy our peaceful country
,
... so that they can rise
Kazakh tents everywhere.
Be the luck on our side.
Sartai.
We might never meet again.
But in my heart you'll be forever.
I want you to remember,
when you pull into battle tomorrow.
Zere, I love you from the very first day.
But I did not know about the price,
the cost to us.
Whatever happens, one thing you should know
:
I'll hold you forever in my heart
.
Allah!
- Advances closer together!
- Allah!
Forward, Kazakhs!
Allah!
Attack!
Sartai. Look, over there!
Pans to the right!
The battle has begun.
The Dsungars are superior.
You are in the majority.
You have their full combat power together down there.
We do not have time
to let our troops.
- How many are we?
- Seven of Turkestan.
- Thirteen of Oiyl.
- Eight of Bayanaul.
- Five of Torgay.
- Ten of the Urals.
Nine out Shalkar!
Sartai, we are about one hundred.
No, we are not.
My brothers and sisters!
In our hearts we are strong as a thousand fighters.
Feel the force!
Today we will take revenge!
For the shed blood of our fathers,
... sisters and brothers and for those in. ..
... Need to wander around their own country as
orphans.
Many of us will fall today.
But our courage will make us immortal
!
And the hand of Allah will show us the way!
We shall certainly make the Dsungars!
- Let's send them to hell!
- Down with them!
This is the all-
decisive battle!
We will carry the day!
And we should never meet again on this earth
,
... I promise you will
we meet again in heaven!
Let's get our freedom! Allah!
Stand by!
Sets!
Wait for my command!
Shoot!
Archers! Shoots
Korlan!
Shows no mercy!
Destroy them!
Power it down!
Tell everyone that we will fight to the last man!
Brings you victory!
Spared no!
Have you no compassion!
My Lord, Tomor Batyr, he has fallen.
Go.
Yes.
Whose  troop is it? You have entered the edge of the
Dsungars.
Sartai, as is the banner of Dsungars!
Just a little piece!
We will bring it to us.
Let them feel our wrath! Allah!
Where did they come?
Who is that?
Why do not they kill these savages?
My Lord, we have lost two generals.
Get out!
This cursed peasant pack!
Signals the retreat.
It's over.
Retreat! Withdraw!
Iliyas!
What should we do?
There is Sartai.
Asan!
My spear!
Taimas.
I got my revenge.
We have kept our promise.
Comrades!
We won!
Sir, the enemy has surrendered!
The victory is ours!
The Siegt is ours! Forward!
Forward!
The Dsungars are beaten.
This day belongs to you, children of Alash!
I told you, this is not a Dsungar
far and wide.
Come on! Who catches me has won!
Where you lead your way also,
in my heart you'll always be.
Next!
Aligns the dome for Sartaizhan
to as high as possible.
Zerezhan, take the two rods
and keep the tent roof. - Yes.
Thank you.
So, it depends on!
Nazar.
Nazar. We name the child after
Sartai?
But it is his father!
And how about if we rename it to
Alpamys?
No one will dare attack us.
Allah himself must have put in your mouth
those words. So be it!
Original sub by pulzator,
direct translate with google
by yusof125