Apparently, a building was due to an unknown infectious disease
precaution sealed off.
Among those that are included in the building,
Nearby residents, police, firefighters
and two employees of a broadcasting company ...
... Concrete information on the pathogen.
Neither the minister nor the experts were able to present ...
... There could be only one survivor,
when there is a TV reporter ...
... The streets around the building are locked spacious.
As just confirmed the military has brought the situation under control.
The air is clean.
Understood. Back before.
Here long.
Guzmán, Lucas. In the third floor.
Give me cover.
In here.
All right.
Second floor, fixed charge.
Los upwards.
Lucas.
Lucas! Mist.
Lucas, where were you, damn it?
- Completed. - All charges attached.
- Got it.
- Get out of here.
- What was that? - Shit, shit, shit.
The blast in four minutes.
Get out of here.
Get out of here, folks. All man out of here!
What's up?
Are you okay? Do you get air?
Get out of here, now!
Shit!
I have no more ammo!
- Shoot! Shoot! - Apart!
Shit!
You're the doctor.
You can help me.
Blowing up in three minutes.
As are the rules.
Come on. Come on. Come on!
We have to get out of here.
Help, I'm here!
- We have to get. - No way!
We have no time.
- Go before I do that. - You're crazy.
Get me out of here, please.
Damn.
Everything's fine. Do not panic.
I am doing you do not.
Blowing up in a minute.
Look at me. I'll take you out of here.
Hallo, Angela.
Only the rest.
The prevent you from hurting yourself.
So it is good.
Do you remember anything?
No.
Hold still.
Not.
It's almost over.
Where am I?
We ensure that you lack nothing.
Good night.
Sorry.
You may know where the wedding is?
Apparently I had a drink too much,
and my daughter took me to the room.
Because I must have fallen asleep.
I do not know what you're talking about.
I do not know where I am.
My mind is playing tricks on me well.
So, I do not know where we are.
- This'll be fun. - Have you seen anyone else?
Okay, we do the following.
I'll find out where we are. Wait so long here.
- Equal someone will pick you up. - Is good.
If you see my daughter, tell her,
I'm here.
Yes, I tell her.
How is she?
She is alert and has quite caught.
We only lose time. She is healthy. There is no reason for suspicion.
She was more than six hours in there.
We need to be sure.
That hurts me.
That's okay, I loose something.
Stay here!
Shit. Watch Out!
The patient escapes.
Seize them, if need be by force.
- How long? - Two minutes.
- It runs upwards. - Do not move!
Come on, faster!
She runs to the dining room.
Hold it!
Run! Run! Come on, walk on!
Run! Run!
Hold it.
- You? - Apart.
- We have them. - Have you not heard?
- Help me. - I said, "apart."
- Me. - Do not move!
Shit!
Come on, quickly.
Come on, come on.
Hold it! Hands up, no movement.
Hold it. Do not move!
- We have them and wait for orders. - Where are we?
Take down their arms. The test says it is clean.
- Who are you? - Take her to her cabin.
- You should rest. - No.
Do not worry, we will not bind. I promise.
I want to know who you are.
I regret the incident.
- I'm Dr. Ricarte. - I want to speak my superiors.
You sent here.
And my partner?
I assume you mean the Corporal Lucas.
We had to examine it. Just routine. He is soon to you.
Why are we here? That was not part of the operation.
We provide complete isolation here.
What for? Us nothing is missing. They examined me.
The situation is more complicated than you think.
There was another case in Barcelona.
We were able to bring it under control, but an error would be fatal.
Let me guess: a wedding.
There was only one survivor. I see that you already know it.
Hey, new passengers?
That's wonderful.
Excuse me.
Our captain Ortega happy to show you his ship safely.
Captain.
You probably came with the last group on board.
Seems that way. My name Guzmán.
I carry you around.
- Then you have the say here? - Saying, those who pay.
And the doctors pay enough so that I can sit down to rest.
40 years on the sea enough for me.
After this I will return home. It is time.
The doctors call the shots?
Yes, and they have brought along their own army.
I think you already know.
What is the status?
28 knots. Paying wind from the northeast.
We will meet soon to a low pressure area.
All right. Ahead with the least power. With luck, it warps before.
Of course, we have no hurry.
Gorostiaga ship's officer. From Bilbao. A great guy.
Pilot, which is simpler. And call me Goro.
This does not look good.
That one? Tell the venerable soldier. The were.
Do you have something done on it?
You should disinfect it.
Look at him, he's a doctor. Experts for Infectious Diseases and such.
Again.
This boat is too old for such jaunts.
No, he is not too old.
The generator is overloaded by all the medical equipment.
What's up?
We have brownouts, since we have expired.
At night, the current drops even completely.
The build down there a kind of laboratory or so.
- What medical equipment? - As I said, it does not concern us.
Sorry.
I did not want to disturb you, but ...
Do I know you?
No. With so many people, I'm all messed up.
But you are one of my grandchildren or to the bride?
You probably had a drink too much.
But do not worry, dear, me too.
Nick. Nick!
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Nick is the radio operator, even if it looks different.
Well, there is not much to do.
They have the frequencies encrypted, and only they have the codes.
- We have no contact to the outside? - Not even lifeboats treat us.
This has probably told you no.
Even the drainage system has been shut down.
They insisted.
Yes, as they called it? Security log.
- Is that understood? - How far have you got with the camera?
I'm working on it, but it takes.
The camera still works, but the hard drive has copped it.
I need to get out each frame individually. A Friemelei.
Nick is also our computer or whatever you call it.
The doctors want him to restore the video.
They are interested greatly.
I found them at the reporter.
That does not exist. You have Ángela Vidal saved?
So what in the way.
- If you knew how happy he is. - I am a huge fan of her.
I do not miss any of their programs.
And now they visit you personally.
So it looks.
If you have saved them, then you probably know them well.
Well, at least a little. Enough to imagine.
Yes of course.
Very good.
How do you find our Filipino DJ?
There was probably nothing better.
This is the signal for food. You get used to it already.
Here speaks the deep sea. What's up?
Everything okay down there?
- It's worse than I thought.
- crap.
You will need patience up there.
So, we have enough time.
Come for dinner. Then you go on.
Yeah, it's probably better.
Here you are.
What else is not.
You know ...
I eat at night is not much.
I've had enough a glass of warm milk.
I see.
Are you a glass of milk for the Lady?
- Milk? - And some cookies when it comes.
Maybe you have a little meat or at least sauce.
Hey. The bracelet does not mean that you're on a cruise ship.
Take it easy.
Where have you been?
- The same can I ask you. - Yes.
- Do you know what my family? - No.
I understand that the wedding has to be modern,
but this is too much of a good thing.
- Milk and cookies. - Toll.
Thanks, that's very sweet.
Over there, there is sugar.
Oh, yeah? A little bit will not hurt me.
She is totally confused and does not know where she is.
- Someone has to talk to her. - Oh yeah?
What do we say? That her family is dead?
I was just at the captain.
They had to cut the lifeboats, and the radio traffic is stopped.
- What? - That's right.
You have set up a laboratory.
There was no mention of preventive quarantine?
A laboratory?
They conceal what us. What are all the soldiers?
Have you seen the cameras?
They are everywhere. Even while peeing they film you.
That makes me mad.
Maybe it's not so bad.
Seems to have worked. Good work.
You could be good for Naval Intelligence. I have ...
- Seriously? - Well, you never know.
Marinegeheimdienst, wow.
Will you actually from here in the surveillance cameras inside?
- Who do you think I am? - You've seen earlier ...
That was my first act. So I pass the time.
As I have discovered that?
Madness.
- You they ask me before, right? - Of course.
And the lab?
The door opens with a numerical code. Visitors are as undesirable.
They weigh in safety, but do not know me.
There it is.
- What are they doing in there? - Definitely not good.
I have seen how they have invited cages.
What should be the well?
Cages.
And what's behind that door?
No idea. Since there is no cameras.
Closer I get to not ran.
200%. Not bad, eh?
No, not bad.
Goes with all cameras?
What are you like?
Please not now.
It happened again.
Comes.
Hey!
What is?
So, I do not know what are you doing down here,
but that would have long since work again.
Oh, yeah? Well, if you say so.
He wants to fuck us.
It may be that their negroes there, where you come from, everything look relaxed.
Here goes the other.
Now get the fuck out!
I come from Móstoles.
And here it goes the way it suits me.
You heard me. Hurry up.
Do not worry, it's me.
What are you doing here?
I was scared.
It's nothing. I'm with you now, okay?
- Let's go to the cabins. - Wait.
Please tell them nothing.
Look, nobody here does you what. Nobody.
Come over.
This will force eight, shall we live?
It comes directly to us.
- Apparently. - Shit.
This goes down sooner than we thought.
What you thought that?
On my last trip, it can still crash again properly.
I have a bad feeling.
- Sorry. - Good Morning.
Good Morning.
This is Ángela.
- Hello. - Hello.
Much of yours.
- It's over there ... - Goro.
- And since yours is bigger fan. - The one can say.
Well, I see sometimes your shipment.
- I'm Nick. Hello. - Hello.
- It saves the video from your camera. - Well, I'll try.
My Camera?
Is she here?
Do you see your gear actually on TV?
Of course not, silly question.
I remember the report with the garbage men.
You jumped into the container.
And the guy did not believe his eyes.
That was great.
- Want one? - No.
- Excuse me, would you perhaps? - What?
Interjected something for me, something like, "Hi, I'm Ángela Vidal"?
That would be really great.
It does not have to be now.
With so what annoy people secure at all times.
What a bummer.
- I'm sorry. - Nonsense, that was my fault.
It is waterproof. At least you sold it to me.
If we go down.
- Have you looked at it you? - A few excerpts.
I do not know what was going on, but luckily I was not there.
OPERATION COMPLETE
There it is. Very good.
This would be done. Now I need to sort them out just yet.
25 frames per second. This takes.
- How long for? - About an hour.
Maybe less.
You really do not want any? They are delicious.
The.
He is gone. The host is gone.
What the hell are you saying?
- Sound the alarm! - No!
We need to maintain control. Complete.
The straps are intact.
- Someone has loosed him. - Impossible.
A security guard would have noticed something.
- It was during the power outage. - And what about the door code?
- How many know him? - Very few.
- Nobody does something so senseless. - All come along.
Get in touch with the Taser and the serum.
- What you up to? - Find him before he attacks someone.
Let's hope this works.
Cursed.
- What about the food? - What is it?
The Filipino's asleep. We've been waiting for ten minutes.
This useless idiot.
Edwin?
Holy gun barrel as it look like here?
Oops.
Well, at least you gave thee this day even bother.
Sag mal, träumst you DAHINTEN?
The men are hungry, and the mood shifts equal.
Come into gear, did you hear?
I'll take that with. Hurry up, otherwise there will be trouble.
OPERATION COMPLETE
Yes. Wonderful.
That's it.
SEND FILE
Today's lamb. A blessing.
- I hope it is because something else. - Sure.
In 20 minutes, the second layer begins. Hurry up.
And, how are you today?
The well believe that I did not notice it,
that they have put me into the home,
without me saying anything.
Do you have something today hunger?
No. The hunger is not missing me.
My stomach does not play with. Could not you talk to the steward?
Maybe he can make me some noodles or croquettes.
I ask for times. I can not promise anything.
Hello?
Sorry.
Is there something else?
The Lady has a sensitive stomach and want some pasta or ...
Shit.
Here, try just once.
Bad it does not smell. I can try even once.
No! No! Do not eat!
- What's happening? - The chef tries to bite me.
- What? - And he did that?
No. No.
- Has anyone eaten what? - No.
Okay, you stay here.
- Wait. - Stay here.
Hold it.
- What happened? - I thought it was just quarantine.
Tell me what happened.
- The chef tries to bite me. - Do you know what that means?
- Where is he? - In the kitchen.
I have included it in the store.
All right. Come with me.
Only you.
Now it will not take long.
This will be my crowning glory.
Is not it?
Somehow it's not well.
I need to have an upset stomach.
It does not surprise me. This is the worm in the raw fish.
- Anisakis? - Was?
- This worm called Anisakis. - Whatever.
But there was no fish.
It would be better if you lie down a bit.
I hold the position.
A serum. We have worked on.
We were able to stop two outbreaks,
but next time we might have less luck.
I thought, nothing is known about the virus.
We know more than you think.
We have a sample.
We have injected a host and wait for the symptoms.
- One moment. Where did the test? - It does not matter.
Someone has released the host, and presents us with a problem.
- Excellent. - Give him the Taser.
We do not have much time.
- What are you doing? - We need to test the serum.
Once the door is on, press off. The electric shock will paralyze him.
- It has to be fast. - Okay.
Ready?
- Item. - Now!
Out of the way!
Get out of here!
Damn.
What the hell happened?
There is a feedback.
Damn, this can not be.
Apparently so.
It should have worked.
You have lost control. So, call kindly help.
- He's right. You need to get us out. - You know the rules.
Nobody gets us out of here.
Not any more.
We have to go to the lab and continue working.
Wait a minute, what about us?
We do not know whether the food is infected.
- No one has eaten something. - Yes, I arrived in time.
- Then there is no need to worry. - I beg your pardon? We were the second group.
- You can not leave us here. - We can not take any chances.
- Well then. - Now wait yet.
I gave you what you wanted. Do not do this to us at this.
What is he talking about?
I'm sorry.
Come on, we do not have time.
Lucas?
What have you done?
They wanted me to bring a blood sample from the building.
Infected blood?
- It was only a little. They thought ... - Who?
It is not a simple virus.
A few pastors have shown me terrible photos.
- You have no idea. - What else?
It is said that they would finance it all.
You miserable bastard! Now what?
Well though.
This is no way to deal with each other.
Do not know what it is.
Perhaps you would anyone say,
that your entire family is dead!
- Dead! - Leave her alone!
Enough!
Whatever that is,
if the food was infected, we can get to what passed.
We go to the bridge. Ortega can help us.
And how do we do that? We do not even weapons.
Take everything that benefits us. Pace.
- Here. - This does not help us.
What else is not. Lot.
Come on.
Will it soon!
Please do not take this as an insult,
but I could lay down and like something.
Back, back.
The, the, the.
Back, back, back. Back!
Shit!
Away from it!
We have to get out of here!
Come on, we need to bridge.
Come on, let's go.
They are everywhere on the ship. Where is Goro?
His concern was not good. He is lying down.
Shit.
- Deep sea. What's up?
- All quiet down there?
I did not come to dinner.
Then keep it up until you hear from me again.
- What's going on?
- Do what I tell you.
Lock the door.
Here long. Comes.
- Are you sure? - Yea, come.
Call my children to pick me up.
We're almost there.
- I make them any circumstances. - Come on.
What is now? Do you have anything to do?
What is this?
Get out of here!
Help me!
- I can not. - Shoot!
- I can not. - Help me!
What the hell is that?
Let him go!
What's this?
The oil pressure decreases. This was just what we needed.
Get out there!
Damn shit! What was that?
- Are you all right? - Yes.
Where is she?
- You ran away. - I get the same too!
- What do we do now? - You go to the bridge. I am looking for.
Hey, where are you going?
You have no weapon. That would be sheer suicide.
We can not let them down.
I've messed up.
I am what you owe.
Let's go.
It's us. Make you!
- Do not. - But ...
- Open up! - Perhaps they are infected.
- Nick! - Goro! Goro!
Los purely with you.
Close your door!
What's going on out there? Are the doctors coming after you?
Now you are in command. We go home.
I would like to, but the engine oil comes out.
He could catch fire. I put it off.
- No! No! - Man, now calm down!
Wait. We could turn on the auxiliary motor.
- Then do it. - This is only from the engine room.
To give a shit! What is really going on here?
You were in the building.
I have no idea. But these doctors know something.
And we need to find out what it is.
Logo. And how do we do that? Want to ask them easily?
Can not you hack into their computers?
You have connected me to send them the video.
Shit that have an internal encryption.
- What is that? - Not game.
I'm at a loss. It's all right.
It should have worked.
Maybe the virus has mutated in the DNA of the host.
- Then, each sample would be different. - Damn it.
We need the original strain that is not mutated.
The girl.
But we do not.
Gentlemen,
it's over.
No, wait.
- There must be a way. - I'm sorry.
You know the protocol.
- No. - 20 minutes. Enjoy them.
Waiting. We could try it with an enzyme inhibitor.
Maybe we reach a higher strength of the membrane.
This keeps only the process. It would not do.
Not without the original strain. I'm sorry.
I beg you. You can not do that.
We were not allowed to fail.
- You know the rules. - No.
Wait. He has done it.
We have the video.
Here, look at yourself.
- What are the oldest folder? - One moment.
Here.
What is this?
- My goodness. - Wait, wait.
I know that name.
From the building. He stood there on newspaper clippings.
This is the same girl. Since all photos hanging from it.
These are treatment data.
The Diocese of Naples has admitted it.
- The Church? - "Medical findings." What's this?
Wait a minute.
Was in the newspaper that she was possessed.
It was about the church, and a demon.
Let the shit.
It all makes sense. They wanted a doctor's judgment.
And who has admitted it?
Look at one.
What's this?
- It does not exist. -. And if it's the girl.
- What was she doing there? - It's rewind.
What is happening?
Oh Gott.
It is a parasite.
The source of the virus. We had him under our noses.
So this is the demon: a parasite.
This thing has used the girl as a wearer.
But in order to protect himself, he has immunized them.
It's all the years grown in the body of the girl.
Until he found a more suitable host.
We have the original strain. Set things up for the procedure.
We need to see her this thing. It is not too late.
Lady.
Señora, we have to the other.
Come with me.
No, no, no.
You can contact me times.
Do not move.
Drop your weapon and turn around.
Where is the reporter?
On cruise.
For the last time.
Where is she?
- What's happening? He does not respond? - No.
And he will not.
Then we go down yourself and make the engine.
For sure. Nothing easier than that. But I do not go out there.
Shall we wait around here until these critters come from?
This is my last trip.
If someone wants to go home, it's me. But I want to arrive alive.
Power on!
- Lucas! - Power on.
What is this?
No one touches them. Walk away from her.
- What's going on here? - It is a parasite. She wears it.
- From him the virus goes out. - I beg your pardon?
- What did you say? - The video shows it clearly.
You can look at it like.
What are you talking nonsense?
- It is clean. - This it is.
This thing immunized its host. So he can go undetected.
- Easy, we need her alive. - Let her go!
- You make a mistake. - They should let them go.
- Your gun is unloaded. - The here before.
You probably do not understand. The parasite is the original strain.
Only through Him we get the serum. It's the only way.
- I do not care. - Please, be reasonable.
We take him out of her without hurting her.
No, you not believe a word.
You are a doctor.
You know only too well that it is our only chance.
No.
No!
- For the laboratory it is too far. - We take the table.
- Fast. - No!
- Beeilung.
- Nick! Nick!
Careful.
No, do not. No! No!
- On the back. - Help!
Hold on tight.
Bind it firmly. Very good.
Wait, and if you're wrong?
As I said, you can view the video itself.
- Time is running out. - Nick.
Release it.
- I can not find it. - He must be there.
Doctor here.
Hold her head. Concentration.
So.
- I need towels. - In the bathroom.
Come on, quickly!
Fast. Here, hold her tight.
What is going on here?
No. No!
- Help me damned! - I have no ammunition.
Shoot. Shoot!
- What is it? - No idea.
Grab it! Go!
Shoot!
Shoot already! Go!
Holds it! You can not escape.
It's just a scratch. It's nothing.
No.
Waits.
With the strain it works. You said it yourself.
We can synthesize the serum yet.
There is no time. You know that.
You need me yet.
No.
- Now what? - Now we are looking for the reporter.
No, the game is over.
They now call for help. Only you can operate the radio.
- Not without serum. - You never get.
If we do not get it,
We return with safety back anywhere.
Come on, we have no time.
Radio frequency to nine. It can not be far away.
Fog.
So, to me that's enough. Can you steer the ship?
I can try. I helped a few times.
We go down. Do you know how in terms of the auxiliary engine?
I think so. But I'm not going down.
With four knives we will not get far.
- Let the shit. - Do you know something better?
Waits. In the chest at the front deck are fishing equipment.
Oh great, now we go fishing.
You stay here. We're going to look.
When we get back, we'll go into the engine room.
From closing. You're the only one who can steer the ship.
This is the front cover.
This is a damn maze.
Da. There she is.
I have them. It is at the cabins.
- Where?
- In the hallway to the cabins.
The, Beeilung!
Shit, she goes off to the cameras.
I lost it.
Where is she?
So a damn shit!
I see you. She goes to the dining room.
Go forward!
She is in the transition to the dining room. Hurry! Hurry!
Ángela, no. Over here.
It's me, Nick. Take the radio.
Now take it already.
Come on, Ángela. Now take it already.
Okay, now the Seven.
Push the Seven. Come on, pressing the Seven.
- Nick? - Now we can talk. I see you.
If you demolierst the cameras,
I can do nothing.
- All right.
- Run away. They're after you.
What are you waiting for?
They're right there.
What are you doing? They are every moment with you.
Ángela, listen to me.
You must immediately since gone.
Next.
Why are you doing this?
- You go inside. - All right.
- Los, los, los! - Hier, nimm.
- What are you doing, Lucas? - Wait!
Come on, come on!
The party can start.
Where is she? How can they escape us only?
- We already had. - Caution.
Where the hell are they hiding?
Help!
Help me!
Do something! The fire extinguisher!
Take the fire extinguisher. Come on!
Time!
Help!
- I do not know how that goes. - Pull him one on!
You are wrong.
I do not know what you want from me, but you're wrong.
Now you can check it.
Go to your laboratory shit back and check it.
And then you leave me alone.
I'm sorry.
- And now? We have no more weapons. - You can go.
Wait.
What do you have in your hand?
They were bitten.
Do not! No!
BEGIN ANALYSIS
DATA PROCESSING IN PROGRESS
Nick? Nick, are you there?
Why did you do that?
Trust me. I need the code to the laboratory.
Was?
I have to prove that they are wrong them.
Please.
But you have bitten him. I've seen it.
Trust me, Nick.
Together we can get away from here, but I need the code.
I beg you.
Nick.
All right. I give it to you.
Guzmán has shown me how I abfilme him through the camera.
Here it is. I hope you know what you're doing.
That can not be.
- But it is so. - But I've seen it myself.
- He has penetrated into you. - I do not care.
I'm not the one you are looking for.
- Harpoons. - Right, harpoons.
And nothing more?
- I see. - All right.
We're going down, and you put the engine.
Then it's time to go home.
Waits. Ángela is healthy.
Ricarte it has reviewed. I saw it by the cameras.
It is in the laboratory. We need to get them.
All right, I'll go. You two going into the engine room.
We meet here.
- Say it. - It is impossible.
- There must be an error. - There is no mistake!
You must stay away from me or I'll kill you!
Tell them! Now!
Say what?
The parasite leaves the host when he finds a more suitable.
Through them he could make it out of the building.
The video proves it. We have seen it.
I do not care. Their analysis has found what else.
If she was the host, you would be infected.
- She bit her. - I know that too.
But there must be an explanation.
You fooled us something.
Is that true, Ángela? Deceiving you tell us from what?
And you? Perhaps you are deceiving us from what?
Why did you want the code to the lab?
You asked Nick about it. How So?
I wanted to know what's in there.
When I met you, you came out of the lab, right?
You've released the monkeys.
Oh, yeah? And why should I have done that?
You saved me from the building.
We were almost a minute alone.
If this thing inside of me ...
It leaves its host when it finds a better one.
- Was not it? - Right.
The old host is then useless.
You are very brave, Ángela. I like that.
Self-destruction enabled.
Only 20 minutes.
- It's over. - Die!
Where are you going, Ángela?
Attention, you so do not hurt.
Immediately evacuate.
Now the party starts.
The detonation takes place in 18 minutes.
Immediately evacuate.
No!
Hold it.
Go back!
Give it to him!
Let's go, Nick. Go!
Los, los.
Here long.
- Here it is? - Yes.
- Fast. - Shit.
What is it?
- Nick, what is? - It's not.
Why not? You mean, you can.
- I said I can try. - Now, come on!
- Quick, quick! - Yes.
Come on! Shit.
Damn!
Shit.
Give me that.
- Run, Nick! - Shit!
Take to the motor!
Help me, Nick!
The Nick!
- No, no. Please do not. - Nick!
Immediately evacuate. The detonation takes place in 13 minutes.
Immediately evacuate.
Immediately evacuate. The detonation is performed in ten minutes.
No, do not. I am healthy. I am clean.
- Where is Angela? - I dont know. We disappear.
The ship will explode.
See ago. This is an inflatable rescue boat.
- The engine we can use. - Where is Angela?
Forget it. It's too late. You must think of yourself.
We make it two for this ship down.
Really.
Leck mich doch.
Class, Nick.
Immediately evacuate. The detonation is carried out in eight minutes.
Cursed.
Angela!
Monkeys!
Shit.
We have to go. The thing is in the air.
Holy shit!
- No! - Come on, the dining room.
You are away.
- Do you hear something? - No.
Immediately evacuate. The detonation takes place in six minutes.
We need to cover. The time is equal expired.
And the engine? Where is the engine?
- He has wedged itself. He is in progress. - Damn!
It does not matter.
We go out, get him and run away, okay?
All right.
One two three.
Did you think you get away from me?
After all, what we have experienced together?
No, do not!
No!
No, Ángela. I come to you with. I still have a lot to do.
Let's get out of here, go!
Detonation in four minutes.
The, lauf! Los!
Immediately evacuate.
The, lauf!
Weg hier, los!
Run!
Give me the engine. Give it to me!
- We have to jump. - No!
Then bring to us. Spring already!
No!
I can not!
Spring!
Nick!
Spring, Angela!
Lass's, Angela. Na los!
You have to let go! Go!
Angela!
- Nick! - Here! Take my hand!
Take my hand!
Take my hand, Ángela.
The.
Spring already in!
- Shit, he does not go. - Come on, we need to get out of here!
A car please on Hotel Plaza.
I put two guests from the center and go out.
War's a good party, huh?