My name is Abigail Russell.
I look like a slut,
but don't be fooled.
This is merely a disguise to lure
the dangerous predators
who walk among us.
This is their jungle,
their breeding ground.
And tonight, I am on the hunt.
These are the cheaters.
The married, lying scum.
They are like diseased cells,
cultured in alcoholic Petri dishes
that destroy
unsuspecting families.
And infect millions
of innocent vaginae.
There is no cure
for the married cock.
Only me.
The nurse.
Your money's no good here.
Two.
Hmm.
Till death do us part.
What would your wife think?
Abby: I always give
them one last chance.
So, you got a name?
I mean, what should I call you?
Call me whatever
the fuck you want.
(GASPING)
(CHUCKLES) Hey, come on.
Give me that back.
ABBY:
Beautiful family.
You're a very lucky man.
Okay. Okay,
give me the wallet back.
Fred W. Ward the Second
from Ridgewood, New Jersey.
Boring.
I get it. Really.
No, I don't think
you do, Fred.
You see, I'm all
about a man with a ring.
So, Fred from Ridgewood,
New Jersey,
are you a no-good
cheating son of a bitch?
Yes.
Yes, absolutely.
And your beautiful wife, how does
she feel about your behavior?
My wife?
She's got no fucking clue.
I'm afraid she will now.
Ow! Shit!
Did you bite me?
God, no. Just a small laceration
to the femoral artery.
You crazy bitch.
Don't be such a pussy, Fred.
What the fuck?
So, here's the deal.
At the rate you're bleeding,
you'll be dead in a few minutes.
And your wife and
those two beautiful girls,
they won't be scarred by a cheating
sack of shit like yourself.
Pay close attention now.
You have
a couple of choices.
You could either head
down those stairs...
However, in approximately 90 seconds,
you'll lose all consciousness.
Or...
You can take
the fast way down.
(SCREAMING)
Abby: From the time
I was a young child,
I was taught there is
no higher calling
than helping those who
cannot help themselves.
I work at one of the great
institutions of healing.
All Saints Hospital.
The men here take the doctor-patient
relationship very seriously.
When they say, "Open wide,"
you might want to make sure
they are wearing pants.
We each get a newbie to mentor
here at All Saints.
This is mine.
Danni Rogers.
She reminds me a lot of myself
when I first started.
She has the looks,
the insecurities,
and emotional credentials
to really make a difference.
This is our story.
And for you nurses
out there, lighten up.
You do your job your way,
and I'll do my job mine.
(MOANING)
I love my fucking job.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I am Dr. Robert Morris,
the Chief of staff
here at All Saints.
And on behalf of the administration,
I want to welcome you,
and let you know that
we consider our nursing staff to
be the backbone of this hospital.
You are our angels of mercy.
And now I would like
to introduce to you
the real person
in charge here.
The head nurse,
Betty Watson.
Welcome to All
Saints Memorial.
This is a momentous day for
each and every one of you.
For today, you join
the elite fraternity
of healers known
as the Nurses Corps.
Now get over here,
let me make it official.
(LARRY CHUCKLING)
Mom!
We are so proud of you.
Congratulations.
Thank you, Mom.
I was so nervous up there.
I'm so glad that's over.
Hi.
Abby! (GIGGLING)
We are so lucky to have you.
Abby, this is my mom.
Abby's been such an inspiration to me.
You have such
a special daughter here.
Thank you.
STEVE: Champagne.
For the lady of the hour.
Congratulations, baby.
I'm so proud of you.
Thank you.
Abby, this is
my boyfriend Steve.
Hi.
Abby Russell.
And you must be
the esteemed Dr. Larry Cook.
Yes.
Well, enjoy the moment.
See you in the halls.
I'll see you. Bye.
To Danni.
(SIREN WAILING)
Abby: This is Danni's
boyfriend. Steve.
I guess he wasn't smart enough
to go to medical school
so he did
the next best thing.
He gets to wear a uniform
and drive a big truck.
(CLATTERING)
Hello?
Is someone in here?
(SCREAMING)
You scared the hell
out of me. You're crazy.
We'll get in trouble.
What's gotten into you?
I can't believe
we're doing this.
Why don't you
just move in with me?
We can do this
whenever we want.
Move in?
Yeah.
What?
That's a big commitment.
What does that mean?
(STAMMERING)
I have a new job, my mom's
husband is an asshole.
I have all this shit
going on right now.
Baby, what am I missing?
What shit?
Are you kidding me?
Do you not listen to me when we talk?
Where...
Ooh! Whoa!
Someone is in here having sex with
a very gorgeous biracial man.
So I'm just gonna be on my way,
but consider this your break.
You're back in five. You.
Take as much time as you need
because my break is up next. Ow!
(CHUCKLES)
Ooh, I knew she was nasty.
I knew it.
Danni, listen
to me. Hey...
(SIGHS)
Look, I love you.
Okay, just tell me what it
is that I'm not getting.
Just forget it.
(SIREN WAILING)
Their car was toast.
High velocity impact,
driver's side.
Here's your driver.
Hey! You're not
a fucking spectator.
Get in the game.
(PANTING)
Abby: This was the first time Danni
had ever seen anything like this.
She lost her virginity
and the blood flowed.
She needed to
see some carnage.
It's part of being a nurse.
This job is more than sticking
thermometers in butts and looking pretty.
Dr. MORRIS: It's our job to take care
of the problems, not make the problems.
If you can't do this, work
in a doctor's office, okay?
You think about it.
Don't be here if you can't do the job.
ABBY:
That Dr. Pigface Morris.
He loves breaking
in the new girls.
You could see
the bulge in his pants.
I wanted to comfort Danni,
to hold her,
to tell her that everything
would be all right.
But Danni ran to
her boyfriend instead.
DANNI:
No, I can handle it.
Steve, I called you for
support, not to get a lecture.
I gotta go,
I'll call you back.
Steve, now is not the time.
Goodbye.
(SIGHS)
You okay?
I don't know what happened.
They were everywhere,
I just froze.
It happens to all of us.
The first big
one's always tough.
But, hey,
nobody died tonight.
Does it get any easier?
No.
But after a while,
you start to realize
that whatever
you're going through,
it's 100 times worse
for that person on the gurney.
I graduated first in my class.
I never got lower than a 97 on any exam.
I know what I'm doing.
Dr. Morris, shit.
He was so pissed.
He's always pissed.
It wasn't just you.
Come on.
We'll grab drinks
after I shower.
What's wrong?
DANNI:
That's Larry's car.
That fucking scumbag, I knew
he was cheating on my mom.
Wait here.
VALET:
See you again, Dr. Cook.
LARRY:
Thank you. Thanks a lot.
Larry?
I thought you were at a
conference in Boston.
Uh... Yeah, Danni.
It finished up early.
So you called my mom,
your wife, and told her that
you're gonna stop by the Fairmont?
Hey! Get your hand off
of me, son of a bitch.
You're out of line.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
Here you go.
I can't. I can't
have another shot, Abby.
It's so easy. Put your head
back.
Yes.
That's it.
Come on, let's go dance.
Abby!
(MOANING)
I wasn't sure you
were gonna wake-up.
(GROANING)
Where am I?
My apartment.
Jesus, really?
God, the last thing I remember was
downing a drink at that club.
How much did I drink?
Where did I get this?
I don't think I want to know.
Are you looking for these?
Yeah. Thank you.
God, I don't even remember
leaving the club last night.
Shit, did I ever
call Steve back?
Don't worry, I texted
him from your phone.
As you.
I wasn't sure if he
knew about your drinking.
How do you like your coffee?
You seem like a milk
and sugar kind of girl.
Here. Call in sick.
Spend the day with me.
We'll have so much fun.
Abby, it's my
first week, I can't.
It's a hospital.
People get sick all the time.
Sound sick.
Abby, I feel like shit,
but I'm not sick.
Look, I have to go.
Have you seen my
clothes anywhere?
I can't wear this to work.
Abby: Danni was getting all weird.
Not a "thank you."
She was so worried
Steve might find out
that Danni got fucked
by a total stranger.
And she's trying so hard to
remember if she did it or not.
And if that's not enough, she's
wondering if I was a part of the fun.
Here, you can have this.
I was gonna give
it away anyways.
Oh, my God,
thank you so much.
Abby: Either way, she'll tell herself
the whole thing was a dream.
But I won't let her
get away with that.
No, this was no dream.
DANNI: Could we just pretend
last night never happened?
How about next
time we just do, like,
lunch and
shopping or something?
Abby: She got fucked
and she liked it.
She can't turn
her back on that.
I won't let her.
Neighbor! Hey, neighbor!
Hey, haven't seen
you around much.
My schedule's been murder.
What happened to your hand?
Carpal tunnel.
Well, I hope
it's from having fun.
No, I mean,
not what you're thinking.
I worry about you
going out alone.
There's a lot of creeps out there,
and you look kind of, you know...
Slutty?
No, never.
But guys might get the wrong idea.
It's dangerous out there.
I see dead people all the time.
You transport
cadavers to the anatomy lab.
You work with
dead people, Jared.
Yeah, but they
weren't always dead.
Some of them were killed.
I'm just saying,
I've seen some nasty shit.
And if you need protection,
I'd be happy to accompany you.
You're such a gentleman.
I'll be fine.
You have
a good night, Jared.
You, too.
75 Rockefeller.
Abby: I knew Danni's prick
stepfather was a psychiatrist.
I also knew he was
a fucking scumbag.
But I'm
a hands-on kind of girl,
and since I'm here, it can't hurt
to deal with some of my own shit.
We've covered a lot of ground
for our first session.
What is it that gives
you so much anxiety?
I feel there's something
you're not telling me.
I'm an addict.
That's more common than you think
in the health care profession.
What is it that
you're addicted to?
Men.
There's nothing wrong
with desiring men at your age.
No, Doctor,
I'm not desiring men.
I'm addicted to them.
Abby: My mommy and I loved going
to visit Daddy at his office.
I want you to put on your
best smile for Daddy.
Okay, go on in.
ABBY:
Daddy worked very hard.
He was very
dedicated to his practice.
He was a great
influence on me.
Even now, the way I live
my life, the men I choose,
is a tribute to that man.
It sounds like you
had a perfect family.
Dr. Cook.
Do you think
you could help me?
Curing addiction doesn't happen
overnight, it's a process.
There are sex
addiction programs
and treatment centers
that I can recommend.
And we'll continue to work
on it here in our sessions.
That's all the time we have.
Same time next week?
And if you need me sooner...
Here's my cell.
Dr. Cook.
I feel pretty confident
with you at my side.
I can lick this.
Hi, Tony.
Good morning!
Good morning, Doctor.
I'm fine, thanks.
I hope I don't look that tired.
I don't know,
I couldn't get to sleep.
Good morning, Regina.
I guess the paramedic
liked your storage closet
because somebody got flowers,
girlfriend, and it wasn't me.
Huh.
I can't remember the last
time I got some damn flowers.
I don't know why I can't get my
husband to send me something.
I mean, I give him good sex, too.
I got a great rack.
No offense.
You are lucky I was on call.
Gunshot victim.
Internal bleeding.
We drained him,
sewed up the pulmonary lining.
But to prevent
the sack from reopening,
we have to keep
him immobilized.
I want him on Vecuronium.
Start him on 6 cc's.
Now, if he so much as
twitches, you let me know
immediately,
and we'll up his dosage.
Understood.
Hmm.
ABBY: Six cc's.
Sorry.
The Vercu?
Hey, Michelle.
I need 6 cc's of Vecuronium.
Okay. I'll get it for you.
(SIGHS)
Bumpy start for us, Rogers.
But I've got a feeling
you'll fit in perfectly.
Keep it up.
Thanks, Mel.
Thanks, Danni.
Abby: As I watched
Danni's little round ass,
the same one that I had
eaten the night before,
prior to finger-fucking
her to six orgasms,
and when I saw those tacky $10
flowers from dickless little Steve,
I couldn't control myself.
Fuck him. Fuck her.
I'm not some fuck toy to be
played with and tossed aside.
She needs me.
Whether she knows it or not.
I'm so clumsy.
It's okay.
Just be careful.
I'll replace the vase.
It's fine. Here.
I'm sorry.
The flowers are beautiful.
Did he fuck up?
We just had a disagreement.
Do you want to talk about it?
Just us girls?
Steve's now
pressuring me to move in.
Don't ever let
a man pressure you.
He's a really good guy.
They all start that way.
How well do you know Steve?
We met back when
we were freshmen in college,
but we just started dating
a couple years ago.
He was really there for me
when my father passed away.
What happened to him?
Car accident.
Drunk driver.
I'm so sorry.
I know how you feel.
I lost my father when
I was eight years old.
Hold out your hand.
This is an extra
key to my apartment.
Why? What for?
If you ever need
your own space,
or you just want to get
away from Larry or Steve,
it's there for you.
Thank you.
You know, funny enough,
Larry's the reason I go home.
I don't want to leave him
alone with my mother.
Steve just
doesn't understand that.
I understand.
You want to
protect your mother.
Every daughter does.
Hi, Larry.
Hi.
I can call you Larry?
Is that okay?
I mean,
office hours are over.
Of course, of course.
Is there something wrong?
Can you give me a ride?
Sure.
Do you want me to call
somebody about your car?
No, my car is fine.
It's my addiction.
It's happening again.
We should go
somewhere and discuss this.
Yes. Yes, please.
Your house?
Um, no. No,
we can't go there.
Oh. Right.
Wifey.
ABBY: And so the
dedicated husband,
esteemed author, learned
educator and renowned therapist
took me to an alley to fuck.
I wonder if he's going to
bill me for the session.
So, you are officially
my favorite client.
I'd say we're
having a breakthrough.
There's a hotel
around the corner.
What's wrong with right here?
Your wife ever
tie you up, Larry?
No.
(ABBY MOANING)
(LARRY SCREAMS)
What the fuck?
Larry, I've just injected you
with 4 cc's of Vecuronium.
So relax.
Wow. That was fast.
It's already
paralyzed your arms.
And soon, it will make
it impossible for you
to move any other
part of your body.
And while Vecuronium is slightly
more expensive than it's competition,
it produces few
adverse side effects.
It simply paralyzes you.
You look so adorable
strapped in like that.
Here, allow me.
So, let's make
this a happy event.
Once you're gone, your wife will
inherit lots and lots of money.
She will never know
what a creep you were.
You won't get caught.
So you see, Larry,
this is a win-win.
Abby: And as I watched
the monster about to die,
I knew I'd done
the right thing.
This would set things right
for me and Danni.
It was a perfect
jumping-off point.
The very thing for me
and Danni to build on.
I felt a new beginning.
There was actually moisture
trickling down my leg.
Larry made me come,
after all.
Holy shit!
Lady, you got a cell?
Call 911.
MAN 1: (ON PHONE) Directory assistance.
City and listing, please.
ABBY: In Manhattan.
The number of Maestro's.
Thank you.
We'll connect you.
MAN 2: (ON PHONE)
Hello, Maestro's.
Can you tell me
the specials of the evening?
We've got a very nice seafood
Risotto and a lobster bisque.
Sounds so good.
And we've got some
portobello-stuffed ravioli
in a bechamel sauce with
sauteed shiitake mushrooms.
Shiitake mushrooms? Wow.
It's just me, Jared.
Oh. It's kind of late
to be getting in.
Go back to bed, Jared.
You're the best man I know.
ABBY:
I returned home on a high.
An orgasm and
a great meal at Maestro's.
Jesus.
Danni, are you all right?
(TEARFULLY)
Larry was killed tonight.
It's okay, it's okay.
I'll take care of you now.
My mother's sedated. My aunt said
she'd call me if she needs me.
I just had to get out
of there. I'm a mess.
I'm sorry, I just didn't
know where else to go.
You came to the right place.
You'll stay with me.
Thanks, but I was just
on my way to Steve's.
I just really
needed to talk.
I think I'm gonna
move in with him.
Danni, you've
been traumatized.
Now is not the right time to
make that kind of a decision.
He cares about me.
I think he really wants to understand me.
I understand you.
Nobody understands you
like I understand you.
Nobody.
Now, forget
about this Steve.
He's just some loser
you fucked in college.
You're a nurse now.
Grow up already!
Why are you being like this?
Being like what?
I have to leave.
ABBY:
So that was it.
Nobody will ever
understand you like I do.
And you were right.
Larry was a pig.
I just hope his
dick got sliced off
when he went
through the windshield.
I never told you
he was in a car crash.
Miss Rogers.
Detective Ed Rogan.
I'm really
sorry for your loss.
I'm working on your
stepfather's case.
Post mortem and tox came in.
I might have some
questions down the road
so I wanted to
introduce myself.
This probably
isn't the best time.
Probably.
I needed to speak
with anybody
who saw your stepfather
the day he was killed.
Got to roll with
the punches here.
Well, if there's anything you
can think I might need to know,
I would
appreciate you calling me.
I can't think of anything
I need to tell you about him.
Well, again, I'm really
sorry for your loss.
Just give me a second.
Why were you
speaking with that cop?
I was a patient of Larry's.
He meant a lot to me.
I never mentioned it to you.
Please,
give your mother my best.
ABBY: And as simple
as that, I left her.
I had to get back to work
and this mentoring thing
was becoming a distraction.
I wasn't myself.
But I would have never guessed
what was coming at me next.
Good morning! Isn't it
a lovely day to smile?
Good morning.
Have a wonderful day, okay?
Good morning! Oh, darn.
Good morning.
How are we today?
We are peeing in a bag.
Oh! How convenient!
(SCOFFS)
Would you look at this?
What?
This damn lady with these
smiley face stickers.
There are no
smiley face people here.
You think this man pushing his
bladder in a bag feels like smiling?
Probably not.
You think me having to change that
bag is making me want to smile?
Definitely not.
No. Hell no. I hate
these smiley face people.
I tell you what, she better
not bring her ass down here
because I will punch that
bitch right in her face.
See who's smiling then.
Oh, shit, here she comes.
Look down,
I mean, don't look up.
Act like you're
doing something.
Don't look up.
Shit.
RACHEL:
Good morning, Regina.
How did you know my name?
Well, I know everything. I'm
the new HR director. (LAUGHS)
Plus, you're wearing
a nametag. Right there.
(LAUGHS)
I can see it.
So, you can fire my ass.
It's only my first day.
Give me some time.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
That's not funny, honey.
We got a lot of work
to do around here, okay?
We don't got
time to be happy.
So how can I help you,
Miss Adams?
Thank you for asking.
I'm looking for Abigail Russell.
She's doing her rounds. 431.
Thank you.
Oh, no, I'm...
Have a wonderful day.
What's...
See, no, honey, I'm not
really the smiley face type.
Do you have an angry face?
(VENTILATOR BEEPING)
Hello. Have a good day!
Abby?
Hi, Rachel Adams. I just
started up in Human Resources.
Welcome aboard.
Oh! Thank you.
(TRILLING HAPPILY)
(LAUGHING)
You know, you look really familiar.
Where did you grow up?
Right here in New York. You?
A few Miles away. Paramus.
Can't say I've ever been.
Gosh darn it,
you look familiar.
Where did you go to college?
Syracuse. How about you?
Rutgers.
Oh, well,
we'll figure it out.
Well, it looks
like you're very busy.
Yay! So, when
you get a moment,
I'd like to go
over the schedules,
make sure that
we're staffed properly.
Okay, I'll drop by to see you.
Okay.
Thank you. (GIGGLES)
Oh! Oh!
I just realized
who you look like.
ABBY:
Anybody good?
Well, no one you'd know.
My next door neighbor Sarah.
They put her in Sunnyview Institute
when she was just a kid.
The last time I saw her, she was putting
her mother's house up for sale.
But that was a few years ago.
Well, if I run into
someone who looks like me,
I'll make sure to send your regards.
(RACHEL LAUGHS)
Hey, you got any more
of those smiley face stickers?
I'll bet they'd really cheer
up some of my patients.
Of course! Aw!
Thank you.
You're the spitting image of Sarah Price.
Just so you know.
Wowee!
(RACHEL HUMMING)
University of Syracuse. Hmm.
(MOANING)
(EXCLAIMS)
Oh, my God. You scared me.
Is everything all right?
It's been quite a first day.
That was interesting.
ABBY:
I'm so sorry.
It sounds like you
could use a drink.
You want to meet
up later tonight?
Sure.
The Sutton?
It's a date!
Girls' night!
Mmm-hmm.
(SIGHING)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
Abby: Hey.
Do you want something?
I thought you might like to
join me and the new HR girl.
We're gonna go grab a drink.
I'm busy.
I feel like you've been avoiding me.
Where are you right now?
I'm at Steve's.
We're having dinner at his house.
Really?
You need some help with that big bag?
(LINE CLICKS OFF)
ABBY: I was truly confused
by Danni's behavior.
Larry was her stepfather.
She hated the guy.
He's gone
and she's mad at me.
I failed as a mentor.
She failed as a friend.
Game on.
STEVE: Hey, baby.
Didn't hear you come in.
Hi, babe. Hey.
Hi.
Can you get me
my water bottle?
Yeah, sure.
Thank you.
What are you
doing here still?
Just trying to get out the door.
I'm running late.
Looking at porn?
No, I'm just clearing spam.
Baby, you have to get a better firewall.
You good?
What's up with you?
Just need you to hold me.
Sure, baby,
but I can't guarantee
that it won't turn
into something else.
You okay?
What's going on?
It's Abby. She...
I found out she was a
fucking patient of Larry's.
Okay, and?
Well, we are...
We were getting close
and she never told me that.
Since when did you
guys become close?
We're not,
she thinks we are.
And she should have
told me about that.
I mean, she knew how
I felt about Larry.
Danni, is there something else
going on between you guys?
Like what?
Like, you're having other
issues and reading into things.
(PHONE CHIMING)
Who's that?
It's the captain.
He's pissed.
Look, baby, I know this is something
that you need to talk about
and I want to hear it.
Just go. Go to work.
I do want to talk about whatever
it is that's bothering you.
It can wait, okay?
Okay.
All right.
I'll see you later.
(COMPUTER BEEPING)
Is that Danni?
Hi, Danni!
Hi, Rachel.
Danni, say hi.
Hi, Danni. Hi, I'm with Sarah.
Hey.
I'm not with Sarah,
I'm with Abby.
I keep calling her Sarah
because she looks like Sarah,
but she's not Sarah,
she's Abby.
Abby, say hi. Say hi, Abby.
Hey.
Cheers, okay.
So many cheers to you
and to everybody in the world.
(LAUGHING)
Are you okay?
Danni, no...
Um...
Rachel.
Rachel, look behind you.
Rachel, behind you.
You go, girl!
Behind you!
No, no! Behind you, look!
Look, no, no, no.
Look behind you! Look behind you!
No, look, look.
Rachel, look!
MAN ON PHONE:
911, what's your emergency?
Hi, I think I just saw
someone being killed.
It was online,
they skyped me.
Abby Russell, she lives off of Queens
Boulevard in Long Island City.
It's 150117th Street.
Abby Russell.
And she's the victim?
No, she's the killer!
It's happening right now.
You have to send somebody now.
Miss, we're dispatching
a unit right now.
(COMPUTER BEEPING)
ABBY: Rachel's been looking for
a reason to 'cause trouble.
Sticking her smiley little face
into places it shouldn't be.
That's not the kind of things friends
do to each other, is it, Danni?
Poor Rachel.
It looks like someone won't
be at work tomorrow.
Oh, my God.
All right, Miss Rogers,
I think I got it.
You'll just wait here a moment,
Detective Rogan will be with you
when he finishes
his interview.
He's gonna have
some questions.
If you'll excuse me, miss.
ABBY: Danni called the cops on me.
Pathetic.
So I told the big,
black stud cop
that Danni was
a damaged little girl
and how much it pained me
to see her this way.
I'm not sure, but I might have
even squeezed out a tear.
You are lucky.
Your friend's not
pressing charges.
You can't just call 911
and accuse someone of murder.
Hey, what's going on?
Are you okay?
I saw her raising the
needle to Rachel's neck.
Rachel Owens is fine.
She drank too much.
She was passed
out on Abby's couch.
Abby's taunting me.
She's doing this to fuck with me.
Abby Russell seems to think
you're obsessed with her.
Said you broke into her apartment
the night your stepfather died,
that you must have
made a copy of her key.
She gave me
a copy of her key.
Why would she
give you a key?
She suggests you wanted to
be more than just friends.
It isn't like that.
It's not like that?
What is it like? Huh?
Is it like this?
Or is it like
(EXCLAIMS) that?
Huh?
Here's another one.
(LAUGHS)
You guys.
This is my favorite one.
She says you're
obsessed with her.
She drugged me.
I ran a blood test.
I had rufilin in my system.
Can you prove it?
Word of advice,
stay away from Abby Russell.
She killed my stepfather.
She told me to my face, she killed him.
Yeah, I read
your report. Here.
This word.
Can you pronounce it for me?
Vecuronium.
Huh.
What is that?
It's a paralytic drug.
Well, the autopsy report shows your
stepfather had it in his system.
Why would Larry inject himself
with a paralytic drug?
He wouldn't.
It paralyzes you.
Well, someone did.
My boys down in the lab,
they're never wrong.
And something
else is biting at me.
The same day your stepfather died,
you signed out the same drug.
How crazy is that? Huh?
Any reason I shouldn't be
digging up your stepfather?
You can go.
I can only imagine
what you're thinking.
No, you can't.
Steve, please, I'm telling the truth.
You're telling me the truth?
So, you're telling me that somebody
photoshopped those pictures up there?
And somebody else forged your
signature at the hospital.
Steve...
You think I'm stupid, Danni?
I know it looks bad.
Jesus!
It's not like that, though.
It's not like that.
And you've been fucking
around on me with Abby.
I haven't. You know me,
I wouldn't do that.
Steve.
She's a liar, Steve. She's a fucking liar.
She made all of it up, okay?
Can't hear you.
She made it all up.
You know me.
(REVVING ENGINE)
I won't be home tonight.
Steve!
Don't do this.
I didn't really know
who else to turn to.
It's just...
(GASPS)
MAN: So, you're the nurse from All
Saints that called about Sarah Price?
I am.
Man, you know, I haven't thought about
Sarah since she left here when she was 18.
Why was she here?
Poor kid, you know.
She was only eight years old when her
mom walked in on her dad at the office.
He was playing hide the snake
with his nurse.
Robert.
How could you?
Could you wait outside?
Mommy and Daddy need to talk.
Yeah, go on outside, honey.
I told you never to
barge into my office.
Never again, you understand?
When the father's nurse testified
in support of Sarah's mom,
the state sent
the little girl here.
So, what happened to Sarah?
Sarah was a very
complicated kid.
Kind of stuck to
herself most of the time.
Cutest thing, though.
You know, she used to always
walk around with this doll.
It was a nurse's doll.
What happened to her?
About a year later,
the mom committed suicide.
Sarah had no other family.
One of the nurses here, she
became like her guardian Angel.
Janet Russell.
She and Sarah were inseparable.
Sarah used to follow her
all around the institution.
They developed quite
the mother-daughter bond.
As a matter of fact, when Sarah was
released, she went and lived with Janet.
When Janet retired, she
just stopped coming around.
It's like she
just disappeared.
Not sure whatever
happened to Sarah.
Dr. Morris,
I got your message.
What's the issue
you want to discuss?
One of our young nurses had some
troubling things to say about you, Abby.
Well, you know I can be a
little tough on the new girls.
Well, this sounded
a bit more than tough.
I'm considering my options.
Either I can look into this complaint
by the sensitive young nurse,
maybe bring the matter up
before the board...
Or?
Or I provide you
with an opportunity
to show yourself in
a different light.
Let's go someplace private
where we can talk.
(GRUNTING)
You're fucking crazy.
What the fuck?
Let me get some toys.
You know, life is all about
choices, Dr. Morris.
You chose to have
a wife and a family.
(SMOTHERED GROANING)
And I'm guessing that your
kids will be quite messed up.
Now, that is so unfair.
These are just children,
Doctor.
Pure, innocent souls.
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
So, here are your choices.
We can gouge your
cheating eyes out.
Or do we cut out your heart?
(MUFFLED SHOUT)
That is assuming you have one.
Stay with me, John.
No, no.
Let's get rid of
Mr. Weenie.
So he can't cheat on
Mrs. Whiney anymore.
And by the way,
Mr. Weenie is looking
very Teenie right now.
Fuck you.
Should we go for it?
No, no, no!
Yeah?
Fucking Christ!
No.
Fucking insane.
Shh!
(TOOL WHIRRING)
No, no!
I say we start
with your arms.
No, no, no!
(SCREAMS)
Nurses' station,
this is Regina.
Regina, it's Danni Rogers.
I need to talk to Rachel from Human
Resources and I don't have her cell.
Can you look it up for me?
Yeah, because I don't
have nothing else to do.
I'm not an operator.
Come on,
Regina, it's important.
You can look it up
in the employee directory.
The operator
won't give it out.
Anything else?
And by the way, I saw your cute
little boyfriend roaming the halls.
I will let him get a little taste of this
until your skinny ass gets back here.
I could grow that boy up real quick.
Okay, wait. No, here it is.
How about this, girl? They got it
listed under "Smiley Face Bitch."
Regina, can you connect me?
Yeah, I can connect you.
It would be my pleasure.
Because I don't have
a damn thing else to do.
(PHONE RINGING)
Come on, Rachel.
(RINGING SOUNDS CLOSER)
What?
Oh, my God.
(MOANING)
ROGAN:
Really, now?
I'm gonna take
a cold shower.
Hello, sweet thing.
What did you do to Rachel?
ABBY: I was going to ask
you the same thing.
Her blood is in your car.
So is her phone.
Where is she?
She didn't show
up at work today.
I think
something's going around.
I sure hope Steve
doesn't catch it tonight.
(PHONE DISCONNECTS)
(DIALING)
(RINGING)
VOICEMAIL: Hey, it's Steve.
You know what to do.
Steve, listen,
I know you don't believe me,
but you have to stay
away from Abby, okay?
She's dangerous.
You have to trust me.
Abby?
Hey, Abby?
(SCOFFS)
Move!
Excuse me, ma'am?
Here!
VOICEMAIL: Hey, it's Steve.
You know what to do.
Shit.
We'll catch up. All right?
All right, man, talk to you later.
You okay, buddy?
Hang tough, we're gonna
take care of you, man.
Detective Rogan,
it's Danni Rogers.
Look, I know you
think I'm obsessed with.
Abby Russell,
but please just hear me out.
Abby Russell is,
in reality, Sarah Price.
Call the
Sunnyview Institute.
Check it out for yourself,
you'll find out the truth.
Regina!
Regina, Regina, Regina.
Have you seen Steve?
Girl, get your
sex drive in check.
I'm being serious. Fuck.
Where is Steve?
Get out of my face.
Hey!
REGINA:
Hey, hey, hey!
This is a hospital,
not the damn roller derby.
What's going on
with the two of you?
Danni, you know better.
You don't air your dirty laundry at work.
Move, bitch!
You settle down, girl.
You're not going
anywhere, Sarah.
Who?
You lied about your father.
You lied about everything.
Hands off of me!
Don't you touch her.
(MUSIC BLARING ON HEADPHONES)
(DANNI SCREAMING)
You've ruined everything,
you bitch.
(SCREAMING)
Whoa, whoa.
Abby. What's going on?
Danni Rogers is after me.
Please call for help.
Okay, hold on.
Just wait right here.
This is Daniels up on seven.
Danni Rogers just assaulted Abby Russell.
Call NYPD.
Ah!
No! Call the police.
POLICEMAN:
Shit, let's go.
Abby, stop!
(GRUNTING)
Hey. Hey, stop it. Enough.
What the fuck is going on?
(SURGERY TEAM CLAMORING)
Sarah, you don't
have to do this.
I can help you.
You're sick, Sarah.
Let's get you better.
I care about you.
You had your
chance to be my friend!
(SCREAMING)
POLICEMAN:
Hey!
(MAN ANNOUNCING ON PA)
Danni!
Get off of me, Steve.
Danni, calm down.
Let go of me.
Listen to me! Relax!
What the hell is going on?
What is going on?
Steve, you have to
believe me, okay?
She's crazy,
she's a killer. She...
Abby?
Yes, Abby's a killer. She's...
She's gone.
Abby!
Get it open. Go!
It's not working.
She fucking locked it!
Hey! What the hell?
Are you fucking crazy?
Come on!
Open the door!
(HEART MONITOR
BEEPING RAPIDLY)
(BEEPING STOPS)
(INAUDIBLE)
She's saying something.
What the fuck?
(GROANING)
Steve, look at me, okay?
It's gonna be okay.
Stay with me.
Behind you.
Shit.
Look at me.
(TEARFULLY)
Please, help me.
Oh, my God.
Bring a gurney.
Okay, go, go, go!
Prep two, now.
Joan, get this patient down to surgery.
I gotta take care of...
Abby!
Oh, my God.
You heard.
It was a nightmare.
Who the fuck are you? Huh?
Should I call you Sarah?
I don't care who
the hell you are.
You're under arrest in connection
to the death of Larry Cook.
I thought we had
a connection, you and I.
Shit.
We fucked.
End of story.
All right, I don't
know who the fuck you are,
but you have
the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can be used
against you in a court of law.
Look, if it's money you want, you
can have everything I've got.
Shut the fuck up.
Anything you say...
Please, don't shoot me.
Leave me alone!
You crazy bitch.
Please!
Oh, my God. I warned you
it's dangerous out alone.
Jared, you had no choice.
You did what you had to do.
Should we call the police?
We should call the police.
No, listen to me.
He's dead.
You were just protecting me.
Fuck, he's a fucking cop!
Jared.
We can handle this.
We just need to
make this go away.
The police are gonna
turn things around like this
and make you look
like the bad guy.
And you know what
they do to cop killers.
Jared,
you did the right thing.
Thank you for
being there for me.
I can make this go away.
Thank you, Jared.
You saved my life.
Abby: There are two
sides to every story.
Some would see this chapter of my
life as the work of a sick woman.
The way I see it,
everybody's better off.
The wives, the kids
and their bank accounts.
A few less scumbags
to spread unhappiness.
My work here is done.
Can I help you?
Hey there, good morning.
I'm Rachel Owens.
Oh. You're
the new HR lady.
Dr. Bailey's expecting you.
Down the hall on the left.
You are such a dear.
Thank you.
And you have
a wonderful day, okay?
http://subscene.com/u/659433
Improved by: @Ivandrofly