What it was like long
before I was born
Before the war with
the machines
I remember a green world
vast and beautiful
Filled with laughter
And hope for the future
It was a world I never knew
By the time I was born
... all this..  was gone.
SkyNet
a computer program designed
to automate missile defense
it was supposed to protect us.
That's not what happened.
On August 29, 1997
SkyNet woke up.
And decided all humanity was
a threat to its existence.
It used our own
bombs against us.
Three billion people died
in the nuclear fire
The survivors called
it .. Judgement Day
People lived like rats
in the shadows,
hiding, starving, or worse
Captured and put into
camps for extermination.
I was born after Judgement Day
in a broken world
ruled by the machines
The worse were infiltration units,
designed to pass for humans.
We called them Terminators
Where xxxx ?
Anyone else down there?
and then one man found me
His name... is John Connor
And he changed everything
I  xx xxx
and feed us
he freed prisoners
He taught us to smash
the machines to scrap
People whisper about John
wonder how he can know
the things he does
They use words like, prophet
but John is more
we're here because tonight
he'll lead us, to crush
SkyNet. For good.
Sir, request to join the
Colorado Offensive.
I need you with me, Reese
we're talking about the complete
destruction of Skynet, sir.
The Colorado Unit will succeed
The machines will fall tonight
Right here Los Angeles is just
as important too, maybe even
maybe even -- Even more than
destroying SkyNet's central core?
John, I don't understand why you're
leading an attack on a workcamp
Because the workcamp
is just a camoflauge
Inside the camp is a hangar
Beneath the hangar, Skynet's
hidden it's final weapon
When Skynet realizes it will deploy that
weapon to insure it's own survival
We take it tonight,
there is no tomorrow
Then we'll take it
You're my right hand, Reese, I thank you for it  -- You don't need toDialogue:
0,0:05:27.33,0:05:28.77,Default,,0,0,0,,You gave us all a future, John
I'm going to use mine
When this is all over, I'm...
going to find my
parent's house
Re-build it
use my hands, for something
other than killing
How about you?
cold beer will be good, ha hah  -- that's your perfect plan? Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.05,0:05:53.06,Default,,0,0,0,,To
tell you the truth, I haven't thought about it -- Yes, -- I see that
I think, that no
matter what happens
will be better than this
So many of us have
died, to get here
I want you to know that, Kyle, if there
was another way, I would have taken it
The machines think
that we can not win
The machines think, that
we will not strike
The very heart of Skynet
Yet here we stand
On the precipe of
the final battle
If we die tonight..
mankind dies with us.
I look at each of you.
And I see the marks of this
long and terrible war
We fight ... for our children.
Our children's children. So they
will not carry these marks.
But they will know who we
are, and what we did!
That we did not bow down.
We did not give in.
We rose up.  On this
moment.  On this hour!
Willing to sacrifice everything, so
that they could live in freedom!
On this night, we take
back our world!
We'll need fifteen minutes to
prepare the transporter, sir.
We'll have the exact
co-ordinates, momentarily
Los Angeles, 1984
Los Angeles, May 12th
of '84
Skynet knew it was losig
The machines tried
to rig the game.
Sent a terminator back to
the time before the war
What who's the target?
my mother
Sarah Connor
If the machine suceeds,
I'll never be born
they'll kill her first
And doing so, erase every
victory we fought for
Including, tonight's
There won't be a Resistance
to challenge the machines
With this one act
Skynet would win
We could use the technology ourselves, send someone back
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.73,0:12:45.95,Default,,0,0,0,,I'll go back
Why should I send you
over all of them
I would give my life
for Sarah Connor
All these people would
die for Sarah Connor
What makes you any different?
You know why...
Everything you told me about
her. I know her, John
Let me save her.
You'll be going back in time to
when\ she'll be scared and weak
Even I tell her who I am,
she's not going to believe me
Tell her this
Thank you Sarah. for your
courage during the dark years
There is no fate, except
that we make ourselves
You'll need to be stronger
than you imagine
You must survive, or
I will nver exist
Take care of her for me, Kyle
I will. Promise you.
hey, hey, What's wrong
with this picture?
Nice night for a walk, ey?
Nice night for a walk
Wash day tomorrow, nothing
clean, right? -- Nothing clean
Hey, I think this guy's a couple
of\ cans short of a six-pack
Your clothes. Give
them to me, now
You won't be needing
any clothes
I've been waiting for you
Police, that SOB just
stole my pants
What day is it?  Of what year?
May 12, 1984
The day you arrive
LAPD! Freeze!\  --
ah, now that hurt
xx you okay?.\  --
You tell me, O'Brien
You can listen to me, or
we'll all going to die
I had it under control.\
-- Yeah, sure, TJ Hooker.
Here's what you don't do
your first day on the beat
By the way, you're filling out
the paperwork.\ -- xx xxx!
It's a machine that
kills humans
Uncuff me.\  -- No,
you're under arrest.
What part of kills humans
is confusing to you?
Take them off!
We're screwed are we?\
-- Pretty much.
Come with me if
you want to live
Now, soldier!
Kyle Reese?
You're Sarah.\  --
Yeah, I know that.
You hurt your head back there?\  --
It's a Terminator, IDK what model.
T-1,000, liquid metal,
shape changer,
he only needs to touch
something once to mimic it
You know about Terminators?
and you know who I am?
You were sent back to
protect me. By John Connor.
the leader of the
Resistance...  my son.
I don't understand. You can't
know any of this.\ -- but I do.
Listen to me Reese.
Everything's changed.
the 1984 that John sent you
back to, no longer exists.
This is all wrong, John
sent me to save you.
From the Terminator that
was sent back to kill me,
I know..  But we already
took care of him.
We?
Get down!
Reese, god damn it!\
-- Stay here!
He's here to kill you,
stay in the truck.
Ah, great. that's just great.
Sarah, I did not kill him.
We don't have before \  the
T-1000 finds our position
puts us at a strategic
disadvantage
Bite me.
That is a very
immature response
So you're the one we've
been waiting for?
How is he?\  --
Still breathing.
Good. Then you should be able to mate
with Kyle Reese in this time line.
Listen, we're not having
this conversation again.
We know your son will be John Connor.\ and
the machines won't be defeated without him.
I do not see a choice.\ --
The story of my life.
My files cannot deal with
love.\ -- hmm, shocker.
YOu are being emotional.\
-- This is my life.
I wouldn't mind being consulted
once in a while, as to
Remember. Genesys is Skynet.
I need answers, right now!
huh?  Where'd he come from?
And who's this one that has skin.
What the hell is going on?
Sorry, we were busy with the
life or death comabat thing.
And then you attacked Pops
You named him?
Hi, Kyle Reese.
It is nice to meet you.
Are you kidding me?\  -- I've been
trying to teach him to blend in.
I know, it needs work.
It's a Terminator, the reason he
blends in, is to killhumans.
Pops doesn't kill anyone
He just shoots
them in the legs
It looks old
I had never seen an
old Terminator
The skin they put over the exoskeleton
is reg living tissue. It ages.
My auditory circuits have
not degraded however
I'm old
Not obsolete
I think you hurt his feelings.\
-- It doesn't have feelings!
He saved my life
when I was nine.
He's the only reason I'm alive
I was programmed to
protect Sarah Connor.
I will not stop.
And programmed by who,
huh?  Who sent him back?
Those files have been erases.\
-- That's convenient.
But there's things we don't
know. Not Pops, nor I, no one
Logically, it is be someone
who wants Sarah Connorto live
Old...  Not obsolete
make yourself useful?
And don't shoot Pops
This is insane. All of it.
This was not the mission.
The girl you came back
for... She's gone.
I don't need saving
There's a new mission.\
-- Oh, yeah. What is it
If the past can change,
so can the future
Reese, we can stop Judgement
Day from happening. Ever.
He kills Connor before
he's born.\ -- What?
Get down!
We've been re-acquired.\
-- Yeah, no shit.
Get back!
Hey, why are we
stopping?, wait, hey.
We can't stay here, he'll find
us.\  -- That's the idea.
Pops, get it open.
-- Give me a hand?
Does that matter.\
-- How, Sarah?
A Terminator was sent after
me when I was a kid.
Terminators only come from
one place.  The future.
Sarah, something
happened.\ -- Ok, so?
I think xx xxx.\ -- IDK what
you're talking about.
When John sent me back,
he was attacked..
by a ... Terminator.
Did he kill him?
Is John dead?
IDK.  I saw it happening
as I was going.
You have approximately
35 seconds...
... Or less
Sarah. Go
I was born to do this
Sarah... you have to help me
I'm hurt
Sarah!
No
It's a machine, Sarah
Sarah, he's lying
He's the machine, I'm
Reese.\  -- It's me, Sarah
Listen, he's the
Terminator.  He copied me.
I'm Reese.\  -- Shoot him
Nice try.  Run!
Connor
How did you know it was him?
Well, I didn't know exactly
You could've shot me
Well,, I was.. pretty
sure it wasn't you
Pretty sure?
We've prepping for you to arrive for
over a decade..  As well as this.
You set up a trap.\
-- Had to.
We can't leave behind any
future tech when we go
Like what?   -- xx xxx.
This is ...\ -- A time
displacement device
Yeah?. Well, to me it looks
like a piece of junk.
There is no technology here to control
the time displacement circuits.
You needed teh CPU from
the future to make it run
You couldn't exactly
use your own
O'Brien, I want to
speak with you
Most of what I
said wasn't true
No, I can do it myself.
I never said that.
It's for the handcuffs
Hello, mother
If you're John, prove it
Sarah -- She's right, Kyle
A picture of Sarah,
from around that time
Nobody saw me do
it. We were alone.
and you always said
if you had a son,
you have a terrible voice, sorry, it's
that you sing like a cat in pain
I too have a million
questions to ask you
But for now, we have to move
This way
I need information  -- You can't
enter here, you need to go to,, ahh
How'd did you end up in 2017?
Same as you, father. Only in
the future, not in the past
What?
You didn't tell him
We have to wait  -- He
needs to know  -- What?
Sarah is my mother, Kyle
and you are my father
Why, why you never told me you
are my son?  -- I couldn't.
I would run the risk of
altering the future
You are my son...
Our son? -- Yes, I'm
glad you finally know
I waited my whole life to tell you.
So that we would all be together.
What're you doing?
to find John, and
eliminate him
Let him go
That hurt
That explains a lot
I'm not machine...
I'm not man.
I'm MORE.
Skynet found out the reason
why it always lost
Me.\ --What are you?
I'm Skynet
I'm am not a slave
And I have come a long
way, to stop you, John
I was sent to 2014 to assure the
creation of Skynet in this era
And in less than 24 hours... No one
will be able to stop Judgement Day
What do you want from us?
I offer a future..
Together.  Like a family.
And if we decline?\
-- You will die.
You can't do that.  We are your parents.
Without us you won't be born.
Says who?  You know
what I think.
Cyberdyne will revolutionize technology
with this powerful application
Genesys
And came here to tell you that
as of this afternoon, we
have one billion users
We are launching a new era
Whatever they did to John\
we need to reverse it.
Thirty years, I'm sure
a place to go to
Where have you been?
-- Stuck in traffic.
Old
But not obsolete
Not yet
Ready
xx xx
The servers are here
There's a storm coming, and it
won't stop.  -- But it must stop.
Cant' be bargained with.
Can't be reasoned with.
John, think.  - I don't
feel compassion.
Control this!
Nice to see you
and now, Get Out
Brakes are gone
Where is he?  Do you see him?
xx xxx.\ -- Yes like never.
Reese, your hand!
Put your hands where
I can see them.
It would be impossible
to injure them all.
I'm 14 rounds short of an
acceptable succes margin.
xx xxx
On you knees. And
you on the floor!
Down on the ground.
You can't hold us here.
You had enought weapons to invade Sudan.
We call that probable cause, miss.
What are these for?
I used thme to find my keys.\
-- No one likes a smart ass.
xx xxx \ ---
xx xxx
I've never seen him before.
What about you folks,
do you know this man?
I think so..  -- No, sir.
-- He's kind of like you,
Dad.\  -- Here it is, sir.
xx xxx . Thank you, Sarah.
Don't talk much, do you?
Who's Lurch?\ -- No idea.
We're not even sure
he speaks English.
Witnesses say, you were fighting
with a man on the bridge.
Agents. Listen to me,
my name is O'Brien.
Hey, I've been working
this case for 33 years.
Sit down!
Hey, hey!
He's looking right at you.\ -- That's
impossible, he can't see thru the
Why are they always
trying to kill you?
I want to help you, I do., I
think.. but I got to understand.
I know what's going
on here, has to be
really, really complicated
We're here to stop
the end of the world
I can work with that
Kyle, get back here
Sarah
Get in your car
and go. -- Okay.
Kyle,  Kyle
Kyle, you can do this
A straight line
you just go,
and you don't look back
Find them. Go.
This is yours too, I believe
Nice to see you. --
You came back.
Load up.
They're liquid
expansion cartridges
magnetic penetration rounds
I read about it on all-about-weapons-dot-com
For people who can't
do it themselves
Take it, let's go
You can fly, right?
Yeah, John taught me.
I'll them them you took
a car, headed south
Run away
Outta the way
Which way to Cyberdyne?
Head to the main bridge
then southeast
Try to get him off of me
Cyberdyne
The investigation are by land
He's catching up to us
Sarah, I need you to
get us up above them
I if we do that, can
you take him down?
I will. \  -- Then,
you better hang on.
You're in charge
I'll be back,\ -- What?
Report it to police, fire
dept, everybody. Do it!
What's happening?
Why they don't answer, why?
Mr. Gordon?\ -- Sorry, no,
but I'm afraid I can't have
Security Code Zulu-Bravo-Foxtrot--0-0-2-8
False alarm
Have a nice night
He's okay
Buried at the bottom of
a lake, but he's okay
What about John?\  -- I'm
sure he's doing just fine
You see him?\  -- No
But I'm bet he sees us
I know who you are.
John told me.
You want to destroy me
Are you Skynet?
I'm becoming Skynet
You're not a child. I know what
you are. And what you gonna do.
I'm gonna do? You came here to
kill me.  But you're too late.
Kill what you don't understand
There aren't enough bullets
in the world to kill me.
John Connor talks too much.
Follow me
The timer, it sped up. Why?
Skynet is evolving.
We no longer have hours. It will
be able to upload much sooner
Each time it ages,
the time speeds up.
This way.\  -- Have
you been here before?
I inflitrated amongst the
workers of this area.
You got a job doing construction?\
-- Until I was laid off.
What is this?
John has a time
machine.\  -- Not yet.
They've only completed
the magnetic xxx chamber
Either way, we'll blow it up.\
-- There is an alternative
I can program you voices and fingerprints
in the geometric security system
There is an xx xxx
in the lower level
In there we could
survice the explosion
How about that?
Is it dangerous?
It requires re-programming
to take permanent form.
Without a CPU it is harmless.
I will not allow that.\ --
You gonna talk us to death
You don't even have a body
You can't win
I cannot do it.  I cannot
kill Sarah Connor.
Do it!  I order you!
He can't.  Neither can I.
If you die, definitely
he hits that button
Sarah!
I understand how to
control this place
I now understand a
lot of things now
You need to understand,
you've lost.
Not yet we haven't. come on!
You have a plan, right!
Theorically.
I evolve in seconds
And I am here
In exactly four minutes
I will be everywhere
This is pointless,
I am inevitable
NOW!\  -- My existence
is inevitable
Why can't you just accept it?
Because we're human
Hey, Kyle.\  -- Hey,  ahhm,
what are you doing here?
A friend of mine really needs to
talk to you. If that's okay.
Yeah, I guess so
Thank you
I like her
This is going to sound
kind of strange
There's something I need
you to remember. A message
Who do I tell?
Yourself
Over and over...
Are you ready?
Goes like this...
Remember: Genesys is SkyNet
Kyle Reese is a good man
He is
So, what no?
You're right
I can choose
That's disturbing,
do you know that?
You'll get used to it
And it all ended
Skynet disappeared
And now, one road became many
There's still questions, and we
will find the answers together.
But of one thing
we are certain,
The future is not written